<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <attachedDocuments>Newsletter_Images/Chatter_Favorites_and_Settings.jpg</attachedDocuments>
    <attachedDocuments>Newsletter_Images/Credit_Details.jpg</attachedDocuments>
    <available>true</available>
    <description>Template for distributing Salesforce News Monthly Newsletter</description>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <letterhead>X2018_Newsletter_Template</letterhead>
    <name>Salesforce News</name>
    <style>freeForm</style>
    <subject>Salesforce News</subject>
    <textOnly>New Releases in Salesforce
 

Credit Details
Credit detail for your customer is now available on the Account Record, in the Customer Success Tab. This new section contains credit details such as risk level, credit limit, and AR balances. Information will appear in the Credit Details section when there is relevant data available. Please visit MyNCR to view invoices related to outstanding AR balances.


Coming Soon
With our last release of Product Scheduler, there was one thing you’ve asked for that we weren’t quite ready to release — but soon, we’ll release an update to Product Schedule that will revolutionize the way you create opportunities. We’re ready to help you save more time! 
Stay tuned…


Quarter Close Schedule
Click here to view a copy of the cut-off times for all quarter-end order and billing requests.


Chatter Desktop Discontinued
If you’ve been a loyal Chatter Desktop user, please note that Chatter Desktop is no longer supported by Salesforce. Going forward, all Chatter activity will require the use of your web browser, and is accessible on the Chatter Tab in Salesforce. 

Be sure to favorite groups such as NSC Community, NCR Global Sales, and GSO Café or other groups you follow so that you can easily keep up with the latest news. You can edit your Chatter preferences in your personal settings to ensure you’re seeing the latest updates. 


Lightning Reports and Dashboards
If you need help creating or editing reports with the new report layout, the Lightning Report Editor video in the Salesforce folder in SAM covers navigating the new layout and features available with Lightning Reports. 


If you have questions or need assistance, please reach out to our Salesforce Administration Team. 
 
Thank you, 
Linda Sherman</textOnly>
    <type>html</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
