<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>Invite for Synergy 2017</description>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <name>Synergy 2017 Invite</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Synergy 2017: Registration Now Open! Save $300 through April 14</subject>
    <textOnly>Synergy 2017: Registration Now Open! Save $300 through April 14

Registration is now open for NCR’s annual Synergy conference!

We invite you to join us for Connected Experiences, where we’ll explore how powerful connections – with consumers, across channels, and among other industry leaders – build the foundation for sustained growth and success. Shaped by the biggest trends in the marketplace as well as valuable insights from our customers and partners, this year’s Synergy promises to be the best yet. Take advantage of our Early Bird pricing through April 14 and save $300 off registration!

NCR Synergy 2017: Connected Experiences
June 26-28, 2017 | Gaylord Palms Resort and Convention Center | Orlando, FL

Our program is being built around your requests for more hands-on breakout sessions and examples of our solutions in action, expanded networking opportunities, and more time to meet with our solution experts. We’ll also be introducing exciting new engagement activities such as our Collaboration Lounge, and bringing back our popular Table Topic discussions during lunch

Register today – and be sure to check our event site for updates and details on our agenda, including keynote speakers, breakout sessions, networking opportunities, and more. We look forward to seeing you in June.
www.ncr.com/synergy


NCR Corporation 3097 Satellite Blvd. Duluth, GA 30096
©2017 NCR Corporation. All rights reserved. www.ncr.com
To unsubscribe or manage subscriptions, please click here .
NCR respects your privacy .</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
