<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>NCR wins the BEST ATM/Self Service Experience Award</description>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <letterhead>Susan_Taylor</letterhead>
    <name>NCR wins the BEST ATM/Self Service Experience Award</name>
    <style>freeForm</style>
    <subject>NCR wins the BEST ATM/Self Service Experience Award</subject>
    <textOnly>I am Susan Taylor with NCR and it’s our goal to help you meet your customer’s need for convenience, and a little wow factor, with service solutions like NCR’s SelfServ ATMs and Interactive Teller.



Are you familiar with NCR Interactive Teller?


NCR Interactive Teller combines video banking and remote transaction processing within the ATM to give your customer the choice of self-service or connecting with a teller.



Transforming yesterday’s financial institution into a “branch of the future” must leverage human and physical resources to:


Optimize space
Integrate with today’s digital technology
Meet consumer expectations
Lower per transaction costs ($4/physical teller, $1.20/Assisted &amp; $.60/ATM)





The current industry trend towards modernization and re-branding efforts means your branch transformation strategy and the solutions you deploy are more important than ever.



I’d welcome the opportunity to learn more about your personal branch transformation strategy and discuss which solutions you feel would best fit your vision for 2018 and beyond.



Reply to this email or give me a call at 937-221-9473 and we can discuss your current branch transformation strategy and which solutions would be the best fit for helping you reach your goals.


Kindest regards,

Susan


Susan Taylor
Account Executive
NCR Corporation

office: 937.221.9473
mobile: 937.502.5807
susan.taylor@ncr.com | ncr.com</textOnly>
    <type>html</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
