<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>false</available>
    <description>Marketing Automation Pre-Announcement</description>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <letterhead>NCRLogoLetterhead</letterhead>
    <name>Lead Nurturing and Scoring</name>
    <style>freeForm</style>
    <subject>Lead Nurturing and Scoring is finally here</subject>
    <textOnly>{!Receiving_User.FirstName},


Global Sales has partnered with Marketing Services in choosing Eloqua, a best-in-class marketing automation provider, to enable lead generation through nurturing and scoring.


With Eloqua, Marketing Services can:

Target the right buyer
Automatically nurture and score leads
Deliver sales intelligence

Deploying in April, the Eloqua system will enable our marketing partners to effectively and efficiently conduct campaigns and events, capture activities associated with nurturing current leads and contacts and generate net new leads for Sales.


What will be different about leads currently in NCR SalesCentral?

Lead records will no longer be entered into NCR SalesCentral.  All current leads will be transferred to the marketing automation system for nurturing and scoring.  Once a lead score indicates “sales ready,” all information about the lead will be carried over into NCR SalesCentral where you will be able to review and convert to an opportunity if appropriate or indicate if it needs further nurturing from marketing.


Will there be any change to my list of Contacts in SalesCentral?

Eloqua and NCR SalesCentral will share data.  As Eloqua receives updated information from contacts via forms, that information will be updated in NCR SalesCentral.  In addition, as marketing engages current contacts in marketing activities, the contact history will be updated with this information.


What if I want to opt my Contacts out of marketing communications?

In SalesCentral, you will no longer be able to edit the Email Opt-out Field.  Instead, you will see a link to Opt-Out Marketing Emails in the contact or lead record.  Selecting this link will update the contact or lead’s preferences in the marketing automation system, which will be the official record of reference for subscription status.

Will I have access to leads in the new system?

When a lead is assigned to you, you will receive an email and a notification in NCR SalesCentral.  In SalesCentral, you will be able to view the lead and the lead history, including online and offline marketing activity.


When will we receive training on the new features?

The introduction of these new lead nurturing and generation capabilities is just a part of our overall sales enablement strategy for 2012.  You will get more information as we conduct training in various locations around the world during a three-week period from April 30 to May 18, as part of the Sales Enablement Roadshow 2012.



Jack Knapp
Global Sales Operations
NCR Corporation

jack.knapp@ncr.com | www.ncr.com</textOnly>
    <type>html</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
