<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>Delivery Surcharges 2022</description>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <letterhead>NCRLogoLetterhead</letterhead>
    <name>Wendys Surcharge Communication 2022</name>
    <style>formalLetter</style>
    <subject>Surcharge and Leadtime Communication</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear Valued Customer,

As we continue to face challenges related to significant part and fuel cost increases, supply chain delays and other contributing factors, we remain committed to delivering best-in-class solutions and services to run restaurants around the world.  We take measures to do so in a cost-effective manner, but we are subject to the same impacts affecting businesses on a global scale.  Maintaining the quality and efficiency you expect necessitates temporary price increases and changes to lead times on some of our solutions and services.

Effective immediately, a new surcharge of $150/per terminal will be added to all new orders.  This new surcharge may be variable quarter over quarter based on the impact part and fuel costs and supply chain delays continue to have on our business.

This will show on quotes and invoices as:  9612-0002-0000 Quarterly POS Cost Surcharge per 5/24/2022 notice

As of May 1, surcharges will be applied to hardware maintenance requests with $12 added for part-only requests and $25 per device for part and technical requests.  These will be billed monthly in arrears at the end of the month based on actual dispatches.
Standard freight charges, where applicable, have been adjusted based on the latest costs.
Effective immediately, standard lead times for hardware are now 26 weeks.  Costs are based on lead times of 26 weeks or greater.  Faster lead times will require additional surcharges and/or may not be accommodated.  Connect with your account representative for special cases.

We appreciate your understanding during this challenging time.  We will continue to monitor the supply chain and macro-economic factors and commit to reviewing these surcharges every 90 days and keep you informed of any changes.

Best regards,

Dirk Izzo
President and General Manager, NCR Hospitality</textOnly>
    <type>html</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
