<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>2021 CSAT Survey Results Notes.09-13-21 RET CSAT Survey Results Note EN.EN Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>We are acting on your feedback</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear {{lead.First Name:default=Valued Customer}},
 
Thank you again to everyone who participated in our 2021 NCR Customer Satisfaction Survey. Your insights are a crucial part of how we learn, grow and make simple possible for you. 

We are excited to share that we saw continued improvement in the survey results, particularly in our overall Net Promoter Score (NPS). 

At the same time, we know that we can always continue to improve. Based on your responses to the survey, we are focusing on the following areas and actions within the NCR Retail business unit:



	- We are rolling out a new structure that establishes clear accountability and a single point of contact for our customers. This enables us to respond to incidents faster and significantly reduce the backlog of tickets.




	- We continue to remain focused on improving our Software Quality and the overall experience of our solutions. We are doing this through a number of different actions including automated processes that automatically check code against predefined convention rules as well as analytics to analyze code health.




	- We have established a project management system with our Professional Services teams to define hand-offs in support of client projects. Furthermore, we are increasing team capacity across all functions to drive velocity and help ensure continued focus to on-time delivery for our customer.


Our goal is to make significant improvements in these areas based on your feedback. We look forward to hearing from you how we are doing. 
 
As always, thank you for sharing your insights and for being an NCR customer.

Warmest regards,

David Wilkinson 
President and General Manager, NCR Retail

Eric Schoch
SVP, Global Retail Sales &amp; Field 
Operations
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
