<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>Inform Hospitality customers on the upcoming launch of a new customer portal</description>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>09-27-22 HOS Hurricane Shutdown Procedures.HOS Hurricane Shutdown Procedures 202</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Hurricane Shutdown Procedures</subject>
    <textOnly>Early today, Hurricane Ian strengthened into a major Category 3 storm and several coastal counties in western Florida have begun evacuations. We hope that you, your employees and your families stay safe during this difficult period. 

To protect against damages and continuity of our services, we have relocated POS equipment from our main staging depot in Florida to outside of the hurricane zone. Depending upon the timing and impact of the hurricane, our supply chain and implementation services may be impacted, and we are doing our best to minimize the impact in advance.     

If you are closing your restaurant in preparation, we wanted to provide the steps below to help you shut down your Aloha system properly.  

 Shutting Down Front of House Terminals:


	-  Be sure to do the master terminal last
	-  Touch the screen and enter Manager password
	-  Touch the button that reads ‘Functions’
	-  There will be four options to choose from; choose ‘System’
	-  In the bottom right-hand corner, touch the button labeled ‘Shut Down Terminal’
	-  The computer will then go black. Once the computer starts to reboot, turn the power to the machine off.
	-  Do this for each of your Front of House terminals, ending with the master terminal last.



 Shutting Down Back of House Site Controller:


	-  Left click on the Windows ‘Start’ button located in the lower left-hand of the screen.
	-  Choose ‘Shut Down’ from this menu.
	-  When prompted, make sur ‘Shut Down’ is marked and left click ‘OK’.
	-  When the computer tells you it’s safe to turn off, turn off the power to the computer.
	-  Ensure all electrical equipment is off the ground. 



 Network Hub:

Make sure the power is turned off and unplug the unit. 

When your system is restarted, it may need to run multiple End of Days. Please be sure to allow extra time for this process without forcing End of Day. Your system should come back up automatically once the End of Days have processed.

 If you have any questions, please call our support line at 844-249-9602.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
