<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>02-24-22 HOS eWeekly Newsletter.Email 1 02-24-22 HOS</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>NCR Payment Processing with Aloha EDC Now Available</subject>
    <textOnly>February 24, 2022
Support for NCR Payment Processing with Aloha EDC now in General Release
We announced on February 8th that NCR Payment Processing is now available for Aloha EDC users and is in 
General Release for the United States. NCR Payment Processing provides secure and cost-effective processing with acceptance of all major payment types across all channels, from authorization to clearing and settlement. With no new hardware required and a quick process to switch to NCR Payment Processing, this integration expands our addressable market and enables us to sell Payment Processing into our Aloha install base more easily.

Some of the features and benefits available include:


	- 
One partner to handle both POS and payments





	- No large up-front investment to transition to NCR Payment Processing




	- Next-day funding is standard, which means quicker access to funds




	- AVS and CVV verification to reduce chargeback liability




	- Self-service management of reporting and dashboards


Additional documentation can be found on Seismic &lt;[[https://email.ncr.com/NjA1LUJRWS03NDAAAAGCp0e3NyQ0DpJas9xY20M08ByJCI9Lp1kVqE6f5Rglakua-PbyOI18VNs49hJo7_QW_hFF7kM=]]&gt;, and training was conducted on the Partner Enablement Call February 18 &lt;[[https://ncr.csod.com/ui/lms-learning-details/app/video/bbebe3e7-0c2d-453d-88c7-cf896d0c0652]]&gt; (NCRU Course # 86838).
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
