<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>12-14-22 HOS Aloha Cloud User Groups.12-14-22 HOS Aloha Cloud User Groups Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Invitation: NCR Aloha Cloud User Group</subject>
    <textOnly>Hello,

In 2023, we are introducing the Aloha Cloud User Group. Members of our user groups will play a vital role in helping NCR continue to shape its technology by providing feedback and guidance on our offerings, solutions and service levels. The members&apos; experience and insight will also help us better understand how to alleviate roadblocks to improve the user experience.

We invite you to apply for this opportunity to help shape and inform the 
future of Aloha Cloud.

The Aloha Cloud User Group has the following objectives: 



	- Evaluate current state of products, sharing candid feedback on product or service gaps and strengths
	- Preview and help prioritize product roadmap strategy and timeline
	- Share industry trends and drivers impacting your organization


Member Benefits &amp; Participation:



	- The opportunity to influence our stretegy roadmap
	- Peer networking and access to NCR&apos;s product leadership
	- Early access to new features and first invites to beta groups


Upon accepting an invitation from NCR, we ask a commitment to attend all three meetings throughout the year. Our first meeting will take place in late February with details to follow. We anticipate the following meetings will take place during Q2 and Q3.

If you are interested in learning more, please fill out this brief form &lt;[[https://forms.microsoft.com/r/Z3LXPr4b6Y]]&gt; or contact your NCR Account Executive. Please note that filling out the form does not commit you; it only verifies your interest and availability. We will be in touch in the coming weeks to notify selected clients of their formal invitation.

The deadline to express interest is January 3, 2023.

FAQ
Will my participation and feedback be confidential? 
Yes, all participants will be required to sign an NDA. NCR will be sharing product strategy details in these sessions and ask that due to the sensitivity of this information, all materials and discussions are kept confidential.

Will I have to travel?
Our first session will be virtual with the 
possibility of in-person meetings later in the year. We will plan to have hybrid meeting capabilities for those who may not be able to make it in person.

Who 
am I representing?
You are the voice for your segment of hospitality, e.g: quick service, fast casual.

Do I have to be the 
representative?
We ask whoever represents your organization be a senior leader in operations, IT or a related role that includes ownership and/or expertise in the point of sale. If you are not the right person to participate, please indicate who to reach out to in your nomination form.

What’s the process? 
We will review the clients who express interest and based on availability, fit and number of people interested we will contact those who are selected for next steps.
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
