<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>My NCR Training Session.MyNCR Spanish Training</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>MyNCR Spanish Training</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;
MyNCR Spanish Training
Hi,
 
You are invited to a live training session on MyNCR. This session will be provided in Spanish and will take place Tuesday, March 24 at 11:00AM EDT. We will be covering all of the core features that you need to run your business – including ordering, invoices, and key management.

Shortly, you will receive a separate email with a link to register for the WebEx session. Upon registration, you will be provided with confirmation and an event invite that can be saved to your calendar.

We will also be sharing written MyNCR training materials in Spanish and a recording of the live training session at a later date.
 
Thank you,
MyNCR Team
Hola,
 
Usted está siendo invitado a una sesión de entrenamiento en vivo para el uso de MyNCR. Esta sesión será impartida en Español y está programada para el Martes 24 de Marzo a las 11:00AM EDT. Se estarán cubriendo todas las opciones y funcionalidades para correr adecuadamente su negocio y esto incluirá, generación de ordines, seguimiento a facturas y administración de llaves y licencias.

En breve, usted estará recibiendo un correo electrónico con un link para registrarse a la sesión WebEx. Una vez que se registre usted estará recibiendo una confirmación y una invitación que podrá guardar en su calendario para no perder la fecha.

De igual forma estaremos compartiendo documentación y materiales de entrenamiento para el uso de MyNCR en español y de igual forma se realizará una grabación de la sesión de 
entrenamiento WebEx para su posterior consulta.
 
Muchas Gracias,
MyNCR Team
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
