<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>04-22-21 HOS eWeekly Newsletter.Subject Line Test</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Insight Polling Upgrade</subject>
    <textOnly>April 22, 2021
Insight Polling Upgrade
NCR is upgrading sites to the new Pulse Agent process to use for Insight polling beginning on Monday, April 26, 2021. Sites will be upgraded in waves on Monday through Thursday each week, and the process will continue for several months until all Insight customers have been upgraded. There will be no interruption to our customers’ operations during the upgrade and no action is required by their team. However, please instruct customers to review the Insight Polling FAQs &lt;[[https://ncr.quickbase.com/up/bqe6gx23b/g/rdb/ek/va/Insight Polling FAQs.pdf]]&gt; for important information on actions they must complete to maintain their site configuration post-upgrade. Contact support@alohaenterprise.com &lt;[[mailto:support@alohaenterprise.com]]&gt; if you have any questions.
Channel NCR Payment Solutions Promotional Offer
In response to our channel partner’s request to lower the barrier of entry for customers who need an EMV contactless payment solution, NCR is offering a special promotion for up to two Equinox Luxe 6200 tethered devices per site for customers who 
sign up for NCR Payment Solutions. Read the details here &lt;[[https://ncr.quickbase.com/up/bqe6gx23b/g/rdd/ek/va/NCR Payment Solutions - Channel Q2 Promotional Offer v2 4-20-21.pdf]]&gt;.
Discontinuation of NCR Kitchen Controller (KC4) with Audio
Due to a shortage of audio components, NCR will no longer be selling the Kitchen Controller (KC4) units with audio features or providing them as part of our return to service model. If you have customers using the NCR Kitchen Controller (Class 1924), it is critical that you read, understand, and act upon this announcement. Read the full announcement here &lt;[[https://ncr.quickbase.com/up/bqe6gx23b/g/rdc/ek/va/KC4 Audio Functionality Removal Announcement FINAL 4-19-21.pdf]]&gt;.
Command Center Client and Secure Access Release, Version # 19.2.3
This release is a maintenance update of the Command Center and Secure Access Clients 19.2 General Release. This Client-only release is being provided specifically in the Azure US Data Center (NUA01-SEC) for easing the user’s migration experience into the new data center.

The updated version will be installed on or after April 22, 2021 for users who are migrated to NUA01-SEC upon their next login to that client. To learn more about the enhancements included in this release, click here &lt;[[https://ncr.quickbase.com/up/bqe6gx23b/g/rda/ek/va/Release Notes - CMC and SA Clients version 19.2.3 - 4-8-21.pdf]]&gt;.
Touch Free Dining Pays Off for Restaurants
Consumers are eager to resume dining out and enjoying the company of good friends and family. But safety still remains their biggest concern. It’s vital for restaurant operators to create a touch free experience, such as pay-at-table, to attract customers to dine on site. Hear some thoughts on this topic from our very own Dirk Izzo, President and GM of NCR Hospitality, in a recent article &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/blogs/restaurants/how-pay-at-the-table-really-pays-off]]&gt; that he penned.
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
