<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>07-27-21 HOS WTAC Board Update - DUMAC Acquisition.WTAC Board Update - DUMAC Acq</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>NCR RaaS Support Update</subject>
    <textOnly>To Our Franchise Community
It has been a few months now since the integration of Dumac into NCR started and we wanted to provide an update on the work to date that has been completed along with a look into the roadmap ahead. As we entered into this partnership, we felt very strongly that the initial focus and investment should be toward the support organization. Similarly, an improvement plan has been formulated for operations, implementations, and installations. This is under final review and will be shared with Wendy’s leadership this coming week for targeted deployment by the end of next week.NCR recognizes that the Helpdesk performance is not where 
we want it to be. However, with the improvements achieved thus far, we are confident that you will soon start seeing a reduction in speed of answer times, improved first call resolution and better knowledge to proactively prevent issues from occurring. The following is a recap of efforts to date in Helpdesk.


	- We successfully transitioned the Helpdesk to the NCR Telephony system


	- This will make reporting more accurate and enable more staff to take calls during peak times thanks to soft phone routing
	- On the go-live day we were able to answer calls within seconds, this reduced wait time dramatically against historical speed of answer metrics




	- We have successfully transitioned to the NCR Incident Management system


	- This will provide better reporting and classification of Support issues
	- This will enable better problem management and a stronger knowledge base to improve first call resolution and proactively prevent issues from happening




	- NCR Aloha Advanced Support has been integrated to address more complex Aloha issues faster and reduce the current backlog


	- Courtesy Callback functionality will be in place at the end of July Stores can focus on serving their customers versus waiting on the phone


	- We have enabled the support functionality within the Pulse mobile app for non-urgent issues Enables case creation through the app from any device, anywhere, anytime


	- Does not require a phone call or email
	- Notes, photos, screenshots and documents can all be added through the app
	- Provides immediate confirmation of your case with an incident ID
	- Updates and incident status provided real-time within the app
	- Global outage notifications are notified automatically




	- Performance issues are largely driven by a staffing gap that we are working on closing as soon as possible


	- The tight labor market has created challenges, but we are making progress
	- We continue recruiting efforts domestically to staff to targeted levels
	- We have identified and are staffing key leadership roles




	- A 3rd Shift has been created in Serbia to provide around the clock coverage and execute overnight helpdesk tasks


	- Development time for the majority of personnel is approximately 3 weeks and we anticipate most of the new team members to start answering phones and working on backlog in the next couple of weeks



If you have any questions or concerns, or if there is ever an escalation needed on your behalf, please feel free to contact us directly for help.Best,








Sesha Madapoosi
GM NCR/Dumac
(813) 418-2353
Seshadri.Madapoosi@ncr.com



Sandy Preizler
Senior Vice President, NCR Hospitality
(914) 715-9045
Sandy.Preizler@ncr.com
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
