<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>10-21-21 HOS TECHFEST 2021.TECHFEST Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>TECHFEST 2021 – REGISTRATION NOW OPEN!</subject>
    <textOnly>Get ready for our annual Hospitality technical conference - TechFest 2021! TechFest runs November 9-11 and is completely virtual. No travel required and attendance is free! Click here &lt;[[https://on.lenos.com/ncr/TechFest2021/Content/Overview]]&gt; to register for TechFest 2021! It’s important to register now &lt;[[https://on.lenos.com/ncr/TechFest2021/Content/RegisterNow]]&gt; so that we may gather important information in advance. Registration closes Friday, November 5th. 

At TechFest 2021, we will have experts and product owners presenting over 15 topics with new and exciting product updates. Technicians will learn the latest implementation techniques for core solutions. Here’s a sample of some of the session content to be presented this year:



	- Wireless Implementation Best Practices




	- Menu and Order Services – Integrating with 3rd Party Applications




	- Digital Ordering Updates and Implementing Contactless Dine-In Best Practices




	- Aloha Simplification and Process Improvements




	- Aloha 19.x Updates with Keyless Licensing – Deployment and Strategy




	- Implementing NCR Order Pay Best Practices




	- NCR Payment Solutions sessions including Payments Troubleshooting, Payment Devices update, Implementation Best Practices and Converting Customers to NCR Payments Processing




	- Consumer Marketing Overview, How to kick off a Consumer Marketing Project, and other Consumer Marketing sessions


Register today for TechFest 2021 by clicking here &lt;[[https://on.lenos.com/ncr/TechFest2021/Content/Overview]]&gt;. 

We look forward to seeing you at TechFest 2021!
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
