<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>NCR Aloha SMB Customer Newsletter.03-04-21 HOS Newsletter Aloha SMB Customer.Ema</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>NCR Aloha: New options for your restaurant</subject>
    <textOnly>Hospitality hot topics
Restaurant wins COVID-19-related rent dispute
In a recent COVID-19-related rent dispute in Massachusetts, the court ruled in favor of the restaurant owner and against the landlord who terminated their 15-year lease and evicted them. It’s uncertain how other courts will use this case as precedent in deciding similar cases. 

 &lt;[[https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/burns--levinson-wins-summary-judgment-for-caffe-nero-in-covid-related-rent-dispute-with-landlord-in-suffolk-superior-court-301227695.html]]&gt;
Curbside delivery beyond the pandemic
Consumers will still use curbside pickup after dine-in services resume, so you should continue promoting your curbside services with push notifications, direct mail and on social media. 

 &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/blogs/restaurants/restaurants-pivot-during-pandemic]]&gt;
#What&apos;sNew@NCR
Online Ordering is getting a lot more powerful
Our new Digital Ordering &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/restaurants/aloha-pos/digital-ordering]]&gt; solution creates a powerful experience. We’ve started moving Aloha Online Ordering users to the platform that includes awesome new features:
- 
Customizable ordering experiences to include your brand&apos;s colors and fonts

	- 
Images galore to highlight your culinary creations and whet guests’ appetites

	- 
Digital Ordering Resizes to fit any device&apos;s screen

	- 
Integration with Drive powered by DoorDash, so you can deliver food without a fleet of drivers, still owning the customer experience and have all orders flow through Aloha
Take orders &amp; payments anywhere in your restaurant with Aloha Orderpay
OrderPay &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/restaurants/aloha-pos/aloha-orderpay]]&gt; puts the power of Aloha in your hands, literally. Your servers can carry this durable and versatile handheld POS everywhere they go to take orders and payments at the table, curb, patio &amp; more. 

 &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/restaurants/aloha-pos/aloha-orderpay]]&gt;
You&apos;ve got 2 new exciting Mobile Pay features!
They&apos;re here - 2 new features in Aloha Mobile Pay make a great experience even better:

Aloha Stored 
Value Payment Option
Guests can use a restaurant’s branded Aloha Stored Value gift cards in Mobile Pay – to pay the full bill, split it or combine multiple gift cards.

Text2Pay
Need a way to easily and securely take payments for call-in orders? Now you can. Enter the guest’s phone number in Aloha and they’ll receive a text link to pay their bill, saving time for everyone.

 &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/support/products/ncr-aloha/ncr-payments-training-for-aloha/learning-videos/ncr-mobile-pay-text2pay]]&gt;
Stay current with Aloha status updates
FREE: Get exactly what you need – convenient online access to Aloha status updates about the software’s health and performance. It’s easy to start receiving updates via text, email or RSS Feed. Subscribe &lt;[[https://status.aloha.ncr.com/]]&gt; today and set up your preferences.
Keep learning
Payments, made simple
Did you know NCR hosts free live payment webinars several times a month? Our payment experts explain complex concepts like reconciliations, chargebacks, statements and fees. Explore our on-demand payments training resources &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/support/products/ncr-aloha/ncr-payments-training-for-aloha]]&gt;.
Additional resources about creating contactless experiences
- 
Even during a pandemic, consumers crave experience from restaurants &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/blogs/restaurants/it-outsourcing-customer-experience]]&gt;

	- 
The importance of strengthening restaurant loyalty programs during the pandemic &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/blogs/restaurants/restaurant-loyalty-program-engagement]]&gt;

	- 
How restaurants can us innovation to engage with customers in contactless ways &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/blogs/restaurants/contactless-customer-innovation]]&gt;
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
