<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>12-22-21 RET Monthly Emerald Newsletter.12-22-21 RET Monthly Emerald Newsletter</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>NCR Emerald Community Newsletter – December 2021</subject>
    <textOnly>December 2021
Dear Emerald Community Members,
 
Thanks for the partnership in 2021 and we’re looking forward to a great 2022! We’re sending our final update of the year and looking forward to seeing you all in the New Year.
EMERALD COMMUNITY MEETINGS
Successful October Emerald Community Meeting – We held our Emerald Community meeting in October with approximately 60 participants from ten companies (Meijer, WinCo, Bashas’, BevMo!, Northgate, Federated Coop, Stater Bros., SpartanNash, Big-Y and NCR) in largely virtual attendance.Topics included the Emerald development process and plan and highlights from the POS release and Roadmap and Emerald deployment and upgrades. Thanks to those who took the time to fill-out the survey – we received 87% positive response, 13% neutral and 0% negative. Some of the feedback from excellent suggestions for future meetings, including:



	- &quot;Future enhancements and roadmap items”
	- &quot;Customer-lead roundtable discussions”
	- &quot;In-person would be better”


The date, time &amp; location of the next Emerald Community Meeting will be announced soon!

In the meantime, we are excited to be participating in the National Retail Federation show next month in New York City. If you plan to also be there, please come visit us at booth #4918!
EMERALD RELEASES AND ROADMAP
Have you checked out the public documentation portal that allows our Emerald customers to see the summary of latest release Emerald 1.6.3? You can access the Emerald POS content from the home page of https://docs.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://docs.ncr.com/]]&gt;. Here is a direct link to the Emerald POS overview &lt;[[https://docs.ncr.com/retail/emerald-pos/overview/]]&gt; page. The Release Notes &lt;[[https://docs.ncr.com/retail/emerald-pos/about/release-notes/version_1_6_1/]]&gt; are under &quot;About&quot;.

Here are some of the highlights from the 1.6.3 Emerald POS release:
REF 466012: Sale Price Query/Price Check Enhancement
REF 434033: Integration: Publish Events for any LP (Loss Prevention/CCTV) Product
REF 507097: L&amp;P Drive Cost Plus Discounts, by Sending Cost Price from the Catalog to the PE
REF 359488: Tender: Support Payment and Refund on Account – Charge Account Tender
REF 513229: Fuel/Tax – Support Fuel Tax for Canada (Inclusive and Exclusive in the Same Transaction
REF 479297: Sale: Display the Price per UOM to the Customer and Cashier when Selling/Weighted/ Quantity/ Volume Items
At the recommendation of our Advisory Board, we will recognize team members from both NCR and clients who have done outstanding work on the Emerald solution, pilots and rollouts.
Nili Zalkind joined Emerald product team as a Product Manager​ to drive strategic initiatives within NCR Retail for Emerald. Originally born in Israel, Nili has lived in Atlanta for 8 years. She holds a bachelor’s degree from Technion Israel Institute of Technology and a Masters degree from Ben-Gurion University of the Negev. She has more than 25 years of retail experience with Retalix and NCR. She is married with 3 daughters. In her free time, she loves to travel and explore new places, and loves to enjoy time with her family and friends.
Grace Chen joined Kristin Schoonover’s team as a Product Analyst this month to help lead key strategic projects for Emerald 2.0. Originally born in China, Grace has lived in Atlanta for 6 years and graduated from Georgia Tech in 2018. She has 3 years of experience with AAS subscription packages and supporting the quote to cash process, making her a major asset to our Emerald Product team. She has a cat named Mochi. In her free time, she loves to travel and enjoy time with her family and friends.
Vinod Kaky has joined NCR as a product manager. He has extensive background in engineering, program management, architecture, and product management over the last 18 years across varying domains of eCommerce, Retail, Insurance &amp; manufacturing. Vinod will help bring NCRs latest platform offering edge deployment to the market. On personal front Vinod spends weekends biking trails in and around Research Triangle Park, Durham along with his two beautiful little ones.
RETAILER UPDATES
On August 25th, BevMo converted from ACS to Emerald in their Livermore, CA location. They also run AMS Loyalty, Connected Payments and NCR Freshop. We are targeting a soft rollout starting in January 2022.
On September 27th, Stater Bros also made the move from ACS to Emerald overnight and opened their first pilot store in San Bernardino, CA. They quickly opened their second store on November 3rd in Whittier, CA including SCO for the first time in Stater Bros. history. They also run AMS Loyalty and Connected Payments.
Here are some of the progress highlights from the rest of the community:
- Emerald 1.5.211 in production stores- Emerald 1.6.203 in QA Lab- Emerald SCO Pilot targeting end of Q1 2022


- Marching towards Emerald Fuel pilot in Q1 2022
- Emerald v1.5.216 in lab. Upgrade to v1.5.217 late December
- Initiating Emerald Grocery Lab with Emerald 1.6.3
- Successful AMS7 Upgrade in Prod
- Emerald 1.6.2 in test lab
- 
Emerald Pilot targeting Q1 2022


- Selected DAX/HQ/AMS
  Lab set-up complete
- Emerald 1.6.3 in lab with early 2022 target deployment
- New St. Louis Foundry store opened in November
 
  
- Completed rollout of all 42 sites
- Upgraded entire estate
- Emerald 1.5.214 in production
- Martin’s banner rollout of Emerald complete (POS, SCO, Fuel, RX)
- Emerald 1.5.211 in production
- Emerald 1.5.214 in lab


- End to End testing with Aurus Payments and Quotient electronic coupons
- Pilot planned for May/June 2022 with Emerald 1.6.4 and AMS 7.14
- Pre-UAT lab testing of Emerald 1.6.3 and AMS 
7.12
As we look back on this year we’re thinking of all of the progress we’ve made together and are truly grateful for your partnership and engagement. On behalf of all of us here at NCR – and the Emerald team especially - we wish you and your families the happiest of holidays and a joyful new year!


THANK YOU!

Team Emerald
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
