<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>2021 CSAT Action Notes Cycle 2.01-11-22 HOS CSAT Action Note EN.EN Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>We are acting on your feedback</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear {{lead.First Name:default=Valued Customer}},
 
At NCR, we remain focused on our customers’ success. Your input helps us learn how we can further improve the services and products we offer you.

We are excited to see significant improvement in our most recent NCR Customer Satisfaction Survey. However, there is always room to do better and we continue to listen to your feedback to identify areas for enhancement. Based on the responses we received, we are focusing on the following areas and actions within the NCR Hospitality business unit.


	- Invoicing—over the past several months, we have been building new infrastructure that will deliver multiple enhancements to our invoicing experience, including deeper 
automation to drive accuracy and a new dynamic invoicing structure that will allow for customer-directed formatting of invoices to provide customers the information they need in the way they need to receive it.




	- Software—it is our goal to provide world-class solutions for our customers. To ensure we continue to improve in stability and usability of our software, we are focusing on significantly expanding our testing scope and automation; releasing cloud-based configuration features for easier menu, price, and employee changes; and launching new tools to make upgrading easier and reduce opportunities for error.




	- Service Delivery—building on the positive feedback received following our Customer Support evolution to a pod approach in 2021, we are applying those same principles as 
well as other tactics in all areas of our business to get even closer to our customers, drive efficiencies and make it easier to work with NCR.


We aim to drive substantial progress in each of these areas in 2022. Our customer satisfaction process will continue and invite you to continue sharing your feedback, letting us know how we are doing in these areas and others.
 
Thank you for being an NCR customer and sharing your opinion with us.

Warmest regards,
 
Dirk Izzo
President and General Manager, NCR Hospitality

Sandy 
Preizler 
Senior Vice President, NCR Hospitality Sales
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
