<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>04-19-21 CX Sofia Customer Communication.Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Your voice counts in helping NCR meet your needs</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear {{lead.First Name:default=Valued Customer}}, 

As we continue into 2021, we know that now more than ever, you need a partner who understands your business needs. We at NCR are proud to work by your side, delivering on high quality service experiences to help you deliver on your business requirements and take your business to the next level.
Together, we continue to be better. And we remain fully committed to driving improvements to help you achieve your network transformation goals. 
 
This year, we continue to enhance the customer experience based on your feedback. Your account manager will be sharing some of those details with you. 

Here are some highlights of those improvements:

- Strategic partnerships to help deliver on your digital transformation strategy
	- Solution innovation with edge computing
	- Continued investment in our strategic portfolio roadmap
	- Achieved solid progress producing higher quality invoicing


Beginning on Monday, April 19, you’ll start receiving our first 2021 relationship survey. It takes only about three minutes to complete and focuses on several ways to strengthen our strategic relationship. The survey is flexible, so you can skip areas that don’t apply. And we love written feedback. This is a big help in understanding the results. 

Your voice truly matters and we’re eager to hear from you. Thank you for your feedback and support. It’s a privilege to be your strategic partner.

Sincerely, 

Sophia Williams
SVP and General Manager
NCR Telecom and Technology
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
