<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>12-17-20 HOS eWeekly Channel Newsletter.12-17-20 HOS eWeekly Channel Newsletter</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>eWeekly - Increase Sales</subject>
    <textOnly>December 17, 2020
Marketing Materials that Increase Sales &lt;#MarketingMaterialsthatIncreaseSales&gt;
Accept payments securely for phone orders &lt;#AcceptPaymentsSecurely&gt;
Year 2 Microsoft Extended Security Update (ESU) Available for Windows 7 Professional &lt;#Year2MESUAvailable&gt;
Reminder: Fulfillment Orders on Christmas Day – December 25, 2020 &lt;#ReminderFulfillmentOrders&gt;
Marketing Materials that Increase Sales
Operators need the best tools and technology to help them accommodate evolving guest expectations and run a successful business. For customers on older versions of Aloha, modernizing their restaurant with the latest technology available in Aloha Essentials is the best way to achieve the digital transformation that will grow their business. 

NCR has an extensive library of marketing resources available on Seismic &lt;[[https://ncr.seismic.com/Link/Content/DCA3VbBgTSRUOv7G7uvogBUg#/?anchorId=3b5e20b6-81f9-4e4c-be5e-fc93081eb57e]]&gt; to support your efforts when speaking with your current customers about the benefits of updating their Aloha solution. Leverage all the materials at your disposal – eBooks, flyers, presentations, infographics, and more – to make a positive impression with your customers and win more deals. If you don’t have access to Seismic, talk to your site administrator today, so you can begin using these materials immediately.

Accept payments securely for phone orders
Taking credit card information over the phone for pick-up orders exposes both restaurants and their customers to risk. Operators can securely process payments without ever verbally exchanging the customer’s credit card information using NCR Mobile Pay. They can simply give the customer a 6-digit code during the call and instruct them to pay their check at ncrpay.com using the code provided. When the customer arrives to pick up their order, it’s already been paid for, so they can quickly be on their way. It’s that easy. Learn More &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/restaurants/mobile-pay]]&gt;
Year 2 Microsoft Extended Security Update (ESU) Available for Windows 7 Professional
The Year 1 Microsoft Extended Security Update (ESU) for Windows 7 Professional expires on January 13, 2021. This ESU supports PCI security protocols, so if customers fail to remain current with all security updates and hotfixes it may negatively impact their PCI compliance. Let your customers know that the Year 2 Microsoft Windows ESU key is now available for purchase to continue running Microsoft Windows 7 Professional Non-Embedded Operating System after the January 13, 2021 deadline and it will be effective through January 11, 2022.
Reminder: Fulfillment Orders on Christmas Day – December 25, 2020
Friday, December 25, 2020 is a U.S. national holiday observed by NCR and our logistics provider. It is not considered a business day, so all orders will be fulfilled as listed below. The cut off time for all orders is 6:00 p.m. ET. 

 	-   Next Calendar Day (NCD) service level orders are not affected by the holiday. These orders will ship the same day as ordered and will be delivered the following day.    	-   Next Flight Out (NFO) service level orders will be available every day, including Friday, December 25th.   	-   Next Business Day (NBD) service level orders will be fulfilled on the next business day following the holiday according to the grid below.

AED Next Business Day (NBD) Fulfillment Schedule         Thursday, 12-24-20     Thursday, 12-24-20     Monday, 12-28-20       Friday, 12-25-20     Monday, 12-28-20     Tuesday, 12-29-20       Monday, 12-28-20     Monday, 12-28-20     Tuesday, 12-29-20</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
