<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>MURTEC 2020.Email #1</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Going to MURTEC? 3 Big Reasons to See NCR</subject>
    <textOnly>Third-party delivery tablets tangling up your counters. Orders coming in from everywhere. Employee turnover and rising labor costs. Technology that just. keeps. changing.

Disruption is everywhere. And it’s making your restaurant business complex. 

That’s why we’d like to personally invite you to MURTEC 2020 this year. We’re on a mission to find out what’s challenging you—and how we can help, starting with a modernized NCR Aloha, our restaurant solution subscriptions, remote maintenance and more.

Meet with NCR &lt;[[http://ncr.com/events/murtec-2020]]&gt; at Booth 66 and discover 3 ways we can move you forward:


	- 

Simplified, scalable solutions and a new platform architecture that digitally transforms your restaurant so you can serve guests from your four walls and beyond— integrating your POS, self-ordering kiosks, kitchen, menus, back office, loyalty, third-party operations &amp; more into one system

	- 

Futuristic technologies that create frictionless service, such as facial recognition payments

	- Complete advisory and consulting services, plus software, hardware, support and managed services that run your restaurant end-to-end


Also, grab your free invitation &lt;[[https://forms.office.com/Pages/ResponsePage.aspx?id=9_FNrh5hT0SJfvlk4SBRcRFvOfptvMtNjDzKoPoPWexUNFpDVldUWTE0VFlNOEMyTVdMR0kwRjlIOC4u]]&gt; to our NCR Cocktail Reception and spend time talking shop with our restaurant experts, industry leaders and your peers. Space is limited.

See you in Las Vegas!
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
