<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>MyNCR  Training Materials.MyNCR Training Materials</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>MyNCR Training Materials</subject>
    <textOnly>Thank you to everyone that was able to join our Spanish MyNCR training session last week. If you were not able to join or would like to watch again, you can download the recording here &lt;[[https://ncr.webex.com/ec3300/eventcenter/enroll/register.do?siteurl=ncr&amp;formId=111240602&amp;confId=111240602&amp;formType=1&amp;loadFlag=1&amp;eventType=1&amp;accessType=viewRecording&amp;internalPBRecordTicket=4832534b00000004d659e2d76d7e82e08aced2e27a21d9805e31b8b5e14a5d46490825fcea0d56bc]]&gt;.

In addition, you can find our training documentation here &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/myncr-training/partners]]&gt; in both English and Spanish. This documentation will be available in the MyNCR Help Center shortly.

Lastly, you can find answers to the questions submitted during the training session here &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/content/dam/myncr-assets/MyNCR-Q%26A-Dual-Language.pdf]]&gt;. We will be following up with answers for any questions which were not included in this document.

Thank you,
MyNCR Team
Hola,

Gracias a todos los que pudieron unirse a nuestra sesión de capacitación en español MyNCR la semana pasada. Si no pudo unirse o desea ver de nuevo, puede descargar la grabación aquí &lt;[[https://ncr.webex.com/ec3300/eventcenter/enroll/register.do?siteurl=ncr&amp;formId=111240602&amp;confId=111240602&amp;formType=1&amp;loadFlag=1&amp;eventType=1&amp;accessType=viewRecording&amp;internalPBRecordTicket=4832534b00000004d659e2d76d7e82e08aced2e27a21d9805e31b8b5e14a5d46490825fcea0d56bc]]&gt;.

Además, puede encontrar nuestra documentación de capacitación aquí &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/myncr-training/partners]]&gt; en inglés y español. Esta documentación estará disponible en el Centro de ayuda de MyNCR en breve.

Por último, puede encontrar respuestas a las preguntas enviadas durante la sesión de capacitación aquí &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/content/dam/myncr-assets/MyNCR-Q%26A-Dual-Language.pdf]]&gt;. Seguiremos con respuestas a cualquier pregunta que no se haya incluido en este documento.

Muchas Gracias,
MyNCR Team</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
