<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>04-03-22 T&amp;T Customer Survey Letter - Sophia Williams.Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Your feedback is important to us</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear {{lead.First Name:default=Valued Customer}}, 

At NCR, we strive to be your strategic partner every day. Thank you for trusting us to provide high-quality service and to deliver on your brand promise. While we remain committed to fostering a successful relationship, we recognize there is room for improvement to continuously deliver a differentiated customer experience. 

From sales to service, our goal is to earn your trust and confidence while making it easy to do business together. We continue to enhance the customer experience based on your feedback. Your account manager will be sharing some of those details with you. 

Here are some highlights of those improvements that we have put into motion since the last survey:


	- 
Updated our strategic account planning approach aimed at building a tighter roadmap together and delivering on your digital transformation strategy

	- 
Expanded our managed services capabilities and new remote monitoring platform to provide greater flexibility, agility, and automation

	- 
Launched various service delivery innovations to improve efficiency, real-time data capture, and reporting
Beginning April 4th, you will start receiving a personal link to our 2022 relationship survey, which takes approximately three minutes to complete. It focuses on ways we can strengthen our strategic relationship and your ongoing NCR experiences. The survey is flexible, so you can skip questions that don’t apply to you. Additionally, we encourage and value written responses to help us understand the results and exceed expectations in the future.

Thank you again for the confidence you have placed in NCR. We value your opinion and plan to use your feedback as a valuable tool for improvement. Your voice truly matters, and we thank you for your business and for your partnership.

Sincerely,

Sophia Williams
SVP and General Manager
NCR Telecom and Technology
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
