<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>03-11-21 HOS biWeekly Newsletter.Major Discount on S500 Servers Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Major Discount on S500 Servers</subject>
    <textOnly>March 11, 2021
NCR is Offering Discount on S500 Servers!
NCR has approximately 600 new S500 servers that we are offering at a deeply discounted price of over 50% off the MRP (list price). These S500 servers are brand new, in the box, and will come with Windows 10 licenses, setting them up for a long product lifecycle. They function perfectly and are only being discounted due to the introduction of the S600 server class. Also, all of these new S500 servers come with a standard 1-year hardware warranty. This limited supply of servers will be sold on a “first come- first serve” basis, so get your orders in today to take advantage of the discount!

The S500 servers have been set up with the discounted price in the channel partners’ catalog. The two PID’s and their sales prices are listed below. To place an order, follow the normal process for ordering any other product. For any questions, contact Austin.Anderson@NCR.com &lt;mailto:Austin.Anderson@NCR.com&gt;.
NCR PID


PID Description


Sales Price



1612-0088-8801
S500-SF 8GB i3 500GB HDD DVD W10 IoT 2019

$ 805



1612-0072-8801
S500-SF 8GB i3 dual 500GB HDD RAID DVD LOCK W10

$ 888
Digital Signage Drives Sales, Improves CX

Digital signage and menu boards are redefining customer experiences, and amid COVID-19, are helping to drive sales. Brands using digital signage are seeing up to 33% increased sales. More restaurants – not just major QSR chains – can implement this technology, and it’s important to select the right digital signage system for a restaurant’s unique goals. Read more &lt;[[https://hospitalitytech.com/using-digital-signage-drive-sales-improve-cx]]&gt;
Stay Current With Aloha Status Updates
If you haven’t subscribed to the Aloha Status Page &lt;[[https://status.aloha.ncr.com/]]&gt;, you’re missing the opportunity to stay informed with 24 x 7 x 365 access to updates about the health and performance of our software. There’s even the added convenience to receive updates via text, email, or RSS Feed.

&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
