<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Channel Newsletter.Newsletter 5.22</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>eWeekly: May 22</subject>
    <textOnly>May 21, 2020
Fulfillment Orders Reminder for Memorial Day
As a reminder, Monday, May 25, 2020 is a U.S. national holiday observed by NCR and our logistics provider, so all orders will be fulfilled as listed below. The cut off time for all orders is 6:00 p.m. ET.


	- Next Business Day (NBD) service level orders will be fulfilled on the next day following the holiday.
	- Next Calendar Day (NCD) service level orders are not affected by the holiday. These orders will be shipped the same day as ordered and delivered the following day.
	- Next Flight Out (NFO) service level orders will be available every day, including Monday, May 25th.
Payment Gateway Virtual Training
Don’t miss this opportunity on May 26 – 27, 2020 to learn more about the NCR Payment Gateway solution, formerly known as Connected Payments. Topics covered include:


	- Configuring the Above-Store solution (ServerEPS)
	- Install and configure the In-Store solution (APS)
	- Troubleshoot the NCR Payment Gateway solution
${CTAText2} › &lt;[[${CTAURL}?${url-parameter}]]&gt;
Improved Speed and Efficiency for Aloha Online Ordering Requests
To streamline the Aloha Online Ordering requests, we created website links to use going forward when submitting requests for Aloha Online Ordering. These external links may be sent to customers.



	- Prescreen Request &lt;[[https://ncr.quickbase.com/db/bqh2kczjb?a=nwr]]&gt;
	- Aloha Online Ordering Customer Questionnaire &lt;[[https://ncr.quickbase.com/db/bqh88nhyh?a=nwr]]&gt;
	- External Enrollment Request &lt;[[https://ncr.quickbase.com/db/bqh86sqp2?a=nwr]]&gt;: For external builds, our team receives this request from Channel Partner’s/Local Offices to 
begin the project.
	- Remove from Demo Mode &lt;[[https://ncr.quickbase.com/db/bqh87fzv3?a=nwr]]&gt;: For external builds, our team receives this request from Channel Partner’s/Local Offices as the 
testing phase step or the final step to go live.
New Automatic Updates for CFC


Great news! NCR is introducing an exciting enhancement to provide automatic updates to the NCR Configuration Center (CFC) software with new system capabilities and fixes. Customers using CFC version 19.12 or higher will receive the first automatic update to version 20.4 during the normal maintenance window on Wednesday, May 27, 2020 between 3:00 a.m. – 7:00 a.m. CT. Please advise customers there may be a brief interruption in service for less than five minutes during the upgrade.
eWeekly Newsletter Survey

Your opinion matters! Please take a few moments to respond to an anonymous survey about the effectiveness of the information included in the NCR eWeekly newsletter. This survey should take less than five minutes of your time. We thank you in advance for your response by June 5th, 2020. 
Take survey  &lt;[[https://email.ncr.com/HB002000A0Q0OY0000Q00ux]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
