<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>04-02-23 T&amp;T CX Customer Letter.EN Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>We want to hear from you</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear {{lead.First Name:default=Customer}},
 
Our top priority is serving you and helping you meet your goals. So we feel very connected to your business and personal success and always feel privileged to be your strategic partner.

We’re committed to driving improvements throughout our business to give you a better total experience. Your account manager will be sharing important updates with a personalized summary of the key actions we’ve taken to help you win in the marketplace.

We continue to drive improvements across the business during this challenging environment by:


	- 
Enhancing our strategic account planning approach aimed at building a tighter roadmap together.

	- 
Expanding our end-to-end services capabilities and a new remote monitoring platform to provide greater flexibility, agility and automation.

	- 
Investing in a new pricing platform to improve response times, a key area of focus in 2023 – more to come.



Beginning on Monday, April 3, we’ll start sending customers our 2023 relationship survey. It only takes three minutes to complete and focuses on several ways to strengthen our strategic relationship. We encourage you to provide any written comments to ensure we understand the context of your total experience working with NCR. We depend on your candid feedback and experiences to guide our priorities and investments. We are also motivated by your positive experiences. It’s the best way we know to keep delivering value to your business.

Thank you for your business, your partnership and your feedback in our annual relationship survey. 

Sincerely, 
 
Sophia Williams
SVP and General Manager 
NCR Telecom and Technology
&lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
