<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>12-09-22 HOS McDonald&apos;s Digital Menu Board Non-Customer Comm 2.HOS McDonald&apos;s Di</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Learn More About NCR’s Digital Menu Board Offerings</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear Valued Customer,

Welcome to NCR!

We are pleased to be your new Digital Menu Board hardware, hardware installation and Break Fix provider, beginning on January 1, 2023. Keep reading to learn:



	- What&apos;s new!
	- About NCR &amp; the team
	- DMB program Offerings (Installations and Break-Fix)
	- Your action items
	- How to contact us




What&apos;s new?

NCR will be your new Digital Menu Board hardware, hardware installation and Break Fix provider, beginning on January 1, 2023. This program is inclusive of supporting:



	- Indoor Digital Menu Boards installations
	- Break Fix options for:


	- Outdoor Digital Menu boards
	- Indoor Digital Menu Boards




The relationship between NCR and McDonald’s is longstanding and we are excited to partner with McDonald’s to provide these service offerings to accommodate your restaurant’s needs.



About NCR and McDonald’s

Sales and Services are people driven, which is why we are proud to say we have the industry’s best! With a team of over 20,000 professionals across 180 countries, and 3,000 remote specialists, only NCR has the power and scale to provide all the support you need. At NCR, we have experienced professionals that are 100% dedicated to McDonald’s. This includes our Account Executives, Customer Care team, Regional Break-Fix Support team and Installation and Project team leads. These teams understand both the technology and the McDonald’s industry. In addition to support from these teams, we also have tools and resources to help operators manage their business more efficiently.

By becoming a DMB customer with NCR you get:



	- MyNCR-Consumer Portal
To help operators manage their business more efficiently, NCR partnered with McDonald’s to develop a customized ecommerce portal. MyNCR allows customers to transact with NCR anytime, anyplace.

MyNCR capabilities include:





	- Online ordering
	- Hardware tracking information
	- View, Download and Print Invoice and Order Details
	- Electronically Dispute Invoices
	- Access Business Relevant NCR Applications in a
	- Self-Management of Application Users







	- Your NCR McDonald’s Account Team
NCR DMB Program Offerings

To learn about all NCR Digital Menu Board program offerings, please click here &lt;[[https://go.ncr.com/rs/605-BQY-740/images/111622_IntegratedMktg_HOSP_McDonalds_programofferings_non-customer_v1.pdf]]&gt;.



Your Action Steps:

Beginning on November 1, 2022, you can add 2023 coverage for your Digital Menu Boards when placing your new store, rebuild, or refresh order.



How to Contact UsPlease contact our dedicated Customer Care Team by calling (800) 421-8230 between 8am – 8pm ET or via email at 
McDonalds.Orders@ncr.com. 



Sincerely,
Your McDonald’s NCR Account Team
&lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
