<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>10-dd-22 HOS McDonald&apos;s Digital Menu Board Comm.Email 1</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>NCR is now your Digital Menu Board provider</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear Valued Customer,

Beginning January 1, 2023, NCR will be your new Digital Menu Board hardware, hardware installation, and Break Fix provider. This is inclusive of supporting Outdoor Digital Menu Boards, Indoor Digital Menu Boards and Free-Standing Digital Merchandizers along with Break Fix options. We are pleased to partner with McDonald’s to provide these service offerings.


NCR Program Offerings



	- New restaurants
	- Relocations
	- Rebuilds
	- Refreshes
	- SAO + 10 year
	- Outdoor Digital Menu Boards (ODMB) (Break Fix support only)
	- Indoor Digital Menu Boards (IDMB)


	- When speaking with your NCR Account Executive (AE) about your upcoming installation activity with your technology order, IDMB hardware and installation services will be included in your quote; no need to manage multiple suppliers for your IDMB installation.
	- For sites not purchasing other technology from NCR, the NCR AE will be reaching out to you for your IDMB quote for your upcoming installation activity.
	- Orders for installation projects should be placed a minimum of 90 days prior to the opening of your restaurant. This will ensure that all orders are actioned, installations are scheduled, and confirmation is sent to meet the opening date of the restaurant.






Experience of the Future (EOTF) and Outdoor Digital Menu Boards (ODMB)

These processes remain the same. You will need to continue to work with your preferred integrator to order and install IDMB for your EOTF projects, and you will continue to work with the construction team for your ODMB solution.


Protect your investment 

While there is not a requirement for Digital Menu Boards to be covered through a maintenance agreement, it is beneficial to cover your investment through a Break Fix contract. Coverage for your indoor, outdoor Digital Menu Boards and Digital Merchandisers will protect your investment throughout the lifecycle of the hardware.
Time and Materials

While we strongly encourage you to choose a Break Fix option to protect your investment, you may opt to be billed on a Time and Materials basis. Costs for this option are outlined below. Please be advised that with this solution, a new media player or screen will also need to be purchased. This service is for the replacement of one piece of hardware per visit. Multiple pieces of hardware not working will be moved to an installation service price model.

Note: All pricing excludes taxes and shipping costs


Next steps beginning November 1, 2022

Beginning on November 1, 2022, you can add 2023 coverage for your Digital Menu Boards. Please contact your NCR Account Executive or the dedicated Customer Care Team by calling (800) 421-8230 between 8am – 8pm ET or via email at McDonalds.Orders@ncr.com to:



	- Place your new installation activity orders for:


	- New restaurant relocations
	- Rebuilds
	- Refresh
	- SAO + 10 year


	- Add Break Fix services for 2023:


	- NCR Current Break Fix Customers: Add DMB to any existing NCR Break Fix contract
	- New NCR Break Fix DMB Customers: Create a new Break Fix contract with NCR
Sincerely,
Your NCR Account Team
&lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
