<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>02-04-21 HOS eWeekly Get the Latest Aloha Status Updates.02-04-21 HOS eWeekly Ge</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>eWeekly – Get the Latest Aloha Status Updates</subject>
    <textOnly>February 4, 2021
Get the Latest Aloha Status Updates
All channel partners should encourage your customers to sign-up today for access to the Aloha Status Page for immediate access to information about the health and performance of our software, 24 x 7 x 365.

It’s so easy to subscribe &lt;[[https://status.aloha.ncr.com/]]&gt; and 
only takes a few minutes to set preferences and instantly start to receive automated updates, via text, email or RSS feed with information about:


	- 
Upcoming software changes and notifications

	- Current incident status information 
	- Previous solution incident reports
	- Maintenance reports


Check out the new Aloha Status Page &lt;[[https://status.aloha.ncr.com/]]&gt; today!
New and Improved NCR Customer Support
We’re excited that our new customer-centric teams for Aloha/Hosted support program successfully launched this week. Customers are already experiencing a difference. Please remember to share information with your customers about the improvements we’ve made to our Customer Support model and ensure they have the correct numbers to call for support. Read more. &lt;[[https://ncr.quickbase.com/up/bqe6gx23b/g/rcm/ek/va/Customer Support Comms Enterprise for Channel Newsletter 1-27-21.pdf]]&gt;
Webinar: The Loyalty Iceberg: Creating Human-Centered Experiences
We know how busy you are. In case you missed this informative webinar, we’ve got you covered. We recorded it, so you can watch it at your convenience, to learn everything it takes to create enduring customer relationships. We’ve compiled proven techniques you can master so your customers choose you over the competition again and again. Check out the recording: The Loyalty 
Iceberg: Creating Human-Centered Experiences &lt;[[https://urldefense.com/v3/__https:/msp6.bigmarker.com/links/-FKOjiiEi2X/N9pJfPvyi/vGIW4tok-7/ijpR5rkFO?redirect_to=https*3A*2F*2Fwww.bigmarker.com*2Fwinsight*2FThe-Loyalty-Iceberg-Creating-Human-Centered-Experiences*3Fbmid*3D82c032089f22__;JSUlJSUlJQ!!In4Qlw!_KX_-m0aNAmLKMXBys1lpcRk6e8gYklTeU04VcS4lFRL9XHJ_jxSX2IAHyAQb2kVL0s$]]&gt;.
Important Reminders:
- The Dallas Data Center will be decommissioned permanently for NCR Mobile Pay only on February 15, 2021. NCR Mobile Pay clients utilizing the Dallas (DFW05) Data Center have until February 8, 2021 to whitelist their NCR endpoints. Read more. &lt;[[https://ncr.quickbase.com/up/bqe6gx23b/g/rck/ek/va/Decommission of NCR Dallas Data Center for NCR Mobile Pay Only FINAL UPDATED 1-27-21.pdf]]&gt;
	- NCR will switch Gateway traffic to route through Apigee on February 23, 2021 between 1:00 and 4:00 AM ET. Clients using the NCR Business Services Platform (BSP) must take actions by February 19, 2021 to avoid any connectivity loss that may negatively impact their business. Read the announcement. &lt;[[https://ncr.quickbase.com/up/bqe6gx23b/g/rcg/ek/va/BSP Apigee Cutovere Comms Revised Date 1-28-21.docx]]&gt;
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
