<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Nashville Letter - David Wilkinson.Nashville E-mail 1</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>NCR Fulfillment Center Update</subject>
    <textOnly>Fulfillment Center Update
Dear {{lead.First Name:default=Valued Customer}},

As you know, NCR’s Nashville Fulfillment Center sustained heavy damage during the tornados that struck the area on March 3, 2020.

I am writing to let you know about several steps we are taking to quickly resume operations and meet the needs of our customers.

First, we have secured an alternate location in greater Nashville where we will move some of the fulfillment center’s key operations. We have already started to outfit the facility with our technology and bring our staging capabilities online.

Our Supply Chain team has increased our parts inventory on order, and NCR is in the process of transitioning our trained and knowledgeable fulfillment employees to alternate NCR centers in Texas and Georgia.

Additionally, we have implemented a retention program for our impacted employees in Nashville to take care of them and keep our trained and knowledgeable staff in place.

All of NCR appreciates your support at this time, and we are committed to working with you to minimize any delay in your orders or implementations. 

We will provide weekly updates to you over the next few weeks so you stay informed.

Thank you for your business and for your partnership.

Sincerely,
David Wilkinson
President &amp; GM of Global Retail
NCR Corporation
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
