<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>03-29-23 CP NAMER Banking Freight Rate Adjustment.03-29-23 CP NAMER Banking Frei</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Important Update: Freight Rate Adjustments for ATM Shipments</subject>
    <textOnly>Important Update: Freight Rate Adjustments for ATM 
Shipments
To our valued Channel Partners,
 
NCR is committed to being a reliable provider of high-quality products 
and services to help our shared customers run their businesses. Due to market and supply-chain dynamics, we conduct regular reviews of the costs involved in doing so and make requisite adjustments as appropriate.

As part of regular review of freight costs in the United States, NCR will be adjusting the default freight charges for all ATM classes, effective May 1, 2023 (detailed below). This follows a detailed, multi-faceted freight cost analysis of our ATM portfolio, resulting in freight charge increases and decreases dependent on ATM class. These changes will be reflected in NCR quoting systems on May 1, 2023.
ATM Freight Rates 
(effective 5/1/2023)




ATM Class


Price (Per Unit)




2012


$1,300




6623


$1,088




6625


$1,396




6627


$1,266




6628


$1,412




2062


$1,675




2063


$1,425




2064


$1,750




6681


$2,601




6682


$2,267




6684


$2,328




6687


$1,571




6688


$2,572
We plan to continue reviewing our costs on a regular basis, and will re-evaluate pricing as the economic 
environment continues to change. Thank you for your continued partnership and collaboration through this process, and please reach out to your CAM with any questions. 

Best regards,
NCR Global Channel Program Team
&lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
