<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>GM CSAT Notes.Retail EN.EN Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>We Are Acting On Your Feedback</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear {{lead.First Name:default=Valued Customer}},

At NCR, we are committed to making simple possible for our customers. Your feedback helps us learn how we can make your life easier by making it simpler to work with us and advancing the solutions we offer.

So far, 2020 has been anything but normal, but we want you to know that we haven’t lost sight of your feedback and made improvements in our Retail business units in the areas that you said were important.




	- Enhancing our software quality and software support. In response, we are changing our agile processes to help improve how we develop and deliver our software. These enhancements include full end-to-end automation for not only our products, but the entire solution along with Behavior Driven Development tests, consistent practices for code reviews and greater sprint governance. Furthermore, we continue to focus on incident reduction and problem management in our software support to enable higher levels of availability.




	- Enhance our services reliability and availability. In 2019, we introduced a structured program that better identifies opportunities to resolve tickets and started soliciting customer feedback on field engineer activity on ticket closure. This real-time feedback helps us drive continuous improvement of our services and I hope you are seeing the first effects. We continue these efforts to improve our service quality.




	- Streamlining our invoicing process. We have started introducing a Services pre-bill functionality within MyNCR for more accuracy of maintenance bills. Furthermore, we are investing in business process management tools that will improve the timeliness of services invoicing. Finally, we’re creating an end-to-end Digital Invoicing process designed to ensure your invoice matches your purchase order or contract, incorporating electronic portals, invoice delivery, and payment options. Our goal is to make invoicing simple.


Your feedback helps us learn how we can make your life easier by making it simpler to work with us and advancing the solutions we offer – like the changes to our support functions to establish an end-to-end view to your success and the innovations around our Next-Generation Retail Store Architecture Platform that we will be able to share soon. 

We look forward to hearing more of your feedback from our 2020 Customer Satisfaction survey, which will be launching later this year. Thank you for being an NCR customer and for sharing your valuable insights with us.

Warmest regards,

David Wilkinson 
President and General Manager, NCR Retail
 
 Eric Schoch
SVP, NCR Retail Sales</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
