<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>NCR Aloha SMB Customer Newsletter.06-23-21 HOS Newsletter Aloha SMB Customer.Ema</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Attract and Retain Great Employees</subject>
    <textOnly>#What&apos;sNew@NCR
Attract and Retain Great Employees
The No. 1 reason former restaurant employees aren’t returning to work? Fear of getting sick, which is no surprise given the importance of their health and safety. With the labor shortage now at an all-time high, how do you attract and retain qualified talent? These six recommendations &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/blogs/restaurants/6-ways-find-restaurant-employees]]&gt; can boost your recruiting strategy.
Run Your Business from Anywhere
Seeing is believing. Case in point: watching this video of NCR Pulse Real-Time Capabilities &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lDEvpQfny00]]&gt; shows how easily you can run your business from anywhere.
Once you’re up and running on Pulse Real-Time, get up-to-the-minute sales information, mobile cloud reporting, alerts, and analytic tools. Even better, open an incident right in the app and attach photos, screenshots, and documents. Contact your NCR Account Executive today to sign up for Pulse Real-Time.
Are Your Payments Fees Increasing?
Over the next few months, some payment processors will increase fees for non-EMV processed transactions. Keep an eye on your statements for potential rate increases and let us help. NCR can review your restaurant’s current payments statements for potential savings.
Staffing Correctly for Online Order Volume
Surging online orders for restaurants present new staffing challenges for operators. While your employees already go above and beyond, you also need a plan in place and the right tools so your operations run smoothly to keep pace with increased demand.
Latest Updates
Tip of the Day: Reboot Aloha for Optimal Performance
Programs that use Microsoft Windows will eat up RAM and slow down your hardware if left running for an extended period of time, causing programs to hang up and terminals to 
freeze.

Avoid this by rebooting Aloha POS terminals, Aloha Kitchen screens, and Fileservers once a week. You’ll optimize performance and minimize impacts to your business. Simply press the Power button to restart the units. After about 10 - 15 minutes, the reboot will complete, and you’ll be good to go.
Knowledge is Power
Keep your business running smoothly with access to all the information you need at your fingertips. Subscribing to the Aloha Status Page &lt;[[https://email.ncr.com/NjA1LUJRWS03NDAAAAF9hJ3-Ii7YyJBh5FdW-e9UAb4bFRq9Az_qRnSoA-EIh1J3YVNik86ms8TTC_WrALfZy3_gv4w=]]&gt; keeps you informed about Aloha via text, email, or RSS feed status. Receiving these alerts saves you time instead of calling Customer Support. Plus, access all the information you need, when you need it.
Discontinued Hospitality Customer Support Numbers
As of June 1, 2021, you must now use your assigned regional NCR Customer Support phone numbers &lt;[[https://ncr.quickbase.com/up/bqe6gx23b/g/rdj/ek/va/Customer Support Phone Numbers 6-4-21.pdf]]&gt; when calling Support for help with Aloha and Silver. Please discard any old Customer Support phone numbers you used previously, as they will no longer work.
The Primer for restaurants—see what’s cooking in your industry
- How central kitchens improve your guest 
experience &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/blogs/restaurants/central-kitchen-guest-experience]]&gt;
	- Steps to transform your dine-in and outdoor 
experience &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/blogs/restaurants/transforming-dine-in-experience]]&gt;
	- Ways to generate a new revenue stream for your 
restaurant &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/blogs/restaurants/generate-new-revenue-streams]]&gt;
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
