<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>08-31-21 RET Emerald Newsletter.Email 1</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>NCR Emerald Community Newsletter – August 2021</subject>
    <textOnly>August 2021
Dear Emerald Community Members,
 
Now with summer winding down and kids going back to school, the Emerald solution team is doubling down on implementations and roadmap execution.
EMERALD COMMUNITY MEETINGS
SAVE THE DATE!  Our next virtual Emerald Community meeting will be on Wednesday October 6, 2021 from 1-3 PM Eastern. Teams invitation and agenda forthcoming from Jeanne Bosworth. We are pleased to welcome our newest Community and Advisory Board members from Stater Bros., WinCo and Federated Coop.
NEW EMERALD ADVISORY BOARD MEMBERS
Manikandan Subramanian
Director, IT Applications
Mark Ennis
 Director, Retail Solutions
Mark Helms
Director, Retail Technology
RETAILER HIGHLIGHTS
Bashas’ – NCR Emerald and SCO are now live in 2 stores with rollout soon. They selected NCR Freshop as their eCommerce platform.
BevMo! – First store pilot going live with NCR Emerald and NCR Freshop in August. This extends the Emerald POS solution into the liquor and specialty beverage market. 
Stater Bros – Moved to Connected Payments on Common cloud and completed AMS upgrade to NCR Cloud. First store pilot going live in September 2021.
Northgate Market – Successfully running Emerald in all of their 42 stores since May 2021, and in June, one of their new stores went live with self-checkout.
SpartanNash/Martin’s – Live with Emerald, self-checkout 
and pharmacy and fuel POS. They are actively rolling out to 21 more Martin’s stores.
EMERALD RELEASE HIGHLIGHTS
Here are a few highlights from our latest release, Emerald 1.6.2.  You can find more info on the  NCR public documentation portal that allows our Emerald customers to see the summary of latest releases. You can access the Emerald POS content from the home page https://docs.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://docs.ncr.com/]]&gt;. Here is a direct link to the Emerald POS overview page &lt;[[https://docs.ncr.com/retail/emerald-pos/overview/]]&gt; and the Release Notes &lt;[[https://docs.ncr.com/retail/emerald-pos/about/release-notes/version_1_6_2/]]&gt; are under &quot;about.&quot;
REF 412039: Loyalty and Promotions - The existing Coupon Type BRM was renamed to Unused Coupon BRM Type and was enhanced to act on an unused coupon. Any retailer using the previous ‘Coupon’ BRM should remove it and adjust their functionality to the new ‘Unused Coupon’ BRM. Unused coupons are displayed back to the cashier.
REF 477862: Total Savings on Receipt / Total Section on Receipt - The Receipt was updated with a new 
ability to display the Total Savings on the receipt (the sum of all rewards (discount or tender).

REF 502897: Tender: Do Not Block Paying Non-FSA Items with FSA Card - The FSA card industry started producing payment cards, which can also be used to pay for regular items, and not only FSA items.

REF 434032: Tender – Enhance 
Verification for 3rd Party Barcode Vouchers such as Coinstar, Bottle Deposit - Emerald handles barcode vouchers such as Bottle Deposit vouchers or CoinStar vouchers as tenders.
REF 411089: Fuel RIG Prepay - Cash Change to Fuel Prepay (Rest in Gas) - The Emerald FuelPOS was updated to support a feature called ‘Rest In Gas’ (RIG). This is a transaction in which the customer purchases an item/s, pays a fixed amount and the system assigns the change amount to a fuel prepay item, i.e., the RIG.
NCR TEAM MEMBER HIGHLIGHTS
At the recommendation of our Advisory Board, we will recognize team members from both NCR and clients who have done outstanding work on the Emerald solution, pilots and rollouts.
Yaniv Terliuc is Software Product Manager and part of the NCR Emerald Product team from the beginning. He has been instrumental in delivering Emerald Fuel and getting us to our first live sites this summer. This included getting us NTEP certified and driving a solution across the Emerald, Fuel and Loyalty product teams. Yaniv maintains a positive attitude, even when facing difficult issues to solve. Thank you for all your hard work!
Yair Reznik is a Solution Architect in the Emerald Center of Excellence for professional services. Yair has 19 years of Retail Software and Professional Services experience and has been a key player with multiple generations of NCR POS software solutions. During his career Yair has worked with a significant number of NCR customers in his previous positions as an ISS45 and StoreLine Engineering Manager. Yair stepped into the role of Emerald PS Solution Architect, leading Technical and Architecture Activities on SpartanNash and RBS projects, including POS, SCO, Pharmacy and Fuel. He is always ready to help to customers and colleagues. We appreciate you!
NCR FRESHOP UPDATE
Since we acquired the eCommerce solution &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/news/newsroom/news-releases/company/ncr-adds-freshop-e-commerce-solution-to-retails-leading-enterprise-pos-software-platform?mkt_tok=NjA1LUJRWS03NDAAAAF-boeKocIK0M9Gl_F39QR1DwhiUtBfnoyCNZaf3Sk-siQuXrYvB2DpP3s1g9vkcg2dvxsiMeAIJAvZhx7zPQ]]&gt; in January, we’ve been rapidly scaling NCR Freshop solution to be an even bigger force in the retail market. Emerald customers BevMo!, Northgate and Bashas’ are now part of the NCR Freshop family.
The NCR Freshop team is excited to also be participating in one of the first live shows since COVID-19 struck: NGA in Las Vegas. There, we’ll host the first NCR Freshop Community Meeting since our partnership was announced.
THANK YOU!
 
The NCR Emerald Team
We currently have these Emerald customers in our Community, representing a diverse and growing cross-section of the U.S. and Canadian grocery segment.
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
