<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>05-09-22 RET EuroCIS 2022 English Email 4.Email 4</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>EuroCIS 2022: Store tech that runs itself AND helps you decide?</subject>
    <textOnly>There are too many touchpoints and too many customer interactions to risk a piece of software or hardware malfunctioning and potentially disrupting your customers. 

Did you know our Digital Connected Services can monitor, maintain and manage your store technology remotely? This makes sure you’re always on, always available. And if there’s a problem? We can spot and fix it before it becomes a problem.

There’s also a goldmine of data running between your connected devices and customers. We can help you use it to find opportunities and make better decisions to grow your business, and so much more.

Visit NCR at Stand 10/A04 and discover how to connect, automate and visualise your retail operation with NCR Digital Connected Services.

You can also explore our latest advancements that help you run your store end to end, simplify your operations and deliver the 
best experiences that differentiate your brand.

If you haven’t yet scheduled a one-on-one consultation &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/retail/eurocis-2022]]&gt; with the NCR team at EuroCIS, we hope you’ll take a moment to do so now. We’re looking forward to seeing you!

 &lt;[[https://www.eurocis-tradefair.com/]]&gt;

Learn more about NCR at EuroCIS. &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/retail/eurocis-2022]]&gt;Schedule a meeting with us at EuroCIS. &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/retail/eurocis-2022]]&gt;Read about what we’re doing with 
leading grocery, mass merchandise, convenience, and specialty brands worldwide. &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/green-room]]&gt;
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
