<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>05-05-21 HOS CMC Migration to Azure Wave 1 Comm 2.Email 2</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Important Announcement</subject>
    <textOnly>Decommission of Command Center in the NCR Dallas Data Center
Dear Valued NCR Customer: 
 
Previously, NCR notified you of plans to migrate Command Center from our on-premises data center to Azure Cloud platform. This is to notify you that your sites have been identified for migration to Azure. This migration will include both a CMCAgent version upgrade and migration to our Command Center environment in Azure public cloud.
 
ACTION REQUIRED:

You must ensure that you whitelist the NCR endpoints to prepare for the migration, or you will be at risk of losing access to your licensed NCR products that are being migrated to Microsoft 
Azure Public Cloud. See the full list of NUA01 Public Endpoints per Application. &lt;[[https://ncr.quickbase.com/up/bqe6gx23b/g/rc9/ek/va/Command Center Firewall New Azure NUA01-SEC Requirements Updated 4-12-21.pdf]]&gt;

To access your migrated sites, you will need to download the Command Center client using this link and instructions &lt;[[https://ncr.quickbase.com/up/bqe6gx23b/g/rc9/ek/va/Command Center Firewall New Azure NUA01-SEC Requirements Updated 4-12-21.pdf]]&gt; provided.

TIMING:
Migration window: May 11-21, 2021

WHAT TO EXPECT:

NCR has already deployed the 
CMCreqcheck.exe software to test and confirm that your site(s) can access the new endpoint. Sites identified for migration will have their CMCAgent upgraded prior to the targeted window noted above. 



	- If you have already upgraded your sites to CMCAgent 19.2.5 or higher, no additional action will be needed


Thank you for your continued cooperation in ensuring that you have whitelisted the NCR endpoints in advance to avoid any risk of losing access to your licensed NCR products once they are migrated to the Microsoft Azure Public Cloud. Please contact NCR Customer Support if you have any questions or experience any issues, so we can assist you as quickly as possible.
 
We appreciate your partnership with NCR.
 
Thank you, 
NCR Hosted Services Team
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
