<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>6-28-21 RET Monltly Emerald Newsletter June 2021.6-28-21 RET Monthly Emerald New</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>NCR Emerald Community Newsletter – June 2021</subject>
    <textOnly>June 2021
Greetings Emerald Community Members,
 
It’s hard to believe that our first half of 2021 is nearly complete! So much has changed in such a short time, in the world, and at NCR. The Emerald solution continues to evolve with these changes and we are excited about what’s in store!
EMERALD COMMUNITY MEETINGS
We will announce the date/time/location of our Q3 Emerald Community meeting soon!
 
Successful April Emerald Community meeting – We held our second Emerald Community meeting in April with approximately 70 participants from ten companies (Meijer, WinCo, Bashas’, BevMo!, Northgate, Federated Coop, Stater Bros., SpartanNash, Big-Y and NCR) in virtual attendance. Topics included Loyalty Roadmap and hearing from retailers Northgate, Meijer and Big-Y about their self-service and eCommerce initiatives. Thank you to those who took the time to fill-out the survey – we received 91% positive, 9% neutral and 0% negative responses. Also we received some excellent suggestions for future meeting topics, including:



	- Retailer presentations were a huge hit
	- Lessons Emerald customers learned during rollouts so others can, too
	- More in-depth functionality of upcoming releases
EMERALD RELEASES AND ROADMAP
We are excited to announce that we now have a public documentation portal that allows our Emerald customers to see the summary of the latest release Emerald 1.6.1. You can access the Emerald POS content from the home page https://docs.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://docs.ncr.com/]]&gt;. Here is a direct link to the Emerald POS overview page &lt;[[https://docs.ncr.com/retail/emerald-pos/overview/]]&gt; and the Release Notes &lt;[[https://docs.ncr.com/retail/emerald-pos/about/release-notes/version_1_6_1/]]&gt; are under &quot;about.&quot;
REF 495522|496709: Deployment of TDM Parser 2.16/2.17
REF 464372: Security - Ability for Single Credentials Cross all Offices
REF 493545: Certification of Windows Server 2019 for CCM Servers and Store Servers
REF 391803: Tax: Canadian Tax – PST, GST, HST, First Nations, Donut Deal, Prepared Food
REF 437387: Capture Pickup Person Identification for Controlled Drugs
REF 457079: Pharmacy: Return an Rx Drug Item - Complete NRR
REF 493369: Fuel - Verify Emerald Fuel Promotions/Loyalty with LPE Phase 1
At the recommendation of our Advisory Board, we will recognize team members from both NCR and clients who have done outstanding work on the Emerald solution, pilots and rollouts.
Anita Walls is a Professional Services Sr. Partner and a leading manager in the Emerald Center of Excellence. Anita has 30 years of Retail Systems Transformation experience and has been a key player with multiple POS solutions, technologies, markets, and retailers – she truly has “seen it all”.

Most recently, Anita has stepped in to lead the SpartanNash Emerald Charter program, driving the project to POS, SCO, Fuel and Pharmacy pilots. Her value is perfectly represented by the fact that SpartanNash has moved from “red” to a Net Promoter Score of NINE! Amazing!
Matt Heeter is the Emerald Lead Technical SME. Today, he plays a key role in the implementation of multiple projects, including Bashas, SpartanNash, BevMo, Northgate Market and Big Y. Matt has been with NCR for almost 18 years and his background is in Retail Software. Prior to Emerald, he worked as a Lead Technical Specialist on the StoreLine PS team.

Matt possesses a great, unique mix of technical skills and knowledge of customer business functionality; his customer service is always exceptional.
Mike Hendry
Executive Vice President Merchandising &amp; Marketing, Northgate Gonzalez Market
In his role as EVP of Northgate Gonzalez Market, Mike is responsible for the company’s Sales, Merchandising, Marketing and Advertising 
functions for this premier Hispanic-focused retailer. Mike has served his entire career in the grocery industry including 17 years with Vons and Safeway serving as the lead architect of their loyalty strategies as well as serving 10 years with Catalina Marketing as President of their Direct Marketing Services Division. Prior to Northgate, Mike served as the Vice President of Retail Banner Marketing at SUPERVALU where he was responsible for the Marketing and Advertising functions at ten U.S. retail divisions. Mike is a graduate of the USC Food Industry Management Program and holds a B.A. in psychology from Cal State University San Bernardino.
CUSTOMER SUCCESS STORY
One of the themes we keep returning to is how we can help retailers run their store operations more effectively and cost efficiently – from front-end to back office. NCR Emerald leverages the Retail Platform and API-first business services to connect all your touchpoints with core capabilities, reporting and analytics. One example of this is the seamless omni-channel experience now available with Northgate Market Pronto &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/green-room/northgate-market-ecommerce]]&gt;!
 
Northgate was one of our first NCR Emerald customers, moving from legacy NCR to our cloud-enabled POS platform in a record 6 
months for their fifirst pilot store. They recently added NCR eCommerce powered by Freshop that allows their customers to make online orders for safe curbside pickup – without the extra costs.
PROGRESSIVE GROCER WEBINAR
Webinar Title: Four Ways Northgate Uses eCommerce to Transform Customer Experience and Gain Consumer Insights­­

Summary:  Hear how Northgate Markets has grown their online sales with a customer repeat of over 50% and an order fill rate over 90% after partnering with NCR.
THANK YOU!
 
The NCR Emerald Team
We currently have these Emerald customers in our Community, representing a diverse and growing cross-section of the U.S. and Canadian grocery segment.
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
