<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>NCR Freshop Newsletters.11-03-21 NCR Freshop Newsletter November 21.Newsletter</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>NCR Freshop Newsletter- November 2021</subject>
    <textOnly>November 2021
Holiday Best Practices
We are thrilled to share with you some new NCR Freshop product updates as well as some tips and tricks to help you get through the busy Holiday season.

We also have some exciting news to share! We will be hosting our first ever NCR Freshop Customer Webinar &lt;[[https://ncr.webex.com/ncr/onstage/g.php?MTID=e7b47884476320ab1b05b3d8f7e2a2fcd]]&gt;, so don’t forget to read to the end of this newsletter for all of the details, including the registration link!
NCR Freshop Product Updates
Admin has a new look!
We are happy to announce that Freshop Admin has an improved, more user-friendly design. It includes everything you were familiar with in the Classic Admin with a refreshed feel.
Manage your own users
The Freshop Admin has the ability for retailers to manage (add/edit) their store&apos;s admin user account information. Learn about Admin User Roles &lt;[[https://support.freshop.com/portal/en/kb/articles/freshop-admin-user-roles-guide-16-8-2018]]&gt; and how to Create/Edit Admin Users in Freshop Admin &lt;[[https://support.freshop.com/portal/en/kb/articles/create-edit-users-in-freshop-admin]]&gt;.
How to maximize Holiday Merchandising &lt;[[https://support.freshop.com/portal/en/kb/articles/holiday-merchandising]]&gt;
Maximize the potential of your NCR/Freshop sites for the holidays. You can create holiday departments and add holiday search terms that will guide customers to the products they want to shop for. You can change the appearance of your site to feature holiday products and place your holiday items all together so they’re accessed with one click.
Adjusting for the Holidays
With the holidays near, you may want to manage slots for the holidays &lt;[[https://support.freshop.com/portal/en/kb/articles/holiday-slot-management]]&gt; that show during checkout. You can shut off slots for an entire day, reduce or increase the number of slots available in a day so you can manage the demand in online orders through the season.
Team Spotlight
NCR Freshop Development Team
We are excited to announce that we are hiring 27 net-new developers, 21 of which have recently been onboarded, to our Development Team. We are dedicated to expanding our Dev. Team to help continue to improve our product, efficiently resolve bugs, and create an easy onboarding process for all new customers.
Customer Story Highlight
ALLEGIANCE RETAIL SERVICES
Allegiance Retail Services, a retailer owned co-op that makes it easier for independent retailers to offer competitive prices, was Freshop’s very first customer and now has 86 member stores on the NCR Freshop platform.

Before switching to Freshop, Allegiance was frustrated that their current eCommerce solution didn’t offer the level of customization and personalized 
service they needed. They wanted a system that let them showcase nutritional information (a priority for many of their customers), digital recipes, shoppable recipes and more—within their budget. 

Freshop&apos;s design and data teams worked closely with Allegiance team members for a smooth implementation of Freshop. Allegiance consistently experienced double digit growth 5+ years running with the help of Freshop. And the co-op company grew more than 500 percent during the COVID surge, demonstrating what a powerful ROI investment they truly made. 

Read the full story here &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/green-room/allegiance-retail-services]]&gt;.
NCR Freshop Customer Webinar: November 10th @ 2 p.m. EST
We are excited to announce that we will be hosting our first, but certainly not last, NCR Freshop Customer Webinar! You can look forward to hearing about adding and editing slots, editing store info and hours, and Holiday merchandising best practices. You won&apos;t want to miss it!



	- Date: Wednesday, November 10th, 2021
	- Time: 2:00 - 2:30 p.m. EST
	- RSVP Here! &lt;[[https://ncr.webex.com/ncr/onstage/g.php?MTID=e7b47884476320ab1b05b3d8f7e2a2fcd]]&gt;


Our intent going forward is to continue sending you these newsletters and hosting webinars in 2022 to keep you updated on everything NCR Freshop-related. We look forward to connecting with you!
NCR Freshop Team
Freshop Support  &lt;[[https://support.freshop.com/portal/en/signin]]&gt;
Freshop Knowledge Base &lt;[[https://support.freshop.com/portal/en/signin#kb]]&gt;
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
