<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>01-06-22 RET NRF 2022 Email 4.Email 4</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>NRF 2022: Store hi-tech that runs itself</subject>
    <textOnly>Simple, made possible.
Remove inefficiencies so your stores can really grow
 NRF 2022 | New York | 16-18 January 2022 | NCR Booth 4819
What simple made possible really means? NCR removes the costs and distractions caused by in-store IT problems by providing managed services that keep applications available, current, secure, and high-performing.

 The 
associates in your store need to stay focused on their customers, and any time a point-of-sale terminal or software application misbehaves, they lose that focus. NCR lets you run the store the way it needs to be ran – with a focus on shoppers, not technology. All the solutions that shoppers and associates need – point of sale, self-checkout, back-office systems – connect to NCR’s Digital Connected Services, which combines cloud-based monitoring and management tools with expert service desks.
 
 This combination means that automated tools can identify when something is going wrong, guiding service professionals to resolve 
many issues quickly and remotely before they even create in-store outages; and, if something does go down, those same tools can provide the history and details to technicians that allow them to make the right fixes in the right places.

 Visit NCR at Booth 4819 at NRF to discover how NCR can make you life easier by hi-technology that runs your 
store.

 &lt;[[https://nrfbigshow.nrf.com/]]&gt;

Learn more about NCR at NRF &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/retail/nrf-2022]]&gt;

Schedule a meeting with us at NRF &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/retail/nrf-2022]]&gt;
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
