<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>GA Announcement.Email 1</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>To Our Georgia Customers</subject>
    <textOnly>To our valued NCR restaurant customers in Georgia: 

We know you have an important decision to make. NCR is here to help.  

With Governor Kemp announcing that restaurants can reopen for dining-in starting on Monday, April 27, ultimately, it’s your choice when you fully reopen your restaurant. We’ll support you whenever you decide to fully reopen. We can consult on any changes you want to make to your operations and ensure your technology is ready. 

As you make your plans, give us a call at 678-627-0401 and let us know how we can help, including:


	- If you need to change your floor plans
	- If your NCR Aloha technology was turned off while you were closed
	- If you were experiencing any issues with your technology prior to closing
	- And anything else you think we can help you with.



Our team would be happy to conduct a full Aloha health check to help you get ready to reopen. If there are any issues, we’ll work with you to resolve them. If you would like to get a start on checking your systems, you can:


	- Validate your internet is working on your back of house computer
	- Sign in to Aloha Manager
	- Sign in to every terminal
	- Print something on every printer



We also have additional resources available for you and your staff:


	- Free online Aloha training &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/restaurants/alohapos-training]]&gt; for your managers and staff
	- Hardware cleaning guidelines &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/coronavirus/cleaning-ncr-hardware]]&gt;
	- Smooth application process for the Payroll Protection Program &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/coronavirus/nymbus-smb-relief]]&gt;
	- Digital marketing recommendations and sample social media and email graphics &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/restaurants/marketingtoolkit]]&gt;
	- Access to additional articles &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/coronavirus/restaurants/3-ways-to-drive-revenue-and-engage-with-customers-while-diningroom-is-closed]]&gt; on contactless payments and delivery, takeout and curbside operations and more.



And we are here with you in Georgia, too. Atlanta is our hometown and in February, we acquired the Atlanta-based office of Retail Data Systems (RDS), one of NCR’s Aloha channel partners. The RDS employees join NCR’s team of 3000+ employees that not only work in Atlanta, but also have the privilege of being guests and raving fans of the metro Atlanta restaurant community. We look forward to being back in your establishment soon. 

Thank you for being our customer. Together we’ll #keepcommercerunning. The RDS-Atlanta office is now the NCR Local Office – Atlanta. Reach out to the same dedicated team that you are used to working with at 678-627-0401 if we can help in any way.



Sincerely,
Dirk Izzo
President, NCR Hospitality</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
