<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>2022 CSAT Results-Survey Notes.07-14-22 HOS CSAT Results-Survey Note EN.EN Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>We are acting on your feedback</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear {{lead.First Name:default=Valued Customer}},

Earlier this year, we conducted our 2022 NCR Customer Satisfaction Survey, with many of our customers participating and sharing their opinion with us. We have continued using that feedback as a foundation for how we learn, improve and make working with us simpler—all to keep our customers satisfied and grow together.

After analyzing the input we received through this survey, we saw that our customers recognized our efforts for improvement. However, we are aware there are still opportunities for further enhancements. That is why we are focusing on the following areas within the NCR Hospitality business unit:

Support


	- 
A top priority is continuous education and up-skilling our team with knowledge certification programs to improve their capabilities and shorten the time to incident resolution.





	- Increasing the use of artificial intelligence technology across our customer base allows us to identify some types of issues and take action to resolve those issues before our customers are impacted.




	- A significant investment in an industry-leading incident support platform. We are in the process of implementing and integrating this new platform within our infrastructure and with MyNCR. Some of the ways you will see a better support experience is:


	- Faster internal communication resulting in quicker resolutions
	- More streamlined dispatching to resolve issues
	- Better visibility to a list of your outstanding cases and reporting
	- &quot;Email to case&quot; functionality






	- First Call Resolution and Speed to Answer metrics continue to improve to help ensure your team is back to focusing on your customers as soon as possible.
Metric


Goal


Dec 2021


May 2022




First Call Resolution


70%


47.3%


61.3% ↑




Speed to Answer


90 sec


51 sec


42.5 sec ↓
Product and Roadmap


	- 
Executing our strategy to simplify our solutions, add new innovations and move more capabilities to the cloud.





	- Aloha v19.6 is now generally available and in use in more than 1,700 locations. This release includes solution integration testing with ~40 different products to certify that all components of our solution work together, improving the user experience. A new Aloha suite installer is also available on Aloha Update that includes the individual product versions that have been tested together as one full stack.




	- A new deployment platform scheduled for Q3 makes upgrading the Aloha store-site software easier and more reliable and enables you to orchestrate the upgrades on all devices at the site.




	- Aloha Cloud was launched with a reimagined user interface (UI) and user experience (UX), available handheld POS and more. Throughout the next 12 months, more new features and integration with the same common set of application programming interface (API) and services as Aloha uses today will be added.




	- In Q1, a new set of educational sessions to keep our customers up-to-date on our products and our roadmap called In the Know was enabled. You can register for upcoming sessions or access prior sessions on-demand at this site.


Billing

Over the past year, significant investments have been made to transform our invoicing accuracy and capabilities. It started with working with our customers to understand unique needs regarding invoice and billing functionality, identifying, securing and implementing the appropriate platform to deliver an experience that supports our customers, as well as reimagining our internal processes. Currently slated to begin rolling out in the coming months, our new billing experience will include:


	- 
Improved asset management capabilities to provide greater accuracy and faster invoicing, saving you time and reducing time required by your team.





	- Self-service invoice customization to enable each customer to view as little or as much detail as needed to support their own business processes. Additionally, this new platform will enable us to deliver invoices by PDF vs. “snail mail,” further driving efficiency.




	- Enhanced support for electronic data interchange (EDI) and transacting through eCommerce portals.




	- Easier to understand product descriptions and simplified, summary pages on invoices.


As always, thank you for being an NCR customer. We look forward to making further improvements and continuing to hear from you.

Warmest regards,

Dirk Izzo
President &amp; General Manager
NCR Hospitality
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
