<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Channel Newsletter 6.3.20.Newsletter 6.3.20</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>eWeekly: June 6</subject>
    <textOnly>June 4, 2020
Contactless Payments Now Available With Aloha
NCR Mobile Pay is a web-based payment solution that’s fully integrated with the Aloha POS. There’s no app to install—guests simply scan a QR code on their check or use their phone’s browser to navigate to ncrpay.com and enter the 6-digit code (ex: AZB678), pay and go. It’s a true contactless experience that puts the power of the payment solely in the hands of the restaurant’s guests. NCR Mobile Pay for table service restaurants using Aloha POS is now available in the U.S. 

Visit our Mobile Pay page &lt;[[https://ncr.seismic.com/Link/Content/DCZTl5EpNMo06NGApuAq0Pkg]]&gt; on Seismic page to access FAQs, hardware and software requirements, and other customer facing documentation.
Improved Freight Charges Transparency
We heard your feedback from across the channel partner community. We’re responding accordingly with important changes to help reduce freight costs and provide greater transparency into these costs. 
Beginning with orders placed on or after June 4, 2020, NCR will apply a ground shipping calculation for freight costs. This helps ensure you are charged the amount displayed when the order is placed. If NCR expedites a shipment, you will only be charged the ground shipping rate displayed when your order is placed. Any orders already in process will be processed according to the freight charges in effect when the order was placed. 
Additionally, in the future we will upgrade MyNCR with additional shipping options, clearly displaying the amount you will incur for your selection to help you manage these costs. We’ll keep you informed when the next upgrade becomes available.
Learn More About NCR Payments
There are only two more opportunities in June to participate in the technical training course for NCR Payment Gateway, the solution formerly known as NCR Connected Payments. Don’t miss this chance to learn about NCR Payment Gateway from our team of experts who have many years of experience facilitating training on this solution. You’ll also want to take advantage of the other upcoming training courses we developed specifically for our channel partners. Advanced registration in NCRU is required to reserve your spot.
${CTAText2} &lt;[[${CTAURL}?${url-parameter}]]&gt;
Your Opinion Matters
As you can see, we updated this newsletter with a fresh new design. We’re also revamping the content to include various topics that will help you deliver the best service to our customers. We want to hear from you about the information you’re most interested in seeing in future issues – training, tips and tricks, system updates, support, and more! Please take a few moments to respond to an anonymous survey and share your opinion about improvements you want to see in the NCR eWeekly Channel Partner newsletter. Thank you for submitting your response by June 5, 2020.

Take Survey &lt;[[https://email.ncr.com/HB002000A0Q0OY0000Q00ux]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
