<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>02-25-21 HOS eWeekly.Online Ordering is Getting a Whole Lot Cooler</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Online Ordering is Getting a Whole Lot Cooler</subject>
    <textOnly>February 25, 2021
Online Ordering is Getting a Whole Lot Cooler
Today, consumers want a user-friendly digital ordering experience. To meet this demand, NCR has a new best-in-class Digital Ordering solution with exciting features that we began moving our existing customers to on February 22, 2021.

Here are just some of the awesome new features in Digital Ordering to share with your customers:


	- 
Operators can customize the ordering experience by tailoring their brand’s colors and 
fonts in seconds.

	- Images galore lets operators feature their restaurant’s culinary creations front and 
center to get customers excited.
	- Brands can now deliver food without managing a fleet of drivers through our integration with 
Drive powered by DoorDash, while still owning the consumer and all orders flowing through Aloha.
	- The new Digital Ordering experience resizes to fit whatever device a consumer uses, providing 
a consistent experience across different devices.
Restaurants Pivot During Pandemic
According to Technomic’s 2020 Delivery and Takeout Consumer Trend Report, 66% of consumers anticipate continuing to use curbside pickup after dine-in services resume. This means operators should continue fine tuning and promoting curbside — keep at it with push notifications, direct mail advertisements, social media promotions and more to ensure their customers know off-premise services are still available. Restaurants can thrive by continuing to invest in the service that enabled many other restaurants to survive through the pandemic. Read more. &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/blogs/restaurants/restaurants-pivot-during-pandemic]]&gt;
Stay Current With Aloha Status Updates
The new Aloha Status Page &lt;[[https://status.aloha.ncr.com/]]&gt; provides exactly what customers need – convenient, user-friendly online access to information about the health and performance of our software. Best of all, it’s free and it’s easy to subscribe, so customers can begin receiving software status notifications via text, email, or RSS Feed. Encourage your customers to visit the Aloha Status Page  &lt;[[https://status.aloha.ncr.com/]]&gt;today to subscribe and setup their preferences.
More New Features for Contactless

We promised it was coming and now it’s here. We’ve added two new features to Aloha Mobile Pay to make a great experience even better.Aloha 
Stored Value Payment OptionGuests can now apply a restaurant’s branded Aloha Stored Value gift cards as a payment option in Mobile Pay – to 
pay the full bill, split it, or combine multiple gift cards.Text2PayNeed a way to easily and securely take payment for call-in orders? Now you can. Operators simply enter the guest’s phone number in Aloha and a text is sent to the guest’s phone with a link to pay their bill, saving time for both the operator and their guests.

Be sure to share this information with your customers!
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
