<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>SBA Statement Analysis.SBA Webinar Thank You.Thank You Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Restaurant Revitalization Fund Webinar Follow-Up Information</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear Valued Partner, 
 
 We would like to thank those customers who attended our webinar, Funding for Restaurants Affected by COVID-19, on April 29th. We hope you found the information about the Restaurant Revitalization Fund Program helpful and that it will simplify the application process for you. For those who were unable to attend the webinar, you can access the recording and view the PDF presentation here &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/blogs/sba-smb-relief]]&gt;.

As a reminder, you must register to submit your application for the Restaurant Revitalization funding at sba.gov &lt;[[https://www.sba.gov/funding-programs/loans/covid-19-relief-options/restaurant-revitalization-fund]]&gt; beginning on April 30, 2021 when the SBA opens registration. Funding is available on a first come, first served basis, so we encourage you to begin the application process as soon as possible.
NCR can help you access your statements showing 2020 vs. 2019 sales data upon your request as follows:



	- Silver users: Click here &lt;[[https://customercare.ncrsilver.com/community?searchQuery=Sales-Summary-Report&amp;subscriptionNumber=A-S00001316]]&gt; for instructions on how to access your data via Silver Back Office.
	- Aloha users: If you do not have Aloha Insight, you are able to pull your data from Aloha Manager and Configuration Center: 


	- Go to Reports &gt; Aloha Point of Sale &gt; Reports &gt; Sales &gt; Sales Summary
	- Highlight 1/1/2019 and 12/31/2019
	- Select Print
	- The report will consolidate all days as one total for 2019 revenue. Repeat the same process for a report on 2020 revenue by changing the dates to 1/1/2020 and 12/31/2020





If you have any questions, please visit the NCR American Rescue Plan Act site &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/blogs/sba-smb-relief]]&gt; that includes frequently asked questions about the Restaurant Revitalization Fund Program and additional resources.

Sincerely, 
 
 NCR Hospitality Team
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
