<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Vigilix Upsell Drip (Without Auto Pay).02 - Send Email 2.E-mail 2 (without auto</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>We will no longer offer Vigilix as a method of remote connectivity on June 30th</subject>
    <textOnly>Retail Data Systems is Moving Away From Vigilix After This Month
Save $250 and $30 a month if you sign up in 7 days!
Because you are a current 
Vigilix user, we are offering no set-up fee and only $20.00 monthly. Take advantage 
of this offer as it ends soon!

Your IT staff can feel confident switching to Secure Access to connect remotely to back office PCs that store and process card holder data—Secure Access meets PCI DSS requirements for multi-factor authentication for remote access. 
With Secure Access, you’ll provide a secure conduit for remote support and management via the internet. It uses multiple layers of security, encryption and 
authentication that eliminate the vulnerabilities that currently exist in traditional methods of remote support.
${CTAText3} &lt;[[${CTAURL}?${url-parameter}]]&gt;
${CTA2Text4} &lt;[[${CTA2URL}?${url-parameter}]]&gt;
PCI Data Security Standard (DSS) Level 4 Merchant Requirements: 



	- Quarterly external vulnerability scans
	- Annual self-assessment questionnaire
Due to these additional requirements, Secure Access alone cannot make you PCI compliant; it addresses only the network security requirements as they relate to remote access. The PCI DSS is a combination of physical, network and software standards. Please see the PCI Quick Reference Guide attachment below for more information.

Because NCR Atlanta Local Office/Formerly RDSSE is a software and hardware reseller, we can only ensure that vendor software and hardware is up to date and compliant with VISA’s various best practices requirements. Due to PCI DSS Standards, we are not authorized to use any remote connectivity software that does not meet the requirements of two factor authentication.
Questions?
After reading the attached documentation, and if you continue to need remote connectivity to your sites, please email the below order form directly to your Client Care Representative or e-mail Customer Care: veronica.lister@ncr.com

 &lt;[[https://email.ncr.com/txY02002B000900AQ00001y]]&gt;The cost of the product offerings is included here. You can purchase the remote access to your system. We are excited to offer this to you and look forward to assisting you with all your point of sale needs in the future!</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
