<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>2022 CSAT C2 Action Notes.01-09-23 P&amp;N CSAT C2 Action Note EN.EN Email p&amp;n</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>We are acting on your feedback</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear {{lead.First Name:default=Valued Customer}},
 
Late last year, we conducted our NCR Customer Satisfaction Survey 2022, with many of our customers participating and sharing their opinion with us. We continue to use that feedback as a foundation for how we learn, improve and make working with us simpler — all to keep our customers satisfied and grow together. 

After several weeks of analyzing the survey, I am excited to let you know we saw improvement in the overall survey results on a company level for the fourth consecutive year, particularly in our Net Promoter Score (NPS).

At the same time, we know there is always opportunity for improvement. Based on your feedback, we are focusing on the following areas within the NCR Payments &amp; Network business unit:


	- 
We are reviewing processes and updating training to improve response times to questions and concerns. 

	- 
We are improving process management to reduce the time needed for new equipment installations, updates and service delivery. 

	- 
We continue monitoring the payment processing platform performance to ensure stability, speed and scalability. 



As always, thank you for being an NCR customer. We look forward to making further improvements and continuing to hear from you.

Best regards,

Don Layden
President and General Manager
NCR Payments &amp; Network
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
