<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>09-29-22 T&amp;T Customer Survey Letter - Sophia Williams Wave 2.Email 1</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Your Feedback is Important to Us</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear {{lead.First Name:default=Valued Customer}}, 

Our highest priority as a strategic partner is to help you achieve your business goals and build enduring relationships. So we work hard every day to provide a high-quality service and deliver on your brand promise. We also recognize that continuous improvement is a vital part of our success. 

We want to earn your trust and confidence and make it easy to do business with us. Your feedback on our surveys makes this possible. Your account manager will share some of our general improvements and value stories that make our relationship strong.

Here are some highlights of those improvements that we have put into motion since our last survey:



	- 
Updated our strategic account planning approach aimed at building a tighter roadmap together

	- 
Expanded our end-to-end services capabilities and new remote monitoring platform to provide greater flexibility, agility, and automation

	- 
Updated Portfolio Priorities to Support Strategic Technologies and Your Business
Beginning October 3, you will receive a personal link to our 2022 relationship survey, which takes approximately three minutes to complete. It focuses on ways we can strengthen our strategic relationship and your ongoing NCR experiences. The survey is flexible, so you can skip questions that don’t apply to you. Additionally, we encourage and value written responses to help us understand the results and exceed expectations in the future.

Your feedback is the best tool we have for serving you better. Thank you for your business and allowing us to be your partner.

Sincerely,

Sophia Williams
SVP and General Manager
NCR Telecom and Technology
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
