<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>02-18-21 HOS eWeekly Who Doesn’t Want More Sales.02-18-21 HOS eWeekly Who Doesn’</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Who Doesn’t Want More Sales?</subject>
    <textOnly>February 18, 2021
Who Doesn’t Want More Sales?

Did you know that our new Lokahi podcast &lt;[[https://ncr.seismic.com/x5/doccenter.aspx?ContentId=7b7b476a-4afc-49d4-948c-861950a4934b#/doccenter/8ef384b5-b3bb-424b-823f-729a41e48366/doc/%252Fdd196e06dc-3738-d46d-9523-f4780ed862c3%252Flf6f26daca-545d-4532-a19e-5cca50f60a96/grid/?anchorId=00b8d308-fef8-4de8-80ed-82e7417c33a1]]&gt; is made by sales for sales? Available now on 
Seismic, Lokahi is a fun and engaging podcast series that lets you hear the latest and greatest sales strategies from some of the most experienced folks around who have been successfully selling the NCR Hospitality portfolio for decades. Who doesn’t want to get more sales? If you do, check out a recent episode, Fireside Chat 
with Scott Wakely &lt;[[https://ncr.seismic.com/x5/doccenter.aspx?ContentId=7b7b476a-4afc-49d4-948c-861950a4934b#/doccenter/8ef384b5-b3bb-424b-823f-729a41e48366/doc/%252Fdd196e06dc-3738-d46d-9523-f4780ed862c3%252Flf03f8ff9c-c531-461a-bc02-e2c907a90b48//?mode=view&amp;parentPath=sessionStorage]]&gt;, in which Vic Martinez sits down with Scott Wakely to discuss timeless sales tactics you can utilize today to close even more deals.
Contactless Just Got Better!
We are introducing two exciting new features in NCR MobilePay – Text2Pay and updates to Aloha Stored Value for even more convenience, while helping improve the contactless experience.

Aloha Stored Value
Consumers can 
now use Aloha Stored Value gift cards to pay for the total check amount or apply a partial payment to the check. Also, multiple ASV cards can be combined to cover the total check balance, so now guests can pay how they want to pay with these flexible new features:

Text2Pay
Text2Pay provides the added convenience for guests to pay remotely for call in orders. It’s so simple that all the operator has to do is press the Text2Pay button and a text is sent to the customer’s phone with the NCR Mobile Pay check link or code to pay their bill securely and conveniently. When guests arrive to pick up their orders they can quickly grab their order and go!

Payments Training for Customers
Help your customers better understand Aloha with NCR Payment Solutions through the training courses NCR is presenting on 5 different topics in February. Please share the information below with your customers about the live training that’s upcoming. They can also listen to the recorded webinars when it’s most convenient for them. Here’s the link &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/support/products/ncr-aloha/ncr-payments-training-for-aloha/webinars]]&gt; to register for the training on these topics:

NCR Payment Solutions with Aloha - Overview
This webinar will highlight some of the terminology used in the payments world, review the flow of the payment transaction from the POS to the processor and give you a quick tour of NCR Payment Gateway Portal and the NCR Payment Processor Portal. 



	- Tuesday, February 23rd, 2021 @ 10 AM Central Time Zone &lt;[[https://urldefense.com/v3/__https:/ncr.webex.com/ncr/j.php?RGID=r8ade60ed2b24e006bd10cc65eb7335f8__;!!In4Qlw!68caSWIO-A5v_gfnFLEaiNx14v-TLB3jeW5SlpE6okCqKqrYBt6LGRgx6yYy3AWKgq4$]]&gt;


NCR Payment Solutions with Aloha - Payments Reconciliation
In this webinar, learn about settlements and funding and how you reconcile your payments from POS to your merchant bank account. 



	- Tuesday, February 23rd, 2021 @ 3 PM Central Time Zone &lt;[[https://urldefense.com/v3/__https:/ncr.webex.com/ncr/j.php?RGID=r6ec4fc8b147d45fbdf12be7d791a7bac__;!!In4Qlw!-sLaTUbKMT0rEV3UhqHeF58_zHKB6eiDmcrCoQd2sXXm6mT7UX3sXvDUBXT57QPXFKo$]]&gt;


NCR Payment Solutions with Aloha - Chargebacks 101
Take an in-depth look at Chargebacks, what they are, why they happen, the reports you can use and how you go through the chargeback dispute process. 



	- Wednesday, February 24th, 2021 @ 10 AM Central Time Zone &lt;[[https://urldefense.com/v3/__https:/ncr.webex.com/ncr/j.php?RGID=r598f414951b019b4ad3713bb7105d298__;!!In4Qlw!9JPvoggZQGOPO57m0gDR9IIz2D7X8cT65MocPh1HsaCO_RjSUqe9o_JZCz0nSx3U7R8$]]&gt;


NCR Payment Solutions with Aloha - Resolve Settlement and Reconciliation Issues
Learn how to identify when a settlement doesn’t happen and what you can do to resolve it. In addition, learn what to do when your numbers don’t match between your POS, Gateway Portal, Processor Portal and your merchant bank. 



	- Wednesday, February 24th, 2021 @ 3 PM Central Time Zone &lt;[[https://urldefense.com/v3/__https:/ncr.webex.com/ncr/j.php?RGID=r197748b38b3a366331e334260fa2acc6__;!!In4Qlw!5RatHBMw-tg829KvX_9H07X6KqmUFggYevPoKv5eoPvVqdmeuL4cGsYNsGmrdPDynOE$]]&gt;


NCR Payment Solutions with Aloha - Statements and Fees
This webinar will take a closer look at the statement of transaction fees you get each month for the transactions processed through NCR Payment Solutions. 



	- Thursday, February 18th, 2021 @ 10 AM Central Time Zone &lt;[[https://urldefense.com/v3/__https:/ncr.webex.com/ncr/j.php?RGID=re79be5993d207bbf58743eab4fd87616__;!!In4Qlw!6g-WWWu16uWHAjmd3O8EB6-MBycgrnqu1JWBnfmX53nA9dLWx235Hh0CgZGvnezYJ4U$]]&gt;
	- Thursday, February 25th, 2021 @ 10 AM Central Time Zone &lt;[[https://urldefense.com/v3/__https:/ncr.webex.com/ncr/j.php?RGID=r551b4f8f5c72f00a7d0fd48a6a114818__;!!In4Qlw!-XYVkJylFyrEs3LdmcknDVVJ92KALPLdFyGwzvse_D-FGJAQfvshEjWzQ5vkM5DvfRE$]]&gt;
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
