<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Activate Enterprise.Send Email 3.Email #3</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>How ATMs can become as agile as any digital channel</subject>
    <textOnly>As digital takes a sledgehammer to the traditional ways of operating, the need for a digital-first approach at every self-service touchpoint is essential.
NCR’s new Activate Enterprise NextGen software makes it simple to take that approach:



	- Simple to run, simple to use - Easily configure and install with everything you need right out of the box.




	- Gain a platform for innovation – No more stuck, siloed ATMs that can’t move with the market. Activate Enterprise NextGen offers agility and flexibility to support extended, digital services.




	- Get more eyes on your ATMs – Using modern web technology, Activate Enterprise NextGen attracts consumers to engage with an intuitive, tablet-like experience they know and love.




	- Cross-sell, upsell and promote with built-in marketing – Drive revenue and engagement with marketing and messaging capabilities.




	- Benefit from NCR’s End-to-End ATM Platform - Activate Enterprise NextGen will help transform how ATMs are owned and used, while enabling their expanded role as an access point for digital services.


Explore Activate Enterprise NextGen here &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/banking/branch-transformation/activate-enterprise-nextgen]]&gt;.
${CTAText2} &lt;[[${CTAURL}?${url-parameter}]]&gt;
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;  
   
© 2020 NCR Corporation. All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
