<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Channel Newsletter 9.17.20.Newsletter 9.17.20</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>eWeekly – Building Restaurant Loyalty</subject>
    <textOnly>September 17, 2020
Building Restaurant Loyalty
In today’s climate, there are many reasons for restaurant operators to add a 
loyalty and rewards program to sustain and grow their business. The primary reason? Consumers are seeking personalized, 1:1 interactions, especially from their favorite brands. And delivering on them is key to success.

To compete, operators must cut through the noise of their raw data to expose actionable information — they have to understand what they’re looking at and more importantly, how to use information to create personalized experiences that not only deliver value to consumers, but also improve business results. Read more &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/blogs/restaurants/beyond-a-delicious-dish-building-restaurant-loyalty-with-your-guests]]&gt;

NCR Consumer Marketing Partner Hub
NCR Consumer Marketing presentations, infographics, and training, oh my! Everything you need to share the many benefits of NCR Consumer Marketing with your customers is conveniently 
located on the NCR Consumer Marketing Partner Hub &lt;[[https://ncr.seismic.com/Link/Content/DCNrAU9IM0BUKchOHx9AJ2UA]]&gt;, a single Seismic page for easy access to a plethora of resources. With the NCR Consumer Marketing solution, restaurant operators are empowered to leverage continuously informed data to deliver enriched guest experiences, ultimately improving customer retention and increasing revenue for their business. Learn more &lt;[[https://ncr.seismic.com/Link/Content/DCNrAU9IM0BUKchOHx9AJ2UA]]&gt;
NCR Channel Partner Enablement Calls Keep You Current
Were you unable to join the NCR Channel Partner Enablement call on September 11, 2020? No worries. Watch the recording &lt;[[https://urldefense.com/v3/__https:/myapps.microsoft.com/signin/NCRU/44b8abb3-ee5d-411d-8520-683fb8b60372?RelayState=*252fDeepLink*252fProcessRedirect.aspx*253fmodule*253dlodetails*2526lo*253dd5956971-ba0c-4815-9ee9-488bb740e2fe__;JSUlJSUl!!In4Qlw!7OKcvUAPGXSqwQ9OBq93yz2kVjMDDb1hxDlk92jBGdJR3JQmC4IJhUR7OmEQ0aAm20oN1g$]]&gt; on NCRU and receive 
credit for participating. To view the recording, search on NCRU for the course name: HOSP SMB Channel Partner Call - 09112020 (#85173). 

Please join us for the next Channel Partner Enablement call on September 25, 2025 for an informative session about Aloha tableside/curbside ordering and payment options, as well as Aloha deployment models. Register &lt;[[https://urldefense.com/v3/__https:/ncr.webex.com/ncr/onstage/g.php?MTID=ec19a0177883b1c6cc3ae5c4f5283ecd9__;!!In4Qlw!7OKcvUAPGXSqwQ9OBq93yz2kVjMDDb1hxDlk92jBGdJR3JQmC4IJhUR7OmEQ0aDhNrICpw$]]&gt; today to reserve your spot!</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
