<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>October Newsletter.Subject Line Test</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Newsletter: Contactless, Curbside Considerations &amp; More</subject>
    <textOnly>NCR Aloha product updates and how they can help you
Get the support you need for a seamless contactless dine-in experience
With Aloha—guests just scan a QR code at your restaurant to see the menu, place their order and pay. It’s easy, safe and reliable. Learn how &gt; &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/restaurants/aloha-pos/contactless-dine-in-consultation?utm_source=Email&amp;utm_medium=Other&amp;utm_campaign=&amp;utm_content=Email&amp;utm_industry=hospitality&amp;utm_sub-industry=Restaurants]]&gt;

Only want contactless payment without the digital menu and ordering? It’s just as easy to add with Aloha. In August, over 190,000 guests paid $11.4M through our contactless payment capabilities. Learn how &gt; &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/restaurants/mobile-pay]]&gt;

A powerful new order and pay device for servers instead of guests
Want your staff to control the order and pay experience rather than leaving it up to your guests? Aloha OrderPay, a new solution coming soon, is an all-in-one, built-for-purpose mobile device that enables 
your staff to take orders and payments at the table or anywhere your customers happen to be. 

Get Current with Your Aloha Solution
If you’re using an outdated version of Aloha, you’re missing out on new capabilities that unlock new revenue streams and productivity. Aloha Essentials is our new all-in-one subscription for hardware, software and services that can help you modernize your tech, drive sales and keep your costs down. 

Contact your NCR account executive to get your technology up to speed.
Resources to help you run your restaurant: 
Exceed their expectations to build customer loyalty &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/blogs/restaurants/beyond-a-delicious-dish-building-restaurant-loyalty-with-your-guests]]&gt; Even with contactless, your customers want personalized, 1:1 interactions with you. Give them what they want and they’ll keep coming back.

Make it easy for your customers to understand pay-at-table &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/blogs/restaurants/how-to-communicate-pay-at-table-options-to-your-customers]]&gt; Whether you do it via social media, your website, your mobile app or signage in your restaurants, make sure your customers understand 
how pay-at-the-table works.

Tips so it looks like you’ve always had curbside service &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/blogs/restaurants/how-to-carry-out-restaurants-curbside-service-for-greater-success]]&gt; We’ve collected a few best practices our clients are carrying out around the world to make curbside operations successful.
 
How to optimize take-out and delivery ordering &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/blogs/restaurants/optimizing-your-restaurant-menu-to-simplify-off-prem-ordering]]&gt; Read about three key menu strategies so you can simplify your menu and streamline your takeout and delivery orders. 

Recover and rebuild &lt;[[https://recoverandrebuild.winsightmedia.com/]]&gt; – Check out Winsight’s website that contains podcasts, webinars, national resources and more so you have everything you need to safely and effectively run your restaurant.
Get more support with these training videos: 
Get more support with these training videos: 
Get more support with these training videos: 
Aloha POS &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/restaurants/aloha-pos-training]]&gt; 
Aloha Kitchen &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ao-AESVRAEQ]]&gt;
NCR Payments &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/support/products/ncr-aloha/ncr-payments-training-for-aloha/learning-videos]]&gt;
Aloha Online Ordering &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLpEgSRC5pj_UVIPeShpvDLZT5C3EKbWiq]]&gt;
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;  
   
© 2020 NCR Corporation. All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
