<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>12-22-21 RET NRF 2022 Email 1.Email 1</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>NRF 2022: Join us in New York for the retail innovation future</subject>
    <textOnly>Simple, made possible.
 Join us in New York for the retail innovation future
 NRF 2022 | New York | 16-18 January 2022 | NCR Booth 4819
The National Retail Federation (NRF) Big Show is the world&apos;s largest retail conference. It’ll be back again as a live event 2022, from January 16-18 in New York, NCR is proud to be part of it. With our theme, &quot;Simple, made possible,&quot; we’re showing you how we can help you run your stores more easily, and innovate more quickly.

 NCR’s innovative digital solutions are changing the future of retail with exceptional advances in customer experience. Let us show you how we can make your lives as retailers easier by running your store from a technical, end-to-end perspective. This puts your focus back on your customers.

 Our NCR Commerce Platform is a foundation for retail. It brings together all of the touchpoints, applications, and data that you need to succeed. Running the store can be simpler and more cost-effective than ever. Also, your marketing, operations, and IT teams can drive faster and more effective innovation using better infrastructure and better intelligence.

Visit NCR at Booth 4819 at NRF to discover:


	- 
Better Checkout - How NCR’s Commerce Platform is advancing self service and Point of Sale (POS) effectiveness.

	- 
Better Store Operations - How our Commerce Platform and Run the Store application improve store operations and management success by keeping applications available, current, secure, and high-performing.

	- 
Better Intelligence - How the data that NCR gathers from touchpoints and applications coupled with our consulting services can optimize labor, reduce costs, and increase customer satisfaction.

	- 
Better Customer Relationships - How NCR makes it easy to improve sales and shoppers’ brand loyalty by providing end-to-end strategies and technologies for engaging shoppers before, during, and after they interact with you.

	- 
Better Infrastructure - How NCR improves the cost and flexibility of deploying new applications and new technology into stores by creating a simple, managed infrastructure across devices and networks



We hope to see you in New York!

 &lt;[[https://nrfbigshow.nrf.com/]]&gt;

Learn more about NCR at NRF &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/retail/nrf-2022]]&gt;

Schedule a meeting with us at NRF &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/retail/nrf-2022]]&gt;
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
