<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>12-27-21 RET NRF 2022 Email 2.Email 2</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>NRF 2022: Better customer experience equals a happier customer</subject>
    <textOnly>Simple, made possible.
Better customer experience equals a happier customer
 NRF 2022 | New York | 16-18 January 2022 | NCR Booth 4819
What makes a customer happy? Customer experience is the most important factor to all retailers. We know how to help you provide your customers the best-possible experiences while shopping at your store, and help you harvest valuable data analytics from transactions.

NCR offers point of service solutions for every segment in retail and has fit-to-purpose applications that give associates all the tools needed to delight shoppers. 

You don’t have to change your POS to have high-tech capabilities, our NCR Commerce Platform brings new capabilities to our existing industry-leading solutions. Thanks to the NCR Commerce Platform, it’s easy to give shoppers choice in how they shop with you. You don’t have to sacrifice consistency, visibility, or manageability to drive demonstrable ROI with data-driven, front-end design.

Visit NCR at Booth 4819 at NRF to discover how the NCR Commerce Platform can help you run the store and improve associate experiences and customer-led experiences.

 &lt;[[https://nrfbigshow.nrf.com/]]&gt;

Learn more about NCR at NRF &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/retail/nrf-2022]]&gt;

Schedule a meeting with us at NRF &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/retail/nrf-2022]]&gt;
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
