<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>2021 CSAT Survey Results Notes.09-13-21 BNK CSAT Survey Results Note EN.EN Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>We are acting on your feedback</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear {{lead.First Name:default=Valued Customer}},
 
Thank you again for your participation in our 2021 NCR Customer Satisfaction Survey. The insights you shared are a crucial part of how we learn, grow and make simple possible for you. 
 
I am excited to announce that we saw positive improvement in the overall survey results, particularly in our Net Promoter Score (NPS). 

At the same time, we know that there is opportunity for continuous improvement. Based on your feedback, we are focusing on the following areas and actions within the NCR Banking business unit:



	- Improve our responsiveness and drive more proactive communications in terms of solution roadmaps and best practices globally.




	- Simplify your experience by delivering it right the first time, from offer to onboarding through post-sales support and success.




	- Standardize our global offers, simplify the software distribution process and continuously improve availability and quality of our solutions and services.




	- Continue to innovate, creating additional customer value by enhancing our NCR as a Service offers.


As always, thank you for sharing your feedback and for being an NCR customer. 

Warmest regards,

Frank Hauck
President and General Manager, NCR Banking
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
