<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>end of life reminder to our Quest users - requested by Jessica B</description>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>02-02-2023 HOS EOL Quest Users Comm.02-02-23 HOS EOL Quest Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>NCR Quest End of Life Reminder</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear Quest Customer:
NCR is committed to providing the highest quality products and services to our customers. As part of our strategic processes, we continually assess our existing solution portfolio to ensure we are giving our customers a clear competitive advantage, new technology and product innovation and operational efficiencies. A key element to driving new innovation can be making the difficult decision to discontinue the availability and maintenance of products that have reached the end of their useful life.


We previously announced the end-of-life date for Quest 
Venue Manager, Quest Suites Catering and Quest Suites Catering Online. This is a reminder that the end-of-life date is 
December 31, 2023. Customers will continue to receive support for this product until we reach that date. Shiji has also announced that the end-of-life &lt;[[https://go.ncr.com/rs/605-BQY-740/images/Shiji - EFT Middleware EOL Announcement 103122 Reminder.pdf]]&gt; for their credit processing product integrated with Quest is December 31, 2023.


NCR has partnered with MyVenue who provides a POS and mobile commerce solution to venues like yours. While NCR will be providing full support to NCR Quest customers until the end of 2023, MyVenue has deep experience with the NCR Quest solution and is ready to offer a phased transition to their solution at your convenience. MyVenue is dedicated to the Stadium and Arena industry.

 
For any questions, concerns or account changes regarding the EOL communication, please send inquiries to QVMCommunications.NCR@ncr.com &lt;[[mailto:QVMCommunications.NCR@ncr.com]]&gt;.
&lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
