<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Hospitality Update #2.Email 1b</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>We are here to weather this storm with you</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;
To our valued restaurant and hospitality customers, 
As the coronavirus pandemic continues to evolve, we know that it is significantly impacting your business, your employees and you personally. For over 130 years, NCR has supported the restaurant industry.  We’ve stood by your side when times have been good – and bad - and we are here to weather this storm with you.  We have 15,000 services specialists around the globe and in your local community keeping commerce running. 

Our top priority is helping you during these challenging times. NCR is actively working with a large national bank and the Small Business Association (SBA) to quickly get you the help you need to support your payroll and working capital.  This includes streamlining the process to apply for and grant small business loans.  
 Specific highlights of government assistance for the hospitality industry include:


 - Federally guaranteed small business loans of up to $10 million to help small companies meet payroll and pay mortgage, rent and utilities bills.
 - A deferral of this year’s Social Security payroll taxes until 2021 and 2022.
 - Emergency Economic Disaster Loans, including a quick advance of up to $10,000.


For more information, we’ve established a resource center &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/coronavirus]]&gt; on the coronavirus pandemic, including a page on the United States’ federal disaster response legislation &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/coronavirus/federal-disaster-response-stimulus]]&gt;.   
Over the next week, we will share more details about our partnership with the bank referenced above, including an easy-to-access online portal for applying for loans. Thank you and know that we are here to support you in any way we can. This crisis emphasizes our ability as an industry to come together for unity and partnership. Thank you for being our customer.
Sincerely,
Dirk Izzo
SVP and General Manager, NCR Hospitality
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
