<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Channel Newsletter 9.24.20.09-24-20 HOS eWeekly Channel Newsletter Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>eWeekly – Aloha Essentials 2.0</subject>
    <textOnly>September 24, 2020
Aloha Essentials 2.0
Aloha Essentials adds more value to our core offering and continues to adjust to the current industry landscape. In addition to critical operational functionality, Aloha Essentials also includes the following capabilities – all for one low monthly subscription fee:


	- 
Online ordering

	- 
Takeout capabilities

	- 
Integration with order aggregators and delivery 
marketplaces

	- 
Payments

	- 
Hardware

	- 
Support and maintenance



Check out the Aloha Essentials e-Book and additional marketing materials here &lt;[[https://ncr.seismic.com/x5/doccenter.aspx?ContentId=7aa783ae-de82-4103-bcfc-e88e4242c38f#/doccenter/8ef384b5-b3bb-424b-823f-729a41e48366/doc/%252Fdd1717070f-03d0-418d-d4c2-282b87790374%252Flfb06111ba-f5e1-4d18-8a8d-32fe4e0f827f/grid/]]&gt;.

“Contactless” technology keeps restaurant brands connected to customers

The comfort of your restaurant customers has always been a top priority. But now you have to consider things you didn’t have to before: How many of your customers feel comfortable dining in a closed space indoors? How important is it for you to have outdoor seating? How far apart do your customers really need to be to relax and enjoy their experience? Do most of your customers still only feel comfortable with take out, delivery or curbside service?

It’s a lot to think about. One way you can start to make everyone feel safer in your restaurants—whether you’re a small business restaurant with one or two locations or a mid-market brand with 50 or more—is to introduce contactless experiences for customers. Read more &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/blogs/restaurants/contactless-is-the-new-comfort-how-touchless-technology-keeps-restaurant-brands-connected-to-customers]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
