<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>2021 CSAT Note Mike Hayford.03-10-21 CSAT EN Note Mike Hayford.EN Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Taking action on your feedback</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear {{lead.First Name:default=Valued Customer}},
 
At NCR, we remain focused on the success of our customers.
 
I would like to thank you for your feedback and your contributions to our 2020 Customer Satisfaction Survey. We saw strong improvement in our year over year survey results, which I am happy to see, especially during such a challenging year. For example, last year our customers told us that invoicing was the area they were least satisfied with. This year, we saw a double-digit improvement in satisfaction with invoicing, thanks to multiple initiatives we took across our business.
 
Our results show significant improvement, but there is always room to do better. Our businesses and functions are putting together action plans to respond to the areas where we need further improvement, and our business leaders will reach out with more detail on the actions they are taking to respond to your feedback.
 
Continuously improving how we support your business remains at the core of our vision and strategy, and your feedback is essential for this 
priority. I look forward to hearing more of your valuable insights in our 2021 survey. 
 
Thank you for being a customer of NCR, and I hope that our support of you in this unusual environment made a difference for your business. 


My best, 

Michael D. Hayford
President and Chief Executive Officer
NCR Corporation
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
