<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>01-21-21 HOS eWeekly Channel Newsletter.01-21-21 HOS eWeekly Channel Newsletter</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>eWeekly – Elavon Changes Effective Immediately</subject>
    <textOnly>January 21, 2021
Immediate Changes for NCR Aloha Customers Using Elavon
On Thursday, January 21, 2021, Elavon is transitioning to a more secure digital certificate, PRODGATE02.VIACONEX.COM, in their production environment to process payment 
transactions using the Entrust certificate. NCR successfully deployed a script to make the changes automatically for customers that are using Elavon for their payment services. However, we recommend that customers validate the changes were applied to their environment by following these instructions &lt;[[https://ncr.quickbase.com/up/bqe6gx23b/g/rcj/ek/va/Instructions to Check the EDC Site.pdf]]&gt;. If customers have any questions, contact NCR Customer Support.
BSP Gateway Cutover from NCR Enterprise Platform (NEP) to Apigee
As part of our continuing initiatives to expand and improve the NCR Business Services Platform, NCR will switch Gateway traffic to route through Apigee on Tuesday, February 2, 2021 between 1:00 and 4:00 AM ET. Clients using the NCR Business Services Platform (BSP) will be impacted by this change if their firewall is leveraging IP-based firewall management rules. Please read the announcement &lt;[[https://ncr.quickbase.com/up/bqe6gx23b/g/rcf/ek/va/BSP Gateway Cutover from NEP to Apigee happening February 2 FINAL.pdf]]&gt; for additional details and ensure your customers to take action by January 29, 2021 to avoid any connectivity loss that may negatively impact their business.
Decommission of NCR Dallas Data Center for NCR Mobile Pay Only
NCR plans to permanently decommission our Dallas Data Center for NCR Mobile Pay only. NCR Mobile Pay clients utilizing the Dallas (DFW05) Data Center must whitelist their NCR endpoints before the designated migration dates or they will be at risk of losing access to their licensed NCR Mobile Pay products that are hosted in the Dallas Data Center. Read More. &lt;[[https://ncr.quickbase.com/up/bqe6gx23b/g/rci/ek/va/Decommission of NCR Dallas Data Center for NCR Mobile Pay Only FINAL 1-20-21.pdf]]&gt;
Aloha Essentials Program Updates

Please be sure to read this announcement about important changes and updates for Aloha Essentials related to the following topics:


	- 
Quoting Tool Changes

	- 
Mobile Pay and Online Ordering

	- 
Product Updates

	- 
Discount/Promotions Updates
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
