<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>09-28-22 Channel Partner PLM and Enablement  Resources Update.Email 1</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Update: How we are Enabling our Shared Success</subject>
    <textOnly>Update: How we are Enabling our Shared 
Success
Dear Valued Channel Partners,
 
You may have seen the recent announcement &lt;[[https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20220915006159/en/NCR-to-Separate-Into-Two-Independent-Industry-leading-Companies]]&gt; that NCR’s Board of Directors unanimously approved a plan to separate the company into two independent, publicly traded companies. One will be focused on digital commerce, the other on ATMs, allowing each to deliver even greater value by focusing on their respective strengths. 

We will share more details as they become available in the coming months, but in the meantime, our goal remains to continuously enhance doing business with you and provide the right resources to help drive our shared success. Many of you have shared recommendations and requests regarding things you’d like to see from our Program, and we are excited to share some of the ways we are working to address your needs. We look forward to bringing you more updates as we make progress in our Partner-experience initiatives.
Partner Engagement Revitalization
Our team is committed to helping you make the most of your engagement with NCR, and we are dedicating focused efforts to revamping key areas of need. We have undertaken this important initiative to improve the Partner experience with NCR from end to end, based on your input and feedback.
Since launching this initiative in Q2 of this year, we have already made strides in achieving 
objectives to support these goals, including:


	- 
Solution Availability | We have standardized our Channel authorized solution list to drive consistency and simplicity in the end-to-end onboarding Partners to sell NCR product. This will accelerate the process, from finalizing agreements, to user activation, to training, and beyond.

	- 
NCRU Training | As some of the content in our NCR University application had fallen out of date, we audited and validated active courses for Channel Partners to ensure all current curricula remain 
relevant to current solutions.

	- 
Business Planning | A new and improved 2023 Partner Business Plan template has been completed to streamline the process of strategizing the upcoming year and outlining executable action plans to 
achieve specified performance objectives.

	- 
Performance Targets | We are bringing back the Partner Target Letter for 2023 with the aim of clarifying/staying focused on revenue targets and other performance metrics for the year. We have defined and implemented a new process for helping us to reach our shared goals and will be publishing Target Letters in January 2023.

	- 
Certification Tracking | We have reviewed our library of Solution Authorization Guides (SAG), which include required certifications. These are currently available on Seismic and we will be working on automating role-specific certifications based on the SAGs beginning in 2023. Please note: Available certifications may vary by industry and solution.
More to come soon…

In addition, we have projects underway to improve Partner activation and certification, configuration/ 
pricing/quoting simplification, centralization of access to documentation, and market mapping and release management. As we continue with these projects, we look forward to sharing more updates with you and welcome any questions or comments you may have.
New Role: Partner Enablement Manager, David Rochatka
Many of you have worked with David Rochatka on our Global Programs team for many years and know of his 
significant contributions to the NCR Channel community – defining program components, requirements, benefits, incentives, and the implementation of the channel partner dashboard in communities. He will now be taking on an expanded role as our Global Partner Enablement Manager. In this role, he is responsible for:


	- 
Building a Partner training program that clearly defines sales and technical training requirements by industry

	- 
Creating role-based training pathways that support individuals within Partner organizations

	- 
Defining measurement &amp; accountability mechanisms and the organizations responsible for managing each of the points in the pathways

	- 
Evaluate our available training, industry best practices, and new available mediums to make recommendations on how to modernize our training options



We are very excited about having David in this new position and about the positive impacts he will make in enabling our Partners!
Questions?
If you have any questions or need additional information, please reach out to your CAM or email channels.program@ncr.com. We look forward to sharing more details with you and appreciate your continued commitment and collaboration.

Best regards,
The NCR Partner Network Team
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
