<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>02-11-21 HOS eWeekly Give Your Customers What They Need.02-11-21 HOS eWeekly Giv</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>eWeekly – Give Your Customers What They Need</subject>
    <textOnly>February 11, 2021
Give Your Customers What They Need
It’s exciting that we’re able to provide customers with the information they need 
about the health and performance of our software on the new Aloha Status Page &lt;[[https://status.aloha.ncr.com/]]&gt;. We’re asking for the continued support of our channel partners to help make sure your customers know about this new page and are taking advantage of it. Please encourage customers to subscribe &lt;[[https://status.aloha.ncr.com/]]&gt; to the Aloha Status Page, which helps improve their experience by having access to:


	- 
Upcoming software changes and notifications

	- 
Current incident status information 

	- 
Previous solution incident reports

	- 
Maintenance reports



It’s also very easy for you to subscribe your customers that have expressed interest in the Aloha Status Page to save them time 
using this link &lt;[[https://status.aloha.ncr.com/]]&gt;.
Why contactless is a top priority for the restaurant industry
In the wake of COVID-19, how does a restaurant incorporate safe, contactless experiences without completely changing their floor plan and operations? By embracing technology to deliver touchless experiences that enhance guests’ safety and provide excellent customer service. Check out this new eBook, Why contactless is a top priority for the restaurant industry &lt;[[https://www.fastcasual.com/resources/why-contactless-is-a-top-priority-for-the-restaurant-industry-an-ncr-perspective/]]&gt;, about different ways that technology can help restaurants achieve contactless ordering and payment within the restaurant. And, don’t forget to share the eBook &lt;[[https://www.fastcasual.com/resources/why-contactless-is-a-top-priority-for-the-restaurant-industry-an-ncr-perspective/]]&gt; with your customers as well.
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
