<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Banking Drip Campaign.NAMER - Email 1 (Newsletter)</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Check Out the Latest on NCR and Banking!</subject>
    <textOnly>Check Out the Latest on NCR and Banking!
Dear all, 

When we entered 2020, with all the excitement and anticipation of what the new decade may hold, I don’t think any one of us imagined almost every country in the world hit with a 
worldwide pandemic. However, several months in, this is the reality that we are facing. 

It’s also been heartwarming to see positive stories of community spirit, staff going above and beyond, and governments and financial institutions committed to helping their people and customers in times of need. We’ve decided to share some of these stories for inspiration and best practices from industry leaders. Check them out here &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/coronavirus/keep-commerce-running]]&gt;. 

We’re learning to adapt and have to think differently about everything we’re doing in our personal and business lives. So we’re working diligently to evolve our solutions to enable financial institutions to serve their customers. 

During this time of social distancing, technology that enables two-way, face-to-face interaction is the primary way to stay connected and engaged. Financial institutions that have deployed our ITMs (Interactive Teller Machines) are finding them priceless since they can perform up to 95% of branch transactions, while their branches are temporarily closed. 

A handful of our ITM customers have used the technology to create a work from home environment. And we’re beginning to see strong demand for upgrading ATMs to ITMs. To unlock the advantages, read more here &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/coronavirus/banking/bankplus-uses-at-home-video-tellers-to-keep-customers-connected]]&gt;. 

At NCR, our customer first attitude has never been stronger. We want to help you keep your staff and customers as safe as they can be – while enabling access to the financial services that #keepcommercerunning. 

Our service technicians are out in the field – with the appropriate protection and protocols – to enable your banks and credit unions to remain operational. We’re committed to keeping to business as usual, with strong business continuity plans in place to provide continuity to our customers and availability for your customers. 

We’ve also launched a dedicated coronavirus hub on our website where you can find resources to help you navigate this crisis, provide the best service and keep your business moving. Find them at www.ncr.com/coronavirus/banking &lt;[[http://www.ncr.com/coronavirus/banking]]&gt;. 

While everyone is working hard to meet the needs of our customers, what I’d love to hear is some of the positive stories you’re seeing. Share them with me at Financial.NAMERFieldMarketing@ncr.com &lt;[[mailto:Financial.NAMERFieldMarketing@ncr.com]]&gt; – so we can share them with everyone. 

Take care and keep safe,
Top Headlines 
 


 Coronavirus Response Resources 
 

We have a dedicated coronavirus response page at www.ncr.com/coronavirus/banking &lt;[[http://www.ncr.com/coronavirus/banking]]&gt; 
where you can find helpful information and resources including:


	- 8 simple steps for increasing digital banking adoption

	- Maintaining your customer connections during social distancing mandates

	- NCR&apos;s free Digital Banking Adoption Campaign Kit

	- Trusted resources you can lean on to stay informed during COVID-19
	- Your checklist for driving digital banking adoption
How to Communicate With Customers &amp; Members Right Now  
 
 
 
Information on the COVID-19 outbreak is changing rapidly, and it can be difficult to know what to say.

Here are some topics to cover: 

 	- Cleaning procedures 	- Banking hours 	- Stay in the know 	- Ask for feedback 	- Educate about your online tools 

 
 Find a complete list of tips here &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/coronavirus/banking/banks-credit-unions-how-to-communicate-to-customers-members-during-covid19]]&gt;.
Improve Visibility, Security &amp; More:
NCR’s New Vision SaaS
 
With this move to a SaaS model, NCR Vision is now a hosted software solution to give you full visibility and control over your ATM channel, improving availability, security and compliance, plus better consumer experiences and business performance.

Read 
more here &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/news/newsroom/news-releases/financial/ncr-vision-software-as-a-service-now-in-use-around-the-world-to-monitor-and-manage-atm-fleets-for-financial-institutions]]&gt;.
Simple Steps to Boost Digital Banking Adoption During COVID-19
 
Right now, digital banking is a must-have. But your customers need to know what digital products, features and services are available before they can use them.

To help drive awareness and adoption, download our editable communications starter 
kit &lt;[[https://ncr.quickbase.com/up/bkdhk66i6/g/rd8/ei/va/Digital Banking_Fast%2C Simple%2C and Safe.zip]]&gt;. Find more strategies and tips on increasing adoption here &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/coronavirus/banking/8-simple-steps-for-increasing-digital-banking-adoption]]&gt;.
BankPlus ITM Remote Assist from Home
 
With more consumers turning to video chat to connect during COVID-19, they’re getting more comfortable communicating via camera. That includes banking transactions. 

Read how NCR customer BankPlus was able to connect 5 remote video tellers to support their network of 35 ITMs from home. Get the story &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/coronavirus/banking/bankplus-uses-at-home-video-tellers-to-keep-customers-connected]]&gt;.
NCR Customer Engineer Spotlight
 
Our customer engineers (CEs) are 
working around the clock all over the world to keep commerce running. One of our CEs, Paul Clemente, recently spent a blustery Saturday afternoon onsite with a banking customer performing preventive maintenance to keep their ATM running. Thank you, Paul!
Industry Trends and the Coronavirus
 
NCR will continue to monitor the crisis, work with governments and practice safety measures. What can we learn from countries and markets that were impacted? In addition to the resources on NCR’s Coronavirus Response Hub, below are some articles from external sites that you may find helpful: 

Following COVID-19: How the virus is affecting the ATM industry &lt;[[https://www.atmmarketplace.com/news/following-covid-19-how-the-virus-is-affecting-the-atm-industry/]]&gt;

Banks’ Playbook For Getting Through The Coronavirus Crisis &lt;[[https://www.forbes.com/sites/ronshevlin/2020/03/24/banks-playbook-for-getting-through-the-coronavirus-crisis/?ss=banking-insurance#af3d30a2c5cf]]&gt;

Cardtronics updates fiscal outlook due to COVID-19 &lt;[[https://www.atmmarketplace.com/news/cardtronics-updates-fiscal-outlook-due-to-covid-19/]]&gt;

Banks can stand among the economy’s first responders &lt;[[https://www.americanbanker.com/opinion/banks-can-stand-among-the-economys-first-responders]]&gt;
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://www.linkedin.com/company/ncr-corporation/?]]&gt;     &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?]]&gt;  
   
© 2020 NCR Corporation. All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?]]&gt; | Unsubscribe &lt;[[https://go.ncr.com/UnsubscribePage.html?mkt_unsubscribe=1&amp;mkt_tok=]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
