<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>09-23-22 Burger King Convention Offer.Email Burger King</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Reclaim the Flame with NCR Technology</subject>
    <textOnly>Thank you for stopping by the NCR booth at the 2022 Burger King Convention – it was great connecting with Burger King franchisees and team members to learn about Burger King’s exciting plans to “Reclaim the Flame” in your restaurants.  We know it’s time to prepare for your technology refresh and NCR is here to support you. Our offerings include:

NCR CX5
With its upscale design with lightning-quick speed, the CX5 POS anchors whichever ultimate operator and customer experience you create. This powerful yet low-cost solution gives you outstanding style, capacity, and strength and can be paired with NCR’s software —or your own homegrown applications.


NCR KC4
The high performing and durable NCR KC4 can effectively manage the ebb and flow of both on-site and off-site orders. This means increased customer satisfaction, whether the order was placed on-site, online, via mobile app, over the phone or through your in-store kiosk.


NCR S600
The NCR S600 is a solid-state, back of house site controller designed and built for best-in-class reliability. The S600 operates on an 8th Generation Intel® Core™ processors redefine mainstream desktop PC performance with up to six cores for more processing power.

Hardware Maintenance
And just as important is to upgrade your tech, it is just as important to maintain your tech. With NCR hardware maintenance, your restaurant’s technology is regularly inspected, cleaned, and adjusted. Secure your hardware investments by signing up for hardware maintenance.


NCR wants to help you Reclaim the Flame and ensure that you have the latest technology in your restaurants to transform and create the ultimate employee and customer experience. Whether you’re already an NCR customer, or looking to come on board, contact the NCR account representative to learn more, or download our Solutions Portfolio to learn more about the solutions available for your restaurants.


DOWNLOAD SOLUTIONS PORTFOLIO &lt;[[https://go.ncr.com/rs/605-BQY-740/images/HOSP_BurgerKing_SolutionsPortfolio_FNL.pdf]]&gt;

Taylor Gill
Account Executive
Taylor.Gill@ncr.com</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
