<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Channel Newsletter 10.22.20.10-22-20 HOS eWeekly Channel Newsletter Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>eWeekly – Aloha Online Ordering Migrating to Public Cloud</subject>
    <textOnly>October 22, 2020
Migration of Aloha Online Ordering to Public Cloud
We are excited to announce the migration of Aloha Online Ordering to the public cloud to best meet growing demand and further modernize our architecture. The migration to the new cloud environment started this week and will take place during regularly scheduled maintenance windows, so there will not be any disruption in service.

A communication was sent to all impacted customers explaining the administrative changes they must make to access Web Admin and Menu Configurator after their Aloha Online Ordering site has been migrated.

Decommission of NCR Dallas Data Center for NCR Mobile Pay Only

In 2019, NCR successfully went live with its hosted services in the Microsoft Azure Public Cloud. As such, NCR plans to permanently decommission our Dallas Data Center for NCR Mobile Pay only. We are planning to move other applications out of the Dallas Data Center in the future as well and will keep you informed as we get closer to the date.NCR Mobile Pay clients utilizing the Dallas (DFW05) Data Center must 
whitelist their NCR endpoints before Friday, November 6th, 2020 or they will be at risk of losing access to their licensed NCR Mobile Pay products that are hosted in the Dallas Data Center.
TechFest 2020 Registration Now Open
Have you registered yet for TechFest 2020 on November 10 -13, 2020? Registration closes Friday, October 30th. TechFest 2020 is virtual this year and attendance is totally free. 

This annual NCR Hospitality technical conference provides a unique opportunity for our Hospitality community to come together to collaborate, learn, and have fun networking with peers in the industry. 

Register now &lt;[[https://on.lenos.com/ncr/TechFest-2020/Content/RegisterNow]]&gt;, to reserve your spot.

Here’s a sneak peek at some of the information you’ll learn:


	- 
Wireless implementation best practices

	- 
Aloha Kitchen and Aloha Takeout integration

	- 
Menu and Order Services – integrating with 3rd party applications

	- 
Implementing Contactless Dine-In

	- 
Upgrade simplification and process improvements

	- 
Keyless licensing – deployment and strategy

	- 
Implementing NCR Order Pay

	- 
NCR Payments training that includes payments troubleshooting, payment devices updates, implementation best practices and converting customers to NCR Payments Processing Topics and more...



Unleash the power of simplicity for the restaurant now by visiting the TechFest 2020 site &lt;[[https://on.lenos.com/ncr/TechFest-2020/Content/Overview]]&gt;.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
