<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>NCR Freshop Newsletters.07-27-21 RET NCR Freshop Newsletter - July 21.07-27-21 R</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>NCR Freshop Newsletter – July 2021</subject>
    <textOnly>July 2021
We are excited to kick-off our July newsletter by being a part of NCR, and we can’t wait for you to see what the future holds for NCR Freshop. We know that by joining the industry leader in retail technology, NCR Freshop can scale more rapidly and be an even bigger force in the market. We are excited about this next step in our journey together with NCR.
Read our acquisition Press Release here &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/news/newsroom/news-releases/company/ncr-adds-freshop-e-commerce-solution-to-retails-leading-enterprise-pos-software-platform]]&gt;.
New Customer Highlight
NORTHGATE MARKET



Northgate Gonzalez Markets is the largest Hispanic supermarket chain in the U.S. When the pandemic hit, it was important that Northgate adopted an eCommerce solution that was budget friendly and gave their customers the same in-store experience that they are used to.  

NCR Freshop helped create a Northgate-branded solution, Curbside Pickup Pronto!, to equip Northgate to continue to differentiate themselves as a provider of excellent customer service, no matter when or where it happens. In just weeks with Curbside Pickup Pronto!, Northgate Market’s online sales have steadily grown with well over 50% in repeat customers. And they have an order fill rate of over 90% with clear ordering activity visibility to make quick adjustments, which helps increase order accuracy.

Now, Northgate’s customers are easily ordering authentic Mexican food and grocery items, which are safely loaded into their car in less than two hours.
Read the full story here &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/green-room/northgate-market-ecommerce]]&gt;.
NCR Freshop Product Updates
See our new features and product release notes below:
Payment gateway CX Pay, Moneris
NCR Freshop has integrated with Moneris as a Payment Provider, which will benefit retailers in Canada. For full release notes, click here &lt;[[https://support.freshop.com/support/freshop/ShowHomePage.do?articlestatus=latest#Solutions/dv/300443000038306981/en]]&gt;
Vantiv Gift Card
NCR Freshop now supports Vantiv Gift Cards as an online tender. Simply provide the required credentials from your Vantiv account. For full release notes, click here &lt;[[https://support.freshop.com/portal/en/kb/articles/vantiv-gift-cards]]&gt;.
Driver’s License Scanning /Age Verification (Adding Android Support)
Now retailers may optionally turn on ID verification (US Driver’s License) as part of the fulfillment process. This feature is currently live for both Android and iOS. For full release notes, click here &lt;[[https://support.freshop.com/portal/en/kb/articles/scanning-driver-s-license-during-order-fulfillment]]&gt;.
NCR Business Services Platform integration
NCR Freshop now integrates with NCR Business Services Platform (BSP), which extends the benefits offered by these two platforms beyond their current capability. For full release notes, click here &lt;[[https://support.freshop.com/portal/en/kb/articles/ncr-business-services-platform-integration]]&gt;.
PCI Level 1 Compliance (ROC)
NCR Freshop is now PCI Compliance Level 1 (RoC) certified by a Qualified Security Assessor (QSA). For full release notes, click here &lt;[[https://support.freshop.com/support/freshop/ShowHomePage.do?articlestatus=latest#Solutions/dv/300443000038911653/en]]&gt;.
Zebra ZQ620 bag tag printing  
NCR Freshop for Stores app can now connect to Zebra ZQ620 bag tag printers, which is a mobile bag printer that supports large print areas. For full release notes, click here &lt;[[https://support.freshop.com/portal/en/kb/articles/zebra-zq620-setup]]&gt;.
Subscribe / Unsubscribe SMS order notifications
If a retailer has enabled SMS/text message-based transaction alerts for their consumers, then consumers may turn on user opt-in/out functionality in their Account Creation &gt;My Account page. For full release notes, click here &lt;[[https://support.freshop.com/support/freshop/ShowHomePage.do?articlestatus=latest#Solutions/dv/300443000039187197/en]]&gt;.
SEO  
Search engine optimization (SEO) involves the process of enhancing the content of your website and improving the ability of customers to locate your website from a search engine such as Google. For full release notes, click here &lt;[[https://support.freshop.com/portal/en/kb/articles/seo-faqs]]&gt;.
Supported Browsers
NCR Freshop supports latest versions of the following major browsers: Chrome, Safari, Firefox, MS Edge. NCR Freshop does not support IE Browser. However, if a retailer is restricted to use only IE Browser due to their enterprise restrictions, NCR Freshop may be able to fix the issue after assessment. For full release notes, click here &lt;[[https://support.freshop.com/portal/en/kb/articles/web-browsers-supported-by-freshop]]&gt;.
Link search term to department
A search term can be linked to a department or redirect to a different page by configuring a Search ReDirect tag. For full release notes, click here &lt;[[https://support.freshop.com/portal/en/kb/articles/link-search-term-to-a-department]]&gt;.
Caldera Forms
Caldera Forms will be sunset / retired at the end of 2021. The Caldera team is working on transition tools to make it simple to move from Caldera Forms to Ninja Forms. These tools should be ready and available shortly.
NCR FRESHOP TEAM HIGHLIGHTS
Nik Teshima
NCR Freshop 
Senior Product Manager
Nik Teshima is a Senior Product Manager with responsibilities for NCR Freshop and NCR Mobile Shopper. Nik provides the product vision and collaborative skills to realize our customer success goals with the development, support, and sales teams.
Nik is a graduate of Queen’s University in Kingston, Ontario with a bachelor’s degree in electrical and computer engineering. Nik came to Freshop from IBM where he had 
many roles of increasing responsibility including software developer, product manager, and program director on offerings such as the Rational Developer tools and various high growth digital, SaaS, and hybrid cloud offerings.
His experience in digital native cloud solutions and aggressive growth go-to-market approaches are an important asset as we scale the NCR Freshop offering within the larger NCR Consumer Engagement Platform.
LOOK FOR US AT NGA THIS SEPTEMBER!
The world is starting to find its “new normal” post COVID-19, and we’re thrilled to be participating in a LIVE SHOW this Fall – we hope to see you there!  You can look forward to hearing from our industry-leaders as they demonstrate our new, innovative NCR Freshop product features and more that NCR has to offer.
Rebekah Raudebaugh &lt;[[mailto:rebekah.raudebaugh@ncr.com]]&gt;
NCR Freshop Product Marketer
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
