<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>08-25-21 HOS Support Quest end of Life Announcement.Email 1</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>NCR Quest End of Life Announcement</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear NCR Quest User:
NCR is committed to providing the highest quality products and services to our customers. As part of our strategic processes, we continually assess our existing solution portfolio to ensure we are giving our customers a clear competitive advantage, new technology and product innovation and operational efficiencies. A key element to driving new innovation can be making the difficult decision to discontinue the availability and maintenance of products that have reached the end of their useful life.
This letter is to formally communicate the End of Life (EOL) notification for 
Quest Venue Manager, Quest Suites Catering and Quest Suites Catering Online Products effective 8/25/2021. The last day to order these products is 12/31/2021. Customers will continue to receive support for this product until 12/31/2023.
NCR is partnering with MyVenue who provides a POS and mobile commerce solution to venues like yours. While NCR will be providing full support to NCR Quest customers until the end of 2023, MyVenue has deep experience with the NCR Quest solution and is ready to offer a phased transition to their solution at your convenience. MyVenue is dedicated to the Stadium and Arena industry. Please contact us at QVMCommunications.ncr@ncr.com &lt;[[mailto:QVMCommunications.ncr@ncr.com]]&gt; to find out more.
Below are the key dates and milestones 
that will be part of this process:






Milestone


Definition


Date




End of Life Notification (EOL)


End-of-Life notification is distributed via email to product users


8/25/2021




End of Sale (EOS)


The last day to place orders for the product


12/31/2021




Reminder Notifications


Notifications emailed to product users regarding EOL process until the End-of-Life date


10/31/2022, 6/31/2023, 10/31/2023




End-of-Support


The last day to receive service &amp; support.


12/31/2023





Thank you for your attention to this notification. Please contact us if you have any questions or need additional information.

For any questions, concerns or account changes regarding the EOL communication, please send inquiries to QVMCommunications.NCR@ncr.com.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
