<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>01-24-22 RET NGA 2022 Customer Facing Email 1.Email 1</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>NGA 2022: Join NCR to see where grocery retail is headed</subject>
    <textOnly>Ongoing staff shortages and supply chain difficulties 
continue to dump heavier workloads on grocery employees, who are struggling to stock shelves, pacify entitled customers and, frankly, keep the lights on. The need to automate tasks, eliminate inefficiencies and streamline operations has never been greater.
 
From POS to business analytics to back-office operations and beyond, we’ve made it easier than ever to integrate and simplify your operations so you can focus on your customers. We can help you meet your customers’ evolving expectations for personalized shopping experiences and make best use of free resources to help you run your business in a whole new way.

Visit us at Booth #1219 at NGA 2022 to discover new ways to:


	- 
Introduce your own eCommerce and delivery services within weeks – and 
without expensive third-party providers

	- 
Delight shoppers inside the store with smarter, easier-to-use self-service 
options

	- 
Automate standard processes to free staff and resources to grow the business 
through improved service, relationships, loyalty, and sales.



Join NCR at NGA 2022 in Booth #1219. We’ll be showcasing how NCR is leading the way in grocery technology.
It’s your chance to put our innovative retail technology to the test – and see how we can help run your store, today and tomorrow.

The NGA Show is fast approaching, and 
we’re looking forward to meeting you and your customers!
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
