<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>2022 CSAT Pre-Survey Notes Cycle 2.09-29-22 BNK CSAT Pre-Survey Note Cycle 2 EN.</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>We want to hear from you</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear {{lead.First Name:default=Valued Customer}},


Continuously improving our customers’ experience remains one of NCR’s top priorities. That is why we take your feedback seriously and are asking you to complete the NCR Customer Satisfaction Survey 2022. You will receive a survey link from customer.success@feedback.ncr.com &lt;mailto:customer.success@feedback.ncr.com&gt; in the next few days.
 
Based on the feedback received during the most recent survey, we have made significant improvements:


	- We proudly deliver increased solution availability year over year (YoY), achieving an 11% improvement on first contact resolution and a 1% performance increase against service level agreement, making NCR the market leader in this space.
	- We conducted a successful dry-run of disaster recovery with the Digital Banking cloud-based solution to improve availability. 
	- Delivering proactive services with Smart Services enables NCR to monitor the health of machines and empowers our customer engineers to address concerns.




	- Realignment to the new regional service model allows our team to deliver customized service experiences specific to local requirements.
	- NCR has improved the resolution of software issues with cloud-based solutions, simplifying deployment.
	- We reduced the customer average speed to answer by 75% for Digital Banking customer support.




	- By focusing on enhanced testing and processes, we are improving defect and backlog reductions, availability and quality of our solutions and services.
	- We established the Fintech Advisory Board, which partners with leading experts across the financial services industry to help NCR prioritize the most critical innovations.


We encourage you to participate in our NCR Customer Satisfaction Survey 2022 and share your open and honest feedback with us. Your feedback is essential for improving our offerings, which can help you run your business better.
 
Thank you for being an NCR customer. I look forward to hearing from you.

Best regards,

Frank M. Hauck
President &amp; General Manager
NCR Banking
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
