<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>TX Announcement - San Antonio + DFW.Email 1</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>To Our Texas Customers</subject>
    <textOnly>To our valued NCR restaurant customers in Texas:

We know you have an important decision to make. NCR is here to help.  

With Governor Abbott announcing that restaurants can reopen for dining-in starting on Friday, May 1, ultimately, it’s your choice when you fully reopen your restaurant. We’ll support you whenever you decide to fully reopen. We can consult on any changes you want to make to your operations and ensure your technology is ready.

As you make your plans, give us a call at 1-866-523-3667 or email LH230077@ncr.com &lt;[[mailto:LH230077@ncr.com]]&gt; and let us know how we can help. If your NCR Aloha technology was turned off while you were closed, please turn it on for several hours before calling. 

Our team would be happy to conduct a full Aloha health check to help you get ready to reopen. If there are any issues, we’ll work with you to resolve them. If you would like to get a start on checking your systems, you can:


	- Validate your internet is working on your back of house computer
	- Sign in to Aloha Manager
	- Sign in to every terminal
	- Print something on every printer



 We also have additional resources available for you and your staff:


	- Free online Aloha training &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/restaurants/alohapos-training]]&gt; for your managers and staff
	- Hardware cleaning guidelines &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/coronavirus/cleaning-ncr-hardware]]&gt;
	- Smooth application process for the Payroll Protection Program &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/coronavirus/nymbus-smb-relief]]&gt;
	- Digital marketing recommendations and sample social media and email graphics &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/restaurants/marketingtoolkit]]&gt;
	- Access to additional articles &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/coronavirus/restaurants]]&gt; on contactless payments and delivery, takeout and curbside operations and more.



Thank you for being our customer. Together we’ll #keepcommercerunning.  Reach out to us at 1-866-523-3667 if we can help in any way.

Sincerely,
Jennifer Trichel
General Manager - Texas, NCR Hospitality</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
