<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Channel Newsletter 9.3.20.Newsletter 9.3.20</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>eWeekly – Aloha Online Ordering Migration to the Cloud</subject>
    <textOnly>September 3, 2020
Migration of Aloha Online Ordering to the Public Cloud &lt;#MigrationOfAlohaOnlineOrdering&gt; &lt;#ReminderFulfillmentOrderOnLaborDay&gt;Upcoming Changes Being Made to Business Services Platform &lt;#UpcomingChangesToBSPlatform&gt;
Reminder: Fulfillment Orders on Labor Day – September 7, 2020 &lt;#ReminderFulfillmentOrderOnLaborDay&gt;
New Discover Card Network Issuer Identification Number (IIN) Ranges &lt;#DiscowerCardNetworkIINRanges&gt;
Migration of Aloha Online Ordering to the Public Cloud
NCR is excited to announce the phased migration of NCR Aloha Online Ordering to a new cloud environment, starting on August 31 through November 1. The public cloud gives our systems increased scalability to meet record-setting peak periods and growing demand with unlimited capacity to meet overall order growth. The migration will take place during the regularly scheduled maintenance windows, so there will not be any disruption in service. After Aloha Online Ordering users have been migrated, they will need to use a new admin URL and redownload the menu configurator.  Read 
more &lt;[[https://ncr.quickbase.com/up/bqe6gx23b/g/rba/ek/va/Migration of Aloha Online Ordering to the Public Cloud.pdf]]&gt; .
Upcoming Changes Being Made to Business Services Platform
NCR is making changes to the Business Services Platform (BSP). As part of our continuing initiatives to expand and improve the platform, we are consolidating all existing APIs onto a single API gateway in Google Cloud. Some of your clients may need to complete the specific actions detailed below by September 7, 2020 to avoid any connectivity loss that may negatively impact their business. 

If your clients’ firewalls are using IP whitelisting, they will need to take the steps listed below. If they do not take these actions, they may experience an outage.




	- Update their firewall’s whitelist to include BSP’s new IP address range. Reach out to heather.boatwright@ncr.com &lt;[[mailto:heather.boatwright@ncr.com]]&gt; for this information if needed.

	- Update their firewall’s settings to leverage Mutual TLS, instead of whitelisting.
	- Update their firewall’s settings to leverage Shared Certificates, instead of whitelisting.
	- Leverage a new “Legacy Firewall Bridge” offering from NCR.



 Get additional details here &lt;[[https://ncr.quickbase.com/up/bqe6gx23b/g/r9/ek/va/Upcoming Changes Being Made to Business Services Platform.pdf]]&gt;.
Reminder: Fulfillment Orders on Labor Day – September 7, 2020
Monday, September 7, 2020 is Labor Day, a U.S. national holiday observed by NCR and our logistics provider. It is not considered a business day, so all orders will be fulfilled as listed below. The cut off time for all orders is 6:00 p.m. ET.

Next Calendar Day (NCD) service level orders are not affected by the holiday. These orders will ship the same day as ordered and will be delivered the following day.

Next Flight Out (NFO) service level orders will be available every day, including Monday, September 7th.

Next Business Day (NBD) service level orders will be fulfilled on the next business day following the 
holiday according to the grid below.

AED Next Business Day (NBD) Fulfillment Schedule         Friday, 09-04-20       Friday, 09-04-20       Tuesday, 09-08-20         Monday, 09-07-20       Tuesday, 09-08-20       Wednesday, 09-09-20         Tuesday, 09-08-20       Tuesday, 09-08-20       Wednesday, 09-09-20
New Discover Card Network Issuer Identification Number (IIN) Ranges
Discover has an alliance with JCB, a major Japanese card brand, and UnionPay (UPI), a major Chinese card brand, to reciprocate in processing international transactions on their respective network rails. The Discover card network Issuer Identification number (IIN) ranges for US acquirers now includes 4 more ranges, in addition to the UPI 62 and 81-series announced last year, to accommodate international transactions for JCB and UPI. These new IINs do not affect Discover card transactions made in the U.S.

Please notify your customers immediately that they must upgrade to the appropriate version of Aloha® POS and EDC to enable acceptance of the added IINs ranges for Discover/JCB and ensure they remain in compliance. The table below indicates the minimum required versions that support the added Discover card IINs.

POS


EDC




12.3.85


15.1.35




15.1.48


15.1.35





If the customer is using P2PE with either CES or TSYS, they also need an updated version of ATG. The table below indicates the minimum required versions.
POS


 EDC


ATG - .NET 4.5.2 on the FOH terminal is required


If running out of date XP terminal




12.3.85


15.1.35


19.3.5


19.1.31




15.1.48


15.1.35


19.3.5


19.1.31





Read more details about the Discover/JCB IIN ranges, here &lt;[[https://ncr.quickbase.com/up/bqe6gx23b/g/rbb/ek/va/New Discover Network IIN Ranges.pdf]]&gt;.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
