<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>05-27-21 HOS eWeekly Newsletter.Virtual Solution Experience</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>It’s Here! Virtual Solution Experience</subject>
    <textOnly>May 27, 2021
It’s Here! Virtual Solution Experience
Exciting news! We’re introducing the new Virtual Solution Experience (VSE), a dynamic Hospitality sales tool that lets you visually demonstrate to customers in a virtual environment how different personas interact with NCR technology in the 
restaurant. Our initial release focuses on the kitchen staff persona, providing a lifelike view of how Aloha Kitchen enables greater productivity, improves order accuracy, and supports higher food quality within the kitchen environment.
${CTAText2} &lt;[[${CTAURL}?${url-parameter}]]&gt;
Fulfillment Orders Reminder for Memorial Day - Monday, May 31, 2021
As a reminder, Monday, May 31, 2021 is a U.S. national holiday observed by NCR and our logistics provider. It is not considered a business day, so all orders will be fulfilled as listed below. The cut off time for all orders is 6:00 p.m. ET.
- Next Calendar Day (NCD) service level orders are not affected by the holiday. These orders will ship the same day as ordered and will be delivered the following day.
	- Next Flight Out (NFO) service level orders will be available every day, including Monday, May 31st. 
	- Next Business Day (NBD) service level orders will be fulfilled on the next business day following the holiday according to the grid below.
AED Next Business Day (NBD) Fulfillment Schedule




Friday, 05-28-21


Friday, 05-28-21


Tuesday, 06-01-21




Monday, 05-31-21


Tuesday, 06-01-21


Wednesday, 06-02-21




Tuesday, 06-01-21


Tuesday, 06-01-21


Wednesday, 06-02-21
Customer Support Numbers for Hospitality
Several months ago, NCR Hospitality transitioned to Regional Customer Support teams with unique phone numbers to better serve Aloha users who leverage our Customer Support. We kept the old general support phone numbers active since that time to allow customers time to acclimate to the new phone numbers.
 
Beginning on June 1, 2021, the old support phone numbers will no longer connect to Customer Support and customers will hear a message instructing them to call their Regional Customer Support phone number. Please ensure your customers know they must now use their assigned regional Customer Support phone numbers as appropriate.
Regional Customer Support Phone Numbers






NCR Aloha Support for Small Business


 


  NCR Silver Support




Texas Region


844-263-0305 


  United States


    877-270-3475




West Region


844-263-0298


  United Kingdom


    0808-178-5520




Northeast Region


844-263-0190


  Australia


    1800-940-975




Central Region


844-263-0147


  New Zealand


    0800-453-736




Southeast Region




844-249-9602




  Or log in to your NCR Silver Back Office 
  to chat with a representative
New Pulse Real-Time Sales Enablement Content
New sales enablement materials are available to share with customers and demo the value of Pulse Real-Time, one of the best features of Aloha Essentials. These helpful resources include:
- 
New Videos:



	- 
Internal-only training video - Offers a refresher on how Pulse Real-Time works and demoing the app 

	- 
External-facing video - Provides a high-level walk through of Pulse Real-Time functionality that is suitable to share with prospects and customers 



	- 
Pulse Real-Time “Journey Guides” - Provide helpful scripts and screen flow visuals to help you prepare for your Real-Time demos. These internal-only documents are created for both the iOS and Android versions of the app. 



Access all these resources on Seismic and look for more great content for Aloha Essentials coming soon.
${CTAText2} &lt;[[${CTAURL}?${url-parameter}]]&gt;
Important Reminders:
NCR Payment Solutions Promotional Offer
 
As a reminder, NCR is offering a special promotion for up to two Equinox Luxe 6200 tethered devices per site for customers who sign up for NCR 
Payment Solutions. Read More &lt;[[https://ncr.quickbase.com/up/bqe6gx23b/g/rdd/ek/va/NCR Payment Solutions - Channel Q2 Promotional Offer v3 5-10-21.pdf]]&gt;

NCR Aloha / Sysco Referral Program

We’re excited about the Strategic Referral Program with Sysco Foods that NCR recently signed. Check out this link &lt;[[https://ncr.quickbase.com/up/bqe6gx23b/g/rdh/ek/va/Sysco Deck for Channel Partners 4.23.21.pdf]]&gt; to learn more.

What’s Going on with Aloha?

Help your customers to always stay informed about the current performance of Aloha by encouraging them to sign-up for 
the Aloha Status Page &lt;[[https://status.aloha.ncr.com/]]&gt;.
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
