<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>2022 CSAT Pre-Survey Notes Cycle 2.09-29-22 HOS CSAT Pre-Survey Note Cycle 2 EN.</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>We want to hear from you</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear {{lead.First Name:default=Valued Customer}},
 
Continuously improving our customers’ experience remains one of NCR’s top priorities. That is why we take your feedback seriously and are asking you to complete the NCR Customer Satisfaction Survey 2022. You will receive a survey link from customer.success@feedback.ncr.com &lt;mailto:customer.success@feedback.ncr.com&gt; in the next few days.
 
Based on feedback received in previous surveys, we have made investments and executed on internal improvements that have created positive progress in the overall experience of our customers. Some examples of these actions are:


	- Aloha Simplification — we are executing on quarterly releases, which continue to improve deployment, upgrade experience, and customer configuration tools. Additionally, each quarter, we are expanding and improving above-store and in-store APIs for common services that work across both Aloha and Silver.




	- We continue to transform our business into regionally focused teams to help create a thorough understanding of our customers’ unique businesses and allow for better positioning to assist with issue resolution and supporting our customers’ goals.




	- We have invested significantly over the last six months in new infrastructure and automation within our billing systems to not only improve accuracy and ease of understanding, but also enable simplification and standardization of invoice formats, and enhanced on-demand access to invoice details and reconciliation actions. The outcomes of these major investment projects are beginning to deliver improvements now and additional enhancements will continue to be rolled out in the coming months.


I look forward to your feedback in our October survey to help inform our continued efforts to improve your experience working with us.
 
Thank you for being an NCR customer.
 
Best regards,

Dirk Izzo
President &amp; General Manager
NCR Hospitality
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
