<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Channel Newsletter 6.11.20.Newsletter 6.11.20</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>eWeekly – End of Support for Aloha Guest Manager Jan. 31, 2021</subject>
    <textOnly>June 11, 2020
End of Support for Aloha Guest Manager Jan. 31, 2021
NCR is extending the end of support date for Aloha Guest Manager (text messaging, reservations and waitlist API) from Aug. 31, 2020, to Jan. 31, 2021 to provide additional time for customers to leverage these products until they can successfully migrate to a new solution.

We recommend customers migrate to solutions powered by NCR partners that are integrated with Aloha POS. Customers should contact our partners directly for pricing, features and functionality. You may share this one-page guide &lt;[[https://ncr.seismic.com/X5/DocCenter.aspx?ContentId=75b7ce87-7142-4a89-a852-11c2748a3f0f#/doccenter/8ef384b5-b3bb-424b-823f-729a41e48366/doc/%252Fdd1717070f-03d0-418d-d4c2-282b87790374%252Fdd4388b120-052f-dbea-43a2-e0276b01635e%252Flddefc094c-010d-471a-b921-5979404d505c%252Flf50d30878-ad1f-43ca-b4d9-d8caa360af48/grid/]]&gt; and functionality matrix with customers to help them select a new NCR partner. Please ensure your customers are aware of the Jan. 31, 2021, deadline and are preparing to transition to other solutions.  
Read More &lt;[[https://ncr.quickbase.com/up/bqe6gx23b/g/rh/ek/va/End of Support for Aloha Guest Manager.pdf]]&gt;
Contactless Payments Gives Guests More Control
NCR Mobile Pay is a web-based payment solution that’s fully integrated with the Aloha POS. There’s no app to install—guests simply scan a QR code on their check or use their phone’s browser to access ncrpay.com, enter a 6-digit code, and pay and go! It’s a true contactless experience that puts the power of the payment solely in the hands of the restaurant’s guests. 

Check out this NCR Mobile Pay 
video &lt;[[https://ncr.seismic.com/X5/DocCenter.aspx?ContentId=677da36a-8458-40e4-96c7-34e26489e8ca#/doccenter/8ef384b5-b3bb-424b-823f-729a41e48366/doc/%252Fdd196e06dc-3738-d46d-9523-f4780ed862c3%252Flfe8cb6c9b-0ffa-4f94-9113-5a5e45e403a6/grid/]]&gt; to see how it works!  
For more information, access the NCR Mobile Pay page &lt;[[https://ncr.seismic.com/X5/DocCenter.aspx?ContentId=12793965-4c93-4ea3-8d18-0a6e02ad0f92#/doccenter/1b8ad09d-6094-4388-a5ec-b72bf41e68bd/doc/%252Fdd31be1cf2-f35f-4ef7-9997-dc64deab3ba9%252Flf248ab550-0d12-4245-b268-7c3117647a0b/grid/?anchorId=9b63495f-6276-4c58-8f06-a7c876f11611]]&gt; on Seismic for 
FAQs, customer facing materials, and hardware/software requirements. Direct your customers to visit NCR.com &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/restaurants/mobile-pay]]&gt; to learn more about NCR Mobil Pay.
NCR Payment Solutions Training and Resources
New technical training courses for NCR Payment Solutions are available on NCRU. All sales representatives and technical contacts are asked to complete their respective courses by July 15, 2020. Please visit this link &lt;[[https://ncr.quickbase.com/up/bqe6gx23b/g/ri/ek/va/NCR Payment Solutions Training and Resources v2.pdf]]&gt; for the course numbers 
and descriptions.
Improved Freight Charges Transparency
To provide greater transparency into freight costs, a ground shipping calculation will be applied to orders placed on or after June 4, 2020, using the amount displayed when the order is placed. All orders processed before June 4th will be charged the rates in effect on the date the order was placed. Future 
upgrades to MyNCR are being planned with additional shipping options, so customers can select their preference and see the freight charges upfront. This provides more flexibility and helps customers better manage freight charges. We’ll let you know when the next upgrade becomes available.
Specialized Aloha and Payments Courses Available
Join us for one of our informative training sessions this month to learn more about Aloha Online Ordering, Aloha Kitchen Configuration, Aloha Takeout and NCR Payment Gateway, the solution formerly known as NCR Connected Payments. Advanced registration in NCRU is required to reserve your spot.

${CTAText2} &lt;[[${CTAURL}?${url-parameter}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
