<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>2023 CSAT C1 Pre-Survey Customer Note.03-30-23 COMM CSAT C1 Pre-Survey Customer</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>We want to hear from you</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear {{lead.First Name:default=Valued Customer}},
 
Continuously improving our customers’ experience remains one of NCR’s top priorities. That is why we take your feedback seriously and are asking you to complete the NCR Customer Satisfaction Survey 2023. You will receive a survey link from customer.success@feedback.ncr.com &lt;[[mailto:customer.success@feedback.ncr.com]]&gt; in the next few days. 

Based on the feedback received during the most recent survey, we have made investments and executed on internal improvements that have created positive progress in the overall experience of our customers. Some examples of these actions are:


	- 
Communication — We are investing in our people and streamlining processes to improve your experience in every aspect of your interactions with NCR. These structural improvements will increase accountability and single points of contact for our customers. No matter your need, we will focus on improvements to keep you informed.

	- 
Invoicing — Throughout 2022, we built the foundation that will deliver multiple enhancements to our invoicing experience. Specifically, we improved automation to drive invoice accuracy and a new invoicing structure that will allow for customer-directed formatting of invoices.

	- 
Onboarding and support — To help improve how we develop, demonstrate and deliver our software, we remain focused on advancing our agile processes. Our onboarding playbooks provide well-defined phase gates to enable clear expectations, focused outcomes and timely implementations. We heard your feedback on breaking down silos and delivering on commitments. Our goal is to focus on incident reduction and problem management in support operations.

	- 
Product lifecycle management — We will provide important updates on the product lifecycle and innovations as we work closely with our customers. To better understand your needs, we have continuous quality feedback loops. We will continue to improve automation and integration testing across our products to help you run your store.

	- 
Service delivery — Building on the momentum following our customer support evolution to a pod approach, we applied those same principles within our implementation and delivery teams to get even closer to our customers, drive process efficiencies and make it easier to work with NCR.

	- Software investment — Our goal is to provide world-class solutions for our customers. We have been focusing our investments in the areas that better help you run your store and your restaurant. Research and consulting firm RBR’s Global POS Software 2022 report recognized NCR as the number one global point of sale (POS) software vendor worldwide. We are addressing your industry demands with continued enhancements to our NCR Commerce Platform, including valuable capabilities like eCommerce, scan and go, frictionless checkout, consumer marketing and personalization.


We encourage you to participate in our NCR Customer Satisfaction Survey 2023 and share your open and honest feedback with us. Your feedback is essential for improving our offerings, so we can transform, connect and run your technology platforms. 

Thank you for being an NCR customer. I look forward to hearing from you.

Best regards,

David Wilkinson 
President
NCR Commerce
&lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
