<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>01-13-22 HOS eWeekly Newsletter.Email 1</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Retiring Legacy Equinox PIDs</subject>
    <textOnly>January 13, 2022
Effective January 14, NCR is removing the following 1618 Class Equinox Luxe Model PIDs and corresponding Kit PIDs from the shared MyNCR reseller “Equinox Luxe Payment Terminals” catalog. These Model PIDs were set up before the current Model PIDs which are enabled for Advance Exchange Depot services and should no longer be required. 

If for any reason, you are continuing to order any of these PIDs, please reference the table below for guidance in selecting the appropriate replacement PID. For more information, review the 1618 Equinox Luxe Order &amp; Configuration Guide online at Seismic &lt;[[https://ncr.seismic.com/Link/Content/DCMDT3qxyyykyOZvRvZEB_AQ]]&gt; (click link or search on “1618”). Current document is also attached here for convenience. If a specific Model PID is not already released in MyNCR pre-configured with the required PIN encryption key (PEK), contact your CAM or the product manager for instruction.
${CTAText2} &lt;[[${CTAURL}?${url-parameter}]]&gt;
Discontinued PID     Abbreviated Description     Replacement     Description     Comment       1618-6200-0001     6200m Generic Model for Stand     1618-6200-50nn     6200m for Stand, pre-configured with SW and P2PE encryption.  Select specific model pre-loaded with required PIN encryption key (PEK) as specified by -nn and PID Description in MyNCR.     See section Configuring for Hospitality Customers in the 1618 Order &amp; Configuration Guide for list of all pre-configured models.  Remember to order host cable separately       1618-6200-0002     6200m with Straight Cable     1618-6200-51nn     6200m with Straight Cable, pre-configured with SW and P2PE encryption.  Select specific model pre-loaded with required PEK.     See above.       1618-6200-0003     6200m Mobile w/Printer     1618-6200-52nn     6200m Mobile w/Printer, pre-configured with SW and P2PE encryption.  Select specific model pre-loaded with required PEK.     See above.  Includes AC charger.       1618-6200-0005     6200m Mobile w/o Printer     1618-6200-54nn     6200m Mobile without Printer, pre-configured with SW and P2PE Encryption.  Select specific model pre-loaded with required PEK.     See above.  Includes AC charger.       1618-8500-0001     8500i Generic Model     1618-8500-50nn     8500i preconfigured with SW and P2PE encryption.  Select specific model pre-loaded with required PEK.     See above.       1618-K101     SW and P2PE Encryption for 6200m      N/A     No need to order SW or encryption separately as pre-configured on all models above.             1618-K102     SW and P2PE Encryption for 8500i     N/A     No need to order SW or encryption separately as pre-configured on all models above.             1618-K2xx ~ 3xx     Specific PIN Encryption Key, e.g., 1618-K299 for NCR Payment Processor (JetPay)     N/A     No need to order PEK separately as pre-configured on all models.     If the model is not already released in MyNCR pre-loaded with the required PIN encryption key (PEK), contact your CAM or the product manager for instruction.
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
