<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>10-14-22 HOS Raas Billing and Invoices Comm.Email 1</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>UPDATE: NCR RaaS Hospitality Billing and Invoices</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear RaaS Community,
 
Thank you for being our customer and we are pleased to be supporting your business.
 
As a follow-up to our communication in July, this is an update on the transition of DUMAC’s portfolio to NCR. The NCR team is actively working on resolving a few lingering issues from the integration that has impacted our ability to invoice accurately and timely. As a factor of the integration, the billing of monthly services like Advanced Exchange, Help Desk &amp; SBONet has been delayed since April 2022. We have addressed the delay and the invoices are now processing, with the expectation that we will be fully current with all monthly service billing within the quarter.
 
We understand that some of these issues may have hindered our ability to service your business effectively. Team NCR is committed to ensuring that you &amp; your business are fully supported. We thank you for your patience.
 
If you have any issues or questions, please contact WendysRaaS.ClientServices@ncr.com. 
 
We look forward to a continued relationship and helping you to run your business.

Sincerely,
NCR RaaS Team
Sesha Madapoosi
GM NCR
(813) 418-2353
Seshadri.Madapoosi@ncr.com
Michael Treboni
Vice President, NCR Hospitality 
(614) 571-6151 
Michael.Treboni@ncr.com
&lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
