<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>05-07-21 HOS Support McD HTF Financing Email Resend.Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Financing options available for the upcoming McDonald’s Technology Refresh</subject>
    <textOnly>Please note the email address to contact HTF about lease options is mcdonalds.support@huntington.atlassian.net &lt;[[mailto:mcdonalds.support@huntington.atlassian.net]]&gt;.
As operators prepare for the upcoming McDonald’s technology refresh, NCR is taking a moment to inform you of the steps you need to take to lease your hardware through Huntington Technology 
Finance (HTF).
 
First, we would like to remind you that the best way to manage your business with NCR is by activating your MyNCR account if you have not done so already. To streamline the process, NCR is moving away from Excel spreadsheets and we are now delivering a modern purchasing experience to our customers. You will now receive an email alert from MyNCR once your order is ready for review. Once you receive that notification, you will log into your MyNCR account to review and approve the order if there are no questions OR decline it with comment and an NCR Customer Care agent will review, update and push a new order notification email to the operator.

Current HTF customers will need to log into MyNCR and


	- 
Accept their order in MyNCR

	- 
Decline the order with comment if you want changes made to the order or contact NCR’s dedicated McDonald’s Customer Care team



Once the order is accepted, NCR will notify HTF who will in turn send paperwork to the operator to finalize the new finance agreement. Operator must sign this acknowledgement within 10 days or less to move forward with the lease option for their order. If the operator does not act within the allotted timeframe, NCR will


	- 
Push their requested delivery date out for an additional four weeks

	- 
Notify operator that order will be invoiced as a direct purchase since HTF documents have not finalized within three weeks of the second requested delivery date



Ready to switch to HTF financing for your hardware order

If an operator is not a current HTF customer but wishes to enroll in the finance program, they will need to decline the order with a comment stating that they 
want to enroll in the HTF program or contact the NCR Customer Care team. NCR will switch the order from a direct purchase to a lease and operator will receive a new order notification email. Once operator accepts the order in MyNCR, the operator must finalize documents sent by HTF as noted in the paragraph above that begins with “Once the operator accepts their order.”
 
Operators with any questions or concerns about HTF financing options should contact HTF representatives for assistance at mcdonalds.support@huntington.atlassian.net &lt;[[mailto:mcdonalds.support@huntington.atlassian.net]]&gt; or by phone at 866-445-7039.

For questions or concerns about MyNCR or your NCR account, please contact the account executive for your field office or the NCR Customer Care team via email at Mcdonalds.Orders@ncr.com &lt;[[mailto:Mcdonalds.Orders@ncr.com]]&gt; or by phone at 800.421.8230 on 
Monday through Friday from 8:00 AM ET to 8:00 PM ET.
ACCOUNT MANAGEMENT AND SALES
 




NCR DIVISION


MCDONALD’S FIELD OFFICE


CONTACT




East


Atlanta, 
Bethesda, 
Stamford



Rob Ireland
rob.ireland@ncr.com
W: (770) 299-6202, C: (828) 719-8236





Central


Chicago, 
Columbus, Denver,
Nashville



Amy Spytko
amy.spytko@ncr.com
C: (315) 327-8603





West


Dallas, Long Beach,
Walnut Creek



Valencia Hunter
valenica.hunter@ncr.com
W: (678) 442-1539, C: (404) 840-6975





New Initiatives/
Program Support



 


Tracey Morgan
tracey.morgan@ncr.com
W: (770) 299-5514, C: (863) 326-0542
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
