<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>2022 CSAT C2 Action Note.09-20-22 BNK CSAT Action Note EN.CSAT EN Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>We are acting on your feedback</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear {{lead.First Name:default=Valued Customer}},


Earlier this year, we conducted our NCR Customer Satisfaction Survey 2022. We use these survey results to drive continuous improvement and evolve our business to best meet your priorities.

In addition to what we communicated in July, based on your feedback, we are making further improvements in the areas below within NCR Banking, globally.


	- We proudly deliver increased solution availability year over year (YoY), achieving an 11% improvement on first contact resolution and a 1% performance increase against service level agreement, making NCR the market leader in this space.
	- We conducted a successful dry-run of disaster recovery with the Digital Banking cloud-based solution to improve availability.
	- Delivering proactive services with Smart Services enables NCR to monitor the health of machines and empowers our customer engineers to address concerns.




	- Realignment to the new regional service model allows our team to deliver customized service experiences specific to local requirements.
	- NCR has improved the resolution of software issues with cloud-based solutions, simplifying deployment.
	- We reduced the customer average speed to answer by 75% for Digital Banking customer support.




	- By focusing on enhanced testing and processes, we are improving defect and backlog reductions, availability and quality of our solutions and services.
	- We established the Fintech Advisory Board, which partners with leading experts across the financial services industry to ensure we are prioritizing the most critical innovations.



Thank you for being a valuable NCR customer and we look forward to our continued partnership.
Best regards,


Frank M. Hauck
President and General Manager
NCR Banking
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
