<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>GM CSAT Notes.Banking - English.Email EN</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>We Are Acting On Your Feedback</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear {{lead.First Name:default=Valued Customer}}, 

At NCR, we are committed to making simple possible for our customers. Your feedback helps us learn how we can make your life easier by making it simpler to work with us and advancing the solutions we offer.

So far, 2020 has been anything but normal, but we want you to know that we haven’t lost sight of your feedback from our regular customer satisfaction survey last year. Your responses help us learn how we can make you more successful by making it simpler to work with us and advancing the solutions we offer.

At the beginning of the year, our CEO, Mike Hayford, shared with you the top areas of feedback we heard from our 2019 Customer Satisfaction survey. We appreciate all the input you gave us, which helps us learn, grow and improve. 

Since then, within the Banking business unit, we have prioritized actions based on the top areas of feedback shared in the survey:


	- 

Driving outstanding customer service. In response, we have invested in our client-facing teams, focused on working closely with you on the entire customer journey to help ensure that NCR enables your success.

	- 

Streamlining the invoicing processes, to make it easier to understand your invoice.

	- 

Improving the availability and quality of hardware and software so that we help you provide a consistent, reliable and high-quality experience to your customers. Our action plan for this focus area includes the integration of customer feedback earlier in the process as we work to continuously improve. 



Enhancing our customer experience remains a top priority for NCR, and we want to know how we are doing. Later this year, we will conduct our 2020 Customer Satisfaction Survey, and we encourage you to participate and offer your feedback. During this time of rapid change, we want to hear from you now more than ever.

Thank you for being an NCR customer and for sharing your valuable insights with us.

Warmest regards,

Frank Hauck
EVP and President, NCR Banking</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
