<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>2022 CSAT Results-Survey Notes.07-14-22 RET CSAT Results-Survey note EN.EN Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>We are acting on your feedback</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear {{lead.First Name:default=Valued Customer}},
 
Earlier this year, we conducted our 2022 NCR Customer Satisfaction Survey, with many of our customers participating and sharing their opinion with us. We have continued using that feedback as a foundation for how we learn, improve, and make working with us simpler—all to keep our customers satisfied and grow together.
 
After several weeks of analyzing the input we received through this survey, I am excited to let you know we saw improvement in the overall survey results for the fourth consecutive year, particularly in our Net Promoter Score (NPS).

At the same time, we are aware there is always room for improvement. Based on your feedback, we are focusing on the following areas within the NCR Retail business unit:



	- Communication—We continue to make structural improvements so that there will be increased accountability and single points of contact for our customers. The relaxation of the COVID-19 pandemic restrictions has increased NCR associate presence in our global locations allowing for greater cross functional communication and creativity internally, plus will increase customer face-to-face interaction opportunities.
	- Software Support &amp; Quality—We continue to remain focused on advancing our agile processes to help improve how we develop and deliver our software. Our goal is to reach full end-to-end automation for our products and the entire solution, consistent practices for code reviews and greater sprint governance. Another key focus remains on incident reduction and problem management in our software support to enable higher levels of availability.
	- Product Lifecycle Management—As part of the overall communication improvements, we will be sharing more details on our product lifecycle and areas of innovation as we work more closely with our customers to better understand your needs and build the products that help you differentiate and grow.



As always, thank you for being an NCR customer. We look forward to making further improvements and continuing to hear from you.

Warmest regards,

David Wilkinson
President &amp; General Manager
NCR Retail
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
