<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>11-22-21 HOS Integration Partner Newsletter.Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>NCR 3rd Party Partnerships Newsletter</subject>
    <textOnly>November 22, 2021
Greetings Third Party Partner,

We’re excited to send you NCR’s second Third Party Partner Newsletter. As always, we value our partnership and hope to stay better connected in sharing the latest updates, new partner additions, support information, FAQ’s and more. Below you’ll find a wealth of content that will hopefully be of interest to you as we continue to build out our partner ecosystem with our joint customers in mind. Giving our customers access to the “best of the best” in each vertical is important to NCR. As you review the information enclosed, please do not hesitate to reach out with any questions or comments (See FAQ’s). We welcome your feedback and look forward to continuing our value-added partnership in the future.
In this issue



	- Welcome New Partners
	- Learn more about our Aloha Essentials program
	- NCR in the News
	- FAQ&apos;s
Welcome New Partners




	- MadMobile - Mobile Restaurant Solutions, Tableside, Guest &amp; Table Management, Loyalty, Online Ordering &amp; Curbside Pickup, Menu Management, Team &amp; Time Management, Restaurant Dashboards &amp; Reports
	- Wisk – Inventory control, business analytics
Frequently Asked Questions



	- How to Obtain NCR Support
	- Billing Questions and Deadlines
	- Do you have another question that is not answered above, please contact Partner Relations at ISV.Partnerships@ncr.com &lt;[[mailto:ISV.Partnerships@ncr.com]]&gt;
Invoicing Updates
Did you know that you have several choices for how you can receive your invoices?



	- Mail – this is the default communication method
	- Email – Please email HospitalityPartnership.HSR@ncr.com &lt;[[C:\Users\CQ185008\AppData\Local\Microsoft\Windows\INetCache\Content.Outlook\NVQVU1M2\HospitalityPartnership.HSR@ncr.com]]&gt; to request email receipt of your invoice and include:


	- Your MCN
	- The email address you would like your invoices sent to


	- Portal – you can apply for Portal access via https://www.ncr.com/how-to-buy/account-request &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/how-to-buy/account-request]]&gt;



	- Here you can view your invoice, view a statement of your account, history and make payments.
	- You can also log an invoice dispute through the portal.
How to obtain NCR support
Remember as an official partner you do not need to have our 
mutual customer open a support incident/ticket. You are empowered to open a support ticket by following these steps:



	- Call the support line at 800-792-5642, option 2.
	- Email support@alohaenterprise.com &lt;[[mailto:C:\Users\CQ185008\AppData\Local\Microsoft\Windows\INetCache\Content.Outlook\NVQVU1M2\support@alohaenterprise.com]]&gt; (for non-critical issues ONLY)



Needed Case 
Information: The following information is required to be provided. This information helps NCR Support quickly create and resolve any technical/support issue:



	- Third Party Partner’s name
	- Name of the customer you are working with
	- Integration Type: Cloud Connect/API, Business Service Platform (BSP), or SDK/COM?
	- Customer&apos;s Site HASP Key #
	- Date / Time issue occurred
	- Detailed Description of issue (Including any API call, any POS error message, Nep org, Enterprise unit, BSP order id)
	- Point of Contact Name &amp; Email/Phone for Third Party Partner and customer
Learn more about our Aloha Essentials program
Everything you need to meet today’s new challenges
 
Your customers and employees want service that’s safe, smooth and low-contact—whether in-house, takeout or delivery. You need easy ways to orchestrate these new experiences, coordinate your kitchen and regain your revenue so you can drive more business and get back to where you want to be. You can do it all with NCR Aloha Essentials:


	- 
Online ordering, curbside pickup and 
delivery integrations to drive digital sales and regain revenue

	- 
Contactless ordering and payment to give 
guests confidence when dining in

	- 
Flexible kitchen technology to easily meet 
the increasing demand for digital orders while keeping your kitchen organized

	- 
Real-time reports via a mobile app to 
dynamically manage your business and check in—even when you’re out

	- 
Gift cards and loyalty to engage guests 
and keep them coming back

	- 
Secure payments processing and the 
world’s #1cloud-enabled restaurant POS

	- 
A single subscription that provides all 
the hardware, software and services you need for one low monthly fee



To find out more, please visit the link below:

https://www.ncr.com/restaurants/aloha-pos/aloha-essentials &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/restaurants/aloha-pos/aloha-essentials]]&gt;
NCR in the News
NCR Acquires Foremost Business Systems, Brings Restaurant Technology and Support to Minneapolis
 
ATLANTA, Aug. 23, 2021 – NCR Corporation (NYSE: NCR), a leading enterprise technology provider, today announced the acquisition of Foremost Business Systems, a point-of-sale (POS) and restaurant solutions provider in Minneapolis.

This transaction further expands the reach of NCR’s restaurant technology – which is trusted by more than 100,000 restaurants around the world. Solutions including the signature NCR Aloha &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/restaurants/aloha-pos]]&gt; POS platform and NCR Aloha Essentials &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/restaurants/aloha-pos/aloha-essentials]]&gt; subscription package provide everything restaurants need to run their business, boost efficiency and increase growth.

To find out more, please visit the link below: 

https://www.ncr.com/news/newsroom/news-releases/company/ncr-acquires-foremost-business-systems &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/news/newsroom/news-releases/company/ncr-acquires-foremost-business-systems]]&gt;
NCR Supporting Restaurant Recovery with Donation to Elevate Together™

ATLANTA, August 16, 2021 – NCR Corporation (NYSE: NCR), a leading enterprise technology provider, today announced a donation of $200,000 to Elevate Together™, a nonprofit 
initiative designed to create growth and prosperity for Black and Hispanic communities.

The donation was made by the NCR Foundation &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/about/foundation]]&gt;, a founding partner of Elevate Together, which is powered by Round It Up America® (RIUA). NCR’s donation is being used to award cash grants to minority-owned businesses in the Atlanta region.

“We want to do what we can to support the restaurant industry as it finds its footing after a difficult year,” said Dirk Izzo, president and general manager, NCR Hospitality. “We are honored to collaborate with Elevate Together and Round It Up America to support the hospitality industry.”

To find out more, please visit the link below:

https://www.ncr.com/news/newsroom/news-releases/company/ncr-supporting-restaurant-recovery-with-donation-to-elevate-together &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/news/newsroom/news-releases/company/ncr-supporting-restaurant-recovery-with-donation-to-elevate-together]]&gt;
100,000+ restaurants rely on NCR. Here’s why
Global scale, local focus

If you’re opening just one or two restaurants in your community, our local experts will help you build a profitable business. And as you grow to 10, 100, 1,000+ locations—or if you’re there already—we’ll be right there every step of the way.

We’re customer-first

“Treat every customer like they are our only customer” is our credo. And we have over 20,000 service professionals in 160 countries, including regional customer care teams and client success managers, that get to know you personally and are measured on your success.

End-to-end solution

From guest acquisition and retention to digital ordering and delivery to managed services that maximize the uptime of your 
technology—you’ll get everything you need to run your restaurants and grow in a simple subscription.
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
