<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>Jessica B Objective: Inform SMB Aloha users of a new product available</description>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>11-22-22 Consumer Marketing - Aloha Enterprise - new product.11-22-22 HOS Consum</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>NCR Consumer Marketing Now in General Release</subject>
    <textOnly>Consumers are expecting more and more from the brands they interact with. They want a tailored experience based on prior interactions, but only 16% of companies can even come close to delivering on this.

You may be challenged with uncovering meaningful insights from the data you collect due to gaps in your customer journey or a lack of in-house expertise. Or your marketing teams may not be able to quickly adapt marketing messages or strategies to reflect changes in guest preferences. 

 With this increased pressure, it’s more important than ever to:


	- Know who your customers are across all buying channels and marketing touch points
	- Uncover critical guest insights based on all spend and non-spend behaviors
	- Leverage automation and segmentation to act on those behaviors and insights
	- Identify and control your margin on both non-loyal and marginally loyal customers
	- Infuse machine learning into your tech stack to optimize purchases, frequency, engagement, and advocacy



We’ve recently launched NCR Consumer Marketing &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/restaurants/customer-engagement-loyalty]]&gt;, an all-in-one data management, loyalty and marketing communication platform that helps you deliver unified guest experiences that matter. 

With our solution, your marketing team can:


	- Manage and motivate the behaviors of all guests – not just the ones enrolled in your loyalty program
	- Trigger data-driven campaigns that meet each of your guests with valuable offers, relevant communication, and thoughtful  recommendations at every point in their journey
	- Reduce costs, resources and time by combining data management, loyalty and marketing into one platform



Join us for a webinar on these new capabilities on December 8th at 1:30 PM. Click here &lt;[[https://ncr.webex.com/ncr/onstage/g.php?MTID=e56ae0b73a3ff71c602f3dff1312b64ab]]&gt; to register.
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
