<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>10-26-21 HOS VitalCast Migration.Email 1</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>REMINDER: Migration of NCR Vitalcast to Microsoft Azure</subject>
    <textOnly>Migration and Decommission of VitalCast in the NCR Data Center
As part of the migration of our products to Microsoft Azure Cloud, we will begin migrating our NCR VitalCast on-premises environment to Azure in November 2021.

The migration will occur in 2 phases on Monday, November 1, and Thursday, November 4. The first phase is the move to a new endpoint followed by the production environment migration to Microsoft Azure Public Cloud. Moving to the Azure Cloud Platform provides multiple benefits:



	- Improved stability and reliability for optimal performance leveraging state-of-the-art technology




	- Enhanced monitoring capabilities to proactively detect anomalies




	- Ability to scale capacity based on workload




	- Optimizes network performance, storage and database performance




	- Improves application performance by identifying bottlenecks to ensure users have the best experience




	- Provides robust capabilities with modern intelligence tools that provide detailed environment and product metrics for analysis and reporting


ACTION REQUIRED:

You will need to whitelist the NCR endpoints now to prepare for the migration, or you will be at risk of losing access to your licensed NCR product that is being migrated to Azure.
Please whitelist the following IP Range: 




Product


Environment


IP Address


Ports


Notes




VitalCast


PROD


192.75.147.10


80, 443, 22


www.ncrvitalcast.com




VitalCast


PROD


20.88.206.72


80, 443


kace.ncrvitalcast.com
TIMING:
Migration dates are November 1, 2021, and November 4, 2021.

WHAT TO EXPECT:


On November 1, 2021, we will migrate to the new endpoint defined in the table above. There is no production downtime expected on this day. On November 4th, you can expect downtime from 4PM - 7PM Eastern Time. If you have already made your firewall/whitelisting changes, there should be no impact to your software and how you use it. Sites that have not performed the necessary changes will no longer be able to post or pick up new content plans for their devices. This will not affect content plans already playing on the devices at the site, but new plans will not be delivered.

Thank you for your cooperation in advance to avoid any risk of losing access to your licensed NCR products once they are migrated to Cloudflare. Please contact NCR Customer Support if you have any questions or experience any issues, so we can assist you as quickly as possible.
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
