<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>2022 CSAT C2 Action Notes.01-09-23 BNK CSAT C2 Action Note EN.EN Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>We are acting on your feedback</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear {{lead.First Name:default=Valued Customer}},
 
Late last year, we conducted our NCR Customer Satisfaction Survey 2022, with many of our customers participating and sharing their opinion with us. We continue to use that feedback as a foundation for how we learn, improve, and make working with us simpler — all to keep our customers satisfied and grow together. 

After analyzing the survey, I am excited to let you know we saw improvement in the overall survey results for the fourth consecutive year, particularly in our Net Promoter Score (NPS).

At the same time, we know there is always opportunity for improvement. Based on your feedback, we are focusing on the following areas within the NCR Banking business unit:


	- 
We have deployed our innovative recycling technology, the 60 series products, which is live in three countries and ready to expand deployments in 2023. 

	- 
We are focused on expanding and simplifying solution offers to software as a service (SaaS).

	- 
We improved solution quality through enhanced test suites and corrective actions.

	- 
Digital Banking support is focused on improving resolve time and speed to answer. 

	- 
Client Services is developing services to improve onboard cycle time for new products to achieve faster time to customer value.



As always, thank you for being an NCR customer and we look forward to making further improvements based on what matters most to you. 

Best regards,

Frank Hauck
President and General Manager
NCR Banking
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
