<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>09-16-21 HOS eWeekly Newsletter.Aloha Loyalty Now Available with Mobile Pay</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Aloha Loyalty Now Available with Mobile Pay</subject>
    <textOnly>September 16, 2021
Existing Aloha Loyalty Now Available with Mobile Pay
Restaurants with Aloha Loyalty can now easily apply their customer’s loyalty account to their checks so they can earn and burn points through Mobile Pay. When Loyalty is activated, a new field appears prompting users to enter their phone number to link to apply any loyalty discounts. Users receive confirmation of how much they saved due to loyalty.



	- Operators can also view how many loyalty discounts have been applied on the Mobile Pay Dashboard




	- To activate with existing Aloha Loyalty customers:


	- For customers who already leverage both Mobile Pay and Aloha Loyalty and would like to activate this feature: send a ticket to Aloha Support to upgrade to the most recent version of Mobile Pay and activate loyalty
	- New Mobile Pay customers will have Aloha Loyalty automatically upgraded if they are subscribed to Aloha Loyalty






	- Feel free to send any other questions/requests to Jessica.boesch@ncr.com &lt;[[mailto:Jessica.boesch@ncr.com]]&gt;




	- Information on Customer Experience: https://ncr.seismic.com/Link/Content/DCc-EZURlOL0Kf03YP5ldjdQ &lt;[[https://ncr.seismic.com/Link/Content/DCc-EZURlOL0Kf03YP5ldjdQ]]&gt;


*Currently this capability is only available for customers subscribed to both Aloha Loyalty and Mobile Pay. We will be working on an integration with the Consumer Marketing Basic Loyalty capabilities included in Aloha Essentials.
Continuing to Support Restaurants Through the Labor Shortage
As restaurateurs continue to struggle with labor shortages, they’re looking for ways to attract new talent. Our latest Primer article outlines how to leverage a referral program to find quality new hires.

https://www.ncr.com/blogs/restaurants/restaurant-employee-referral-program &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/blogs/restaurants/restaurant-employee-referral-program]]&gt;
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
