<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>https://info.bai.org/how-atm-outsourcing-solves-atm-security-challenges-webinar.html?utm_medium=email&amp;utm_source=ncr_ref&amp;utm_campaign=webinar_100422</description>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>09-29-22 P&amp;N BAI Webinar invite.Email 1</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>How ATM Outsourcing Solves ATM Security Challenges</subject>
    <textOnly>In an age when cyber security is top of mind for virtually everyone, the security of physical channels, like the ATM, must not be overlooked. The ATM remains a critical service delivery and satisfaction driver, but as resource allocations follow mobile and online channels, ATM management and security may not keep pace. Consequently, banks and credit unions of all sizes are considering how to outsource the management of ATMs to reduce resource needs while ensuring customer data, experience and loyalty remain safe and intact.

Staying a step ahead of the bad actors who are intent on breaking into ATMs – either physically or digitally - is complex and a constant battle. Outsourcing your ATM fleet management to a third party removes the headache but the security protocols deployed by that provider must be formidable.
 
Join us on this webinar &lt;[[https://info.bai.org/how-atm-outsourcing-solves-atm-security-challenges-webinar.html?utm_medium=email&amp;utm_source=ncr_ref&amp;utm_campaign=webinar_100422]]&gt; as we 
discuss:


	- 
What are the current and emerging security threats to ATMs and self-service 
devices 

	- 
Best practices to protect against cyber and physical security threats 


	- 
ATM as a Service as a strategy to improve service, reduce operational 
complexity and take on security threats all at once

	- 
The security components of an ATMaaS solution and what to look for in a 
provider



Speakers:


	- 
Shpend Ibraimi, Executive Director, ATM as a Service for North America, 
NCR

	- 
Max Garcia, CISO, Banking Division, NCR 
Corporation
${CTAText2} &lt;[[${CTAURL}?${url-parameter}]]&gt;
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
