<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>NCR Aloha SMB Customer Newsletter.04-29-21 HOS Newsletter Aloha SMB Customer.Ema</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Register Now for Pandemic-Related Funding</subject>
    <textOnly>#What&apos;sNew@NCR
SBA grants for pandemic-related revenue losses
The American Rescue Plan Act established the $28.6B Restaurant Revitalization Fund (RRF) to provide restaurants with funding equal to their pandemic-related revenue losses 
up to $10 million per business and no more than $5 million per physical location. You must register on the SBA website starting on April 30th before you can submit an application for a grant. Visit our American Rescue Plan Act site &lt;[[http://www.ncr.com/blogs/sba-smb-relief]]&gt; to learn more about eligibility and check out the resources below for more information.
- Restaurant 
Revitalization Fund Program Guide &lt;[[https://www.sba.gov/sites/default/files/2021-04/2021.04.17 - Restaurant Revitalization Funding Program Guide vFinalshare-508.pdf]]&gt; – This guide goes into detail on what the funds can be used for and who is eligible for a grant.
	- Restaurant Revitalization Fund Sample 
Application &lt;[[https://www.sba.gov/document/sba-form-3172-restaurant-revitalization-funding-application-sample]]&gt; – The questions that eligible companies will need to fill out once the application officially goes live on the SBA portal.
Easily open support cases with NCR Pulse
Now, when you need help, you can create a support incident directly in your Pulse app if you have Real Time, Restaurant Guard, or Customer Voice. You’ll get immediate confirmation of your case with an incident ID, and you can add notes, attach photos, screenshots and documents to your incident.
Contactless dine-in is a game changer
Differentiate your restaurant by offering a contactless dine-in experience. New features in our Digital Ordering platform let guests keep a check open until they’re ready to close out and pay on their phone. They can also stage their order—beverages, appetizer and entrée—sending items to the kitchen when they’re ready for the next course. And the contactless Group Pay option allows one guest to pay for multiple orders from their phone in a single transaction.
${CTAText2} &lt;[[${CTAURL}?${url-parameter}]]&gt;
Insight polling upgrade
NCR is upgrading sites to the new Pulse Agent process to use for Insight polling beginning on Monday, April 26, 2021. We’ll upgrade sites in waves for several months until all Insight customers have been upgraded. Review the Insight polling FAQs &lt;[[https://ncr.quickbase.com/up/bqe6gx23b/g/rdb/ek/va/Insight Polling FAQs.pdf]]&gt; for more details.
Digital kitchens are transforming the industry
The kitchen of today is a digital operation driven by vision and the adversity of the pandemic. Innovations slated for the future were accelerated by months and even years. To see four areas where kitchen technology will continue to shape the future, check out our white paper:
${CTAText2} &lt;[[${CTAURL}?${url-parameter}]]&gt;
Latest Aloha updates
We’re here for you 24/7/365, providing status updates about the performance of Aloha via text, email or RSS Feed, whenever you need it. Sign-up today for the Aloha Status Page &lt;[[https://status.aloha.ncr.com/]]&gt; to start getting the latest updates about the health and performance of our software.
Keep learning
The Primer for restaurants—see what’s cooking in your industry
- 9 ways restaurant tech can enable off-premise ordering 
success &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/blogs/restaurants/restaurant-tech-off-premise-ordering]]&gt;
	- What can restaurants learn from the 2008 financial 
crisis? &lt;[[•	What can restaurants learn from the 2008 financial crisis?]]&gt;
	- Seeing ghosts: The pros and cons of a virtual kitchen &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/blogs/restaurants/ghost-kitchen-pros-cons]]&gt;
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
