<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>10-28-21 HOS eWeekly Newsletter.Email 1</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>New Mounting Bracket for Luxe 6200m</subject>
    <textOnly>October 28, 2021
New Mounting Bracket for Luxe 6200m
A new version of the 1668-K142 adapter for mounting an Equinox Luxe 6200m on the NCR P1535 terminal has been released and is now orderable in MyNCR. The updated kit, 1668-K144, has been modified to change the angle and position of the 6200m so that the pinpad can be moved closer to the terminal
display without interfering with the side-mounted MSR on the POS. Both kits are priced the same. The 1668-K142 adapter will remain orderable to deplete remaining inventory but will eventually be discontinued in favor of the new 1668-K144 option. Either kit must be ordered with the original 1668-K117 VX820 pinpad bracket if 1668-K117 is not already installed on the P1535. The 1668-K136 4” mounting stand and various base options will remain unchanged as alternate mounting options.
Also available is a new 1668-K146 bracket for mounting a 6200m on the NCR CX5/7 POS terminal. All inclusive, this kit features a bracket with sliding arm compatible with all CX configurations, including wall mounts, and allows the pinpad to be placed on either left or right side of the terminal display. Like the P1535 mounting options for the 6200m,
the 1668-K146 is more expensive than a countertop stand and therefore only recommended when the POS is wall mounted and/or placed in tight locations such as a wait station or drive thru window. 1668-K146 is orderable today in MyNCR, but not currently stocked and initial lead times may be over 8 weeks.
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
