<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>05-16-22 BNK 360 Release Announcement.Email 1</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>NCR Operations 360’s delivers fast and efficient data</subject>
    <textOnly>Operations 360 delivers new features to manage and operate your business
We’re excited to announce enhancements to the NCR Operations 360 solution, helping financial institutions bridge the divide between operations management and analytics. The latest version includes a host of new features to help you reach information faster and more efficiently. 

Here’s a quick rundown of what’s new: 

Mobile Experience
If you read only one thing about this exciting release, let it be mobile experience.
 
We heard your feedback that our mobile experience could be improved and redesigned our solution to literally put the power and flexibility of Operations 360 in the palm 
of your hand. Here’s what is different:


	- 
Digitally rich and mobile-optimized experience

	- 
Full access to all Operations 360 capabilities

	- 
Automatic adjustment to any mobile device display 

	- 
Hassel-free, web-based solution – all in a single application



Improved Menu Navigation
We’ve created an entirely new look and organization for the menu navigation. Structured for usability, the new navigation lets you dive in and easily find the information you need to manage your business. 

Electronic Journal
We have enriched the electronic journal experience with an additional dashboard where you can see a side-by-side view of tables, such as Transaction, Supervisor, Host, etc. 

Operations 360 just keeps getting better
These are just a few of the new capabilities on the way. Operations 360 is designed to be the foundational tool for your financial institution – and we’re just getting started. We think you’ll love what this latest release has to offer. 

See the new version for yourself
Watch &lt;[[https://youtu.be/oIhPAlbHLxk]]&gt; the video to see all the new features and capabilities. 

Then, contact your account team to discuss the date you will upgrade to this latest release of Operations 360. 

Kind regards,
 
NCR Operations 360 Product Team
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
