<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>04-14-21 HOS CMC Migration to Azure-UAT Prep.04-14-21 HOS CMC Migration to Azure</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Important Announcement</subject>
    <textOnly>Migration and Decommission of Command Center in the NCR Dallas Data Center
Dear Valued NCR Customer: 
 
Previously, NCR notified you of plans to migrate Command Center from our on-premises data center to Azure Public Cloud platform. This is to notify you that your sites have been identified for migration to Azure. This will include both a CMC Agent version upgrade and a CMC Client upgrade and migration to our Command Center environment in Azure public cloud.
 
You have been identified as having a site in our UAT/Pre-Production environment and our Production environment. Our first phase will be to migrate the sites in our UAT/Pre-Production data center to our Azure Public Cloud environment so you can validate your sites are prepared for the eventual migration of your production sites.

ACTION REQUIRED:

You must ensure that you whitelist the NCR endpoints to prepare for the migration, or you will be at risk of losing 
access to your licensed NCR products that are being migrated to Microsoft Azure Public Cloud. See the full list of NUA01 Public Endpoints per Application &lt;[[https://ncr.quickbase.com/up/bqe6gx23b/g/rc8/ek/va/Command Center Pre-Production Firewall Requirements 4-12-21.pdf]]&gt;.

To access your migrated sites, you will need to download the Command Center client using the link and instructions &lt;[[https://ncr.quickbase.com/up/bqe6gx23b/g/rc8/ek/va/Command Center Pre-Production Firewall Requirements 4-12-21.pdf]]&gt; provided.

TIMING:
Migration window: April 20-22, 2021

WHAT 
TO EXPECT:

NCR has already deployed the CMCreqcheck.exe software to test and confirm that your site(s) can access the new endpoint. Sites identified for migration will have their CMC Agent upgraded prior to the targeted window noted above. 



	- 

If you have already upgraded your sites to CMC Agent 19.2.5 or higher, no additional action will be needed



Thank you for your continued cooperation in ensuring that you have whitelisted the NCR endpoints in advance to avoid any risk of losing access to your licensed NCR products once they are migrated to the Microsoft Azure Public Cloud. (See the full list of NUA01 Public Endpoints per Application.) Please contact NCR Customer Support if you have any questions or experience any issues, so we can assist you as quickly as possible.

We appreciate your partnership with NCR.
 
Thank you, 
NCR Hosted Services Team
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
