<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>2023 CSAT C1 Pre-Survey Customer Note.03-30-23 BNK CSAT C1 Pre-Survey Customer N</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>We want to hear from you</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear {{lead.First Name:default=Valued Customer}},
 
Continuously improving our customers’ experience remains one of NCR’s top priorities. That is why we take your feedback seriously and are asking you to complete the NCR Customer Satisfaction Survey 2023. You will receive a survey link from customer.success@feedback.ncr.com in the next few days. 

Based on the feedback received during the most recent survey, we have made investments and executed on internal improvements that have created positive progress in the overall experience of our customers. Some examples of these actions are:


	- 
We have deployed our innovative recycling technology, the 60 series products, which is live in three countries and ready to expand deployments this year. 

	- 
We are focused on expanding and simplifying solution offers to software as a service (SaaS).

	- 
We are improving process management to enhance solution quality and reduce the time needed for equipment installations, updates and field service delivery.

	- 
We are implementing training and process improvements to support faster resolutions, improve speed to answer, reduce onboard cycle time and achieve faster time to customer value.

	- 
We continue monitoring the payment processing platform’s performance to help ensure stability, speed and scalability.



We encourage you to participate in our NCR Customer Satisfaction Survey 2023 and share your open and honest feedback with us. Your feedback is essential for improving our offerings, so we can transform, connect and run your technology platforms. 

Thank you for being an NCR customer. I look forward to hearing from you.

Best regards,

Don Layden
President &amp; General Manager
NCR Banking
&lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
