<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>3-22-21 RET Monthly Emerald Newsletter.3-22-21 RET Monthly Emerald Newsletter</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>NCR Emerald Community Newsletter – March 2021</subject>
    <textOnly>March 2021
Welcome, 2021 Emerald Community Members!

The momentum for NCR Emerald &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/emerald]]&gt;, our next-gen retail commerce platform continues to build, and we have even bigger plans for this coming year.
 
Below are Emerald customers taking part in our community, representing a diverse and growing cross-section of the U.S. and Canadian grocery segment.
EMERALD ADVISORY BOARD MEMBERS
Lou Labenskyj
Chief Information Security Officer &amp; Sr. Director of Infrastructure &amp; Development

John D’Anna
EVP – Chief Strategic Officer

Steve Harper
IT Director – Market Format Systems

John Raab Jr.
Director Retail IT Services

Mike Tami
Vice President – Information Resources and Technologies

EMERALD COMMUNITY NEWS
- SAVE THE DATE! Our next virtual community meeting is on Wed. April 14, from 1-3:30 PM EST. Topics will include community updates, Emerald and Loyalty roadmap and Emerald retailers sharing their experiences. 
	- Emerald Community – We held our first Emerald Community meeting in October 2020, with 40 customers from six companies in virtual attendance. Topics included Innovation, Next Gen Store Architecture and Big Data.
	- Read our latest press release about Emerald and Big-Y &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/news/newsroom/news-releases/retail/big-y-embraces-the-new-retail-landscape-with-the-ncr-emerald-solution]]&gt;.
EMERALD PROGRESS: OVERALL SOLUTION
The Emerald team made excellent progress toward its 2020 solution goals and are now actively driving more ambitious plans for 2021, including:

NCR Analytics – In 2020, we launched a powerful, best-in-class data reporting and visualization tool using Google Looker. NCR Analytics comes bundled with your NCR Emerald subscription and training is included, free of charge. Download the training videos from the application’s help section in the upcoming release at the end of this quarter. Learn more about NCR Analytics &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/retail/analytics]]&gt; or read our blog article &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/blogs/retail/business-retail-analytics]]&gt;. 

NCR eCommerce powered by Freshop – NCR recently acquired Freshop &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/news/newsroom/news-releases/company/ncr-adds-freshop-e-commerce-solution-to-retails-leading-enterprise-pos-software-platform]]&gt;, seamlessly integrating online and mobile shopping with 
your in-store experience. Using the NCR business services platform, it’s ideal for U.S. and Canadian retailers who use Emerald. Learn more &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/retail/food-drug-mass-merchandise/ncr-ecommerce]]&gt; or read our blog article &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/blogs/retail/grocery-digital-transformation]]&gt;.
FOCUS AREAS FOR 2021
- Deliver market competitive product – Building out market competitive POS features is a top priority for the NCR Emerald product team.
	- Customer experience – The Emerald team is focused on continuous CX improvement to deliver a best-in-class experience for customers from sales, to implementation, to the ongoing product experience.
	- Scalability – Emerald teams across the business – PS, engineering, pre-sales, product and support – are growing to meet the demand of business growth.
	- Product innovation – We’ll continue to drive innovation around three key pillars: Unified CX, reporting &amp; analytics and hyper-personalization.
EMERALD RELEASES AND ROADMAP
Emerald POS official delivery 1.5.3 on Jan 13, 2021
Donations - Phase 2 of the donation functionality is complete. Emerald is now able to inform Connected Payments (CP) to turn on or off the Donation prompt. Emerald also prevents the Donation screen from being prompted during a return transaction.
Age Verification - Emerald was updated with the ability to force start any sales transaction with an Age Verification process by configuration.
Fuel - Various enhancements to support promotions on fuel purchases.
For more information, please contact your Professional Services project manager.
CUSTOMER SUCCESS STORY
Northgate Gonzalez Market &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/green-room/northgate-market]]&gt; is a regional, family-owned business with Emerald in 23 of their 41 stores with a plan to roll out in all stores in 2021. Read how they went from a legacy system to cloud-enabled POS platform in a record six months from plan to pilot store.
Watch the Northgate Market customer spotlight
THANK YOU!
 
The NCR Emerald Team
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
