<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>01-20-22 HOS Prospects Newsletter.Email 1</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>What Are Your Goals for the Year?</subject>
    <textOnly>New year, new goals, new beginnings. It’s time to hit the ground running. Yet action time can feel daunting, especially as time continues to race by while yesterday’s tomorrow is constantly on our tails. Just like you, we expect to achieve a lot. And we’re certain that the new year is giving us the much-needed motivation to conquer all. 

Yes, the pandemic continues to throw challenges at restaurants worldwide. But with the right strategies in place, you can improve how you address and meet these challenges – wholesale, or one-by-one. Additionally, now may be the time to put new tactics in place so you can adapt more promptly with incessant change. Either way, are you ready take on this year and beyond?
Best Tools for the Future of Your Restaurant
Over the past two years, the hospitality industry has adopted and honed the contactless experience. This capability is effective in keeping staff and customers safe and happy. And it’s become increasingly essential to maintaining the bottom line. While implementing these new practices and creating a new mode of business wasn’t and easy, it is indeed getting easier.
${CTAText2} &lt;[[${CTAURL}?${url-parameter}]]&gt;

Customer Wins: Jinya Ramen Bar
With more than 40 restaurants in North America, Jinya Ramen Bar needed to complement its footprint with exceptional online ordering capability. This was necessary to generate additional sales by expanding purchase and fulfillment options in ways that integrate seamlessly with existing operations. But it needed to get up and running quickly. Now, thanks to Aloha Essentials, JINYA has markedly increased customer satisfaction and decreased costs – at all 40+ locations.
${CTAText2} &lt;[[${CTAURL}?${url-parameter}]]&gt;
Aloha’s New Year’s Resolutions
- Eat healthier





	- Save money





	- Prep meals





	- Communicate more





	- Empower those around me
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 
${CTAText2} &lt;[[${CTAURL}?${url-parameter}]]&gt;

© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
