<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>2022 CSAT Pre-Survey Notes Cycle 2.09-29-22 RET CSAT Pre-Survey Note Cycle 2 EN.</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>We want to hear from you</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear {{lead.First Name:default=Valued Customer}},
 
Continuously improving our customers’ experience remains one of NCR’s top priorities. That is why we take your feedback seriously and are asking you to complete the NCR Customer Satisfaction Survey 2022. You will receive a survey link from customer.success@feedback.ncr.com &lt;[[mailto:customer.success@feedback.ncr.com]]&gt; in the next few days.
 
In the meantime, I am pleased to share that the actions we had taken on previous 
survey results created positive progress in our overall customer experience. For example, we structurally established clearer accountability with a single point of contact for our customers. We continued to advance our agile processes to help and improve how we develop and deliver our software. Additionally, we shared more details on our product lifecycle and areas of innovation as we worked closely with our customers to better understand their needs and build improved products to allow differentiation and growth.

I hope you will take our NCR Customer Satisfaction Survey 2022 and share your candid opinion with us. Your feedback is essential for improving our offerings, which can help you run your business better.
 
Thank you for being an NCR customer. I look forward to hearing from you.

Best regards,

David Wilkinson
President &amp; General Manager
NCR Retail
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
