<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>01-15-21 HOS Mobile Pay Azure Migration Notification.01-15-21 HOS Mobile Pay Azu</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Important Announcement</subject>
    <textOnly>Decommission of NCR Dallas Data Center for NCR Mobile Pay Customers Only
Dear Valued NCR Customer: 
 
NCR successfully went live with our hosted services in the Microsoft Azure Public Cloud last year. As such, NCR plans to permanently decommission our Dallas Data Center for NCR Mobile Pay. We are planning to move other applications out of the Dallas Data Center in the future as well and will keep you informed as we get closer to the date.
NCR Mobile Pay customers must ensure that you whitelist your NCR endpoints before January 27, 2021 or you will be at risk of losing access to your licensed NCR Mobile Pay products that are hosted in the Dallas Data Center 
(DFW05).

NCR migrated our hosted services to the Azure Dallas Cloud Platform last year to best support growing demand and to further modernize our infrastructure. We are very pleased with the performance of these services and are excited to see that many of our customers are experiencing these benefits:



	- A scalable solution that supports demand as their business grows
	- State-of-the-art technology that provides improved stability and reliability for optimal performance
	- Utilizes Cloud Platform resources to increase efficiency
	- Enhanced monitoring capabilities to proactively detect anomalies 
	- Ability to scale capacity based on workload 
	- Optimizes network performance
	- Optimizes storage and database performance
	- Improves application performance by identifying bottlenecks to ensure users have the best experience
	- Provides robust capabilities with modern intelligence tools that provide detailed environment and product metrics for analysis and reporting


ACTION REQUIRED:
Please adhere to the deadlines listed below to ensure your environment is not impacted when the data center is permanently decommissioned for NCR Mobile Pay. 



	- Wednesday, January 27, 2021 - NCR Mobile Pay clients must ensure they have their firewalls configured to the following whitelist additional IP addresses:


	- ncrpay.com 65.52.30.178
	- ncrpay.com/dash 65.52.30.178
	- platform.ncrpay.com 52.162.124.109
	- portal.ncrpay.com 52.162.124.109


	- Monday, February 1, 2021 at 2:00 AM – 6:00 AM ET – Dallas Data Center (DFW05) will be permanently decommissioned for NCR Mobile Pay


WHAT TO EXPECT:
During the maintenance window, the following actions will occur:



	- NCR Mobile Pay will be migrated during the maintenance window timeframe listed above
	- NCR Mobile Pay will not function during the maintenance window and will resume normal performance after the maintenance ends
	- Once these actions are completed, customers will be utilizing NCR Mobile Pay within the Azure Dallas Cloud Platform and they will no longer have access to the Dallas Data Center (DFW05) for NCR Mobile Pay


Thank you for your cooperation in ensuring that you whitelist your NCR endpoints before the designated dates listed above to avoid any risk of losing access to your licensed NCR Mobile Pay product hosted in the Dallas Data Center. Please contact NCR Customer Support at 800.792.5642 opt 2, or at support@alohaenterprise.com &lt;[[mailto:support@alohaenterprise.com]]&gt; if you have any questions or experience any issues, so we can assist you as quickly as possible.

We appreciate your partnership with NCR.
 
Thank you, 
NCR Hosted Services Team
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
