<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>12-09-22 HOS McDonald&apos;s Digital Menu Board Customer Comm 2.HOS McDonald&apos;s Digita</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Learn More About NCR’s Digital Menu Board Offerings</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear Valued Customer,

We are pleased to be your new Digital Menu Board hardware, hardware installation and Break Fix provider, beginning on January 1, 2023. Keep reading to review:



	- What&apos;s new!
	- Your resources
	- DMB Program Offerings (Installations and Break-Fix)
	- Your action items
	- How to contact us




What&apos;s new?

NCR will be your new Digital Menu Board hardware, hardware installation and Break Fix provider, beginning on January 1, 2023. This program is inclusive of supporting:



	- Indoor Digital Menu Boards installations
	- Break Fix options for:


	- Outdoor Digital Menu boards
	- Indoor Digital Menu Boards




The relationship between NCR and McDonald’s is longstanding and we are excited to partner with McDonald’s to provide these service offerings to accommodate your restaurant’s needs.



Your Resources

We want to take a moment to remind you that we have the necessary resources in place to help you manage your business more efficiently. The Account Executives, Customer Care team, Regional Break-Fix Support team and Installation and Project team leads are 100% dedicated to you.



	- Your NCR McDonald’s Account Team
- MyNCR-Consumer Portal


MyNCR helps you manage your business more efficiently. With MyNCR you can transact with NCR anytime, anyplace and the customized portal gives access to real-time information about your NCR account.

MyNCR capabilities include:



	- Online ordering

	- Hardware tracking information
	- View, Download and Print Invoice and Order Details
	- Electronically Dispute Invoices
	- Access Business Relevant NCR Applications in a
	- Self-Management of Application Users
NCR DMB Program Offerings

To learn about all NCR Digital Menu Board program offerings, please click here &lt;[[https://go.ncr.com/rs/605-BQY-740/images/111622_IntegratedMktg_HOSP_McDonalds_programofferings_customer_v1.pdf]]&gt;.



Your Action Steps:

Beginning on November 1, 2022, you can add 2023 coverage for your Digital Menu Boards when placing your new store, rebuild, or refresh order.



How to Contact UsAdditionally, to add your existing Digital Menu Boards to your Break Fix contract, please contact our dedicated Customer Care Team by calling (800) 
421-8230 between 8am – 8pm ET or via email at McDonalds.Orders@ncr.com. 



Sincerely,
Your McDonald’s NCR Account Team
&lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
