<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>This email is to inform MVP Customers that we will be launching a new customer portal – NCR Support Hub – that will replace ‘My Support Link – O360’ (NAYS) within MyNCR.</description>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>MVP Customer Com 08-13-22 HOS.09-13-22 MVP Customer Com HOSP V1</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Migration to NCR Support Hub Coming Soon</subject>
    <textOnly>Our NCR founder John H. Patterson once said, “treat every customer like they’re your only customer.” We take this to heart and have been working to improve the tools and applications used to deliver an amazing customer experience. 

Targeting September 27th, we will be launching a new customer portal – NCR Support Hub – that will replace ‘My Support Link – O360’ (NAYS) within MyNCR. 

Built leveraging Salesforce capabilities, NCR Support Hub will offer advanced features that will improve your support experience and reduce the amount of time spent managing your support cases.

 NCR Support Hub comes with:



	- Organized views for easy navigation across Cases (previously called Incidents), Work Orders (previously called Service Requests), and Accounts

	- Filterable/Downloadable reporting and dashboard capability for site performance

	- “Chatter” for adding notes and receiving updates from Support Agents

	- Subscriptions for Case Updates regarding Priority or Status changes

	- Easy Self-Serve Processes for case and work order creation

	- Permission Sets spanning View-Only, Logging Cases, and Creating Dispatches



As a current ‘My Support Link – O360’ user, we will be migrating you to the NCR Support Hub targeting September 27th. The NCR Support Hub will be your new platform for managing Cases (Incidents), Service Requests (Work Orders), and Reporting. 

With this transition, Pulse will ONLY be used for reporting and not for creating cases. You will have the option either to call Support (especially for urgent issues) or create tickets within NCR Support Hub.

Getting Ready for Migration

Moving to the NCR Support Hub will be easy for both you and your employees. A training manual and videos are now available on MyNCR under the ‘MyNCR Training Center’ to start getting familiar with the new user experience and advanced features coming with the NCR Support Hub.  You can also register now &lt;[[https://ncr.webex.com/ncr/onstage/g.php?MTID=e9cb2d6ad1b177d60a68891ec2e653310]]&gt; to attend a live demo and overview on September 21st from 11 AM – Noon ET. 

Transition date will be confirmed on the next communication the week of the 19th.

If you have additional questions, please reach out to your NCR Customer Success Manager or Account Executive.


Sincerely,

NCR</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
