<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>06-10-21 HOS eWeekly Newsletter.Feel the Pulse</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Feel the Pulse</subject>
    <textOnly>June 10, 2021
Feel the Pulse
Our exciting new video lets you demo Pulse-Real Time capabilities &lt;[[https://ncr.seismic.com/app?ContentId=45a321df-d9f0-41e0-9327-16de3b5623b6#/doccenter/8ef384b5-b3bb-424b-823f-729a41e48366/doc/%252Fdd196e06dc-3738-d46d-9523-f4780ed862c3%252Flfce8d2444-4b15-4795-9adb-b5a576666db6//?mode=view&amp;parentPath=sessionStorage]]&gt; to your customers, showing them the mobile cloud reporting, alerts, and 
analytics tool they can use to run their business from any Android or Apple mobile device. All the Information that’s needed is conveniently at their fingertips in the Pulse app to track and monitor everything from up-to-the-minute sales information to notification alerts for issues that require their attention. Access the Pulse demo and other resources on Seismic &lt;[[https://ncr.seismic.com/Link/Content/DC3yGjRfDZ4EGTJxbeO1Yjtg]]&gt;.
Leveraging Demos for Sweeter Deals
In the last issue of eWeekly, we introduced our new Virtual Solution Experience (VSE) &lt;[[https://ncr.quickbase.com/up/bqe6gx23b/g/rdi/ek/va/VSE FINAL 5-18-21.pdf]]&gt;, a dynamic Hospitality sales tool that lets you visually 
demonstrate to customers in a virtual environment how different personas interact with NCR technology in the restaurant. Now, in our Lokahi podcast &lt;[[https://ncr.seismic.com/Link/Content/DCakd7e_xK1EmUjIYZUKSTSw]]&gt; Scott Wakeley discusses the power of how you can leverage demos to shape your sales pitch and address specific business challenges.
${CTAText2} &lt;[[${CTAURL}?${url-parameter}]]&gt;
Knowledge is Power
It’s important that customers always have the information they need to keep their business running smoothly. The best way to stay informed about Aloha is to subscribe to the Aloha Status Page &lt;[[https://status.aloha.ncr.com/]]&gt;. We need your help in ensuring all your customers subscribe to this free service to minimize support calls that can be addressed easily via the Aloha status alerts that customers receive via text, email, or RSS feed. Please encourage all your customers to sign up to receive the Aloha status notifications.
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
