<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Channel Newsletter 10.9.20.10-09-20 HOS eWeekly Channel Newsletter Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>eWeekly – Discontinuation Notice - Accuview</subject>
    <textOnly>October 9, 2020
Discontinuation Notice – Accuview Order Confirmation Display Systems
The Accuview Order Confirmation product and associated items will be discontinued and replaced with NCR Vitalcast, the large format digital menu board product. 

TIMING


	- 
Final forecasts due November 27, 2020

	- 
Final Orders (End of Sales) - May 28, 2021

	- 
Final shipments planned - December 31, 2021

	- 
End of Support and Service - December 31, 2026



The decision to End of Life Accuview is due to declining sales as markets have been moving to large format digital menu boards with order confirmation, as well as some of the parts associated with Accuview are becoming obsolete and would require design modifications in order to continue the product. For a complete list of the products affected click here &lt;[[https://ncr.quickbase.com/up/bqe6gx23b/g/rbk/ek/va/NCRTDS Accuview Discontinuation Notice V2 TL Edits 10-1-2020.pdf]]&gt;.

What is NCR Pulse and how and how are top restaurants using it?

NCR Pulse Real-Time is an instantaneous mobile cloud reporting, alerts and analytics tool that restaurant owners and their management teams use to run their business from their mobile device, no matter where they are. With the app, they gain easy access to real-time insights pulled directly from their Aloha POS system, helping them save time and money. 

The reports are simple to navigate with a modern UI, making it easy to spot notifications, outliers, and sales to help isolate and address issues with guests and keep them happy. Read more. &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/blogs/restaurants/what-is-ncr-pulse-and-how-are-top-restaurants-using-it]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
