<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>11-30-22 HOS McDonald&apos;s Eproduction Email.HOS McDonalds Eproduction</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Get your site ready your NCR professional Eproduction installation</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear Valued Customer, 
 
You have received, or will soon be receiving your hardware for your NCR professional Eproduction installation. We are currently working on getting an installation date scheduled for your site(s).

Starting today, we will need you and your team to begin working on and completing the required site readiness ahead of your installation date.
 
The site readiness items that each Owner Operator is required to complete BEFORE NCR arrives for 
an Eproduction installation are:



	- Have the correct twist lock receptacles installed to power any KVS controller or monitor needed for the installation
	- Have any stainless hood chase mounts, purchased from your KES, installed, and have the mounting brackets that come with them ready on the day of your installation if you are using this option
	- If you need a threaded rod kit to hang a monitor (typically a bake monitor) have that threaded rod installed ahead of your installation as NCR does not install threaded rods


(For any site(s) that have not yet received hardware, it should arrive 2 weeks ahead of your scheduled installation. If you ordered threaded rods they will be included in that shipment) 
 
We have also provided a site readiness checklist &lt;[[https://go.ncr.com/rs/605-BQY-740/images/111122_IntegratedMktg_HOSP_McDonalds_Eproduction_v1.pdf]]&gt; to help with the process.

Ahead of the scheduled installation, NCR will call you to verify site readiness. If a site does not verify site readiness the scheduled installation will be aborted. Note: An abort fee will be applied in this case. 

Additionally, if site readiness is verified but we come to find that, on installation day, the site is not 100% ready per the site readiness checklist, we will install what we can but will have to return at a later date in Q1 2023. Note: A revisit is a billable charge. 

Working together, we can complete your installation this year. Thank you for your collaboration with this project and for your continued partnership. 

Thank you, 

NCR Team
&lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
