<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>12-21-21 BNK Apache Log4J Vulnerability Communication.Email 1</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>An important update from NCR Banking</subject>
    <textOnly>NCR Software Update – Apache Log4j vulnerability

 As a trusted partner, we want to ensure you have the most current 
information on a series of vulnerabilities discovered within Apache Log4j.


	- 
CVE-2021-44228: https://nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2021-44228 &lt;[[https://nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2021-44228]]&gt;

	- 
CVE-2021-45046: https://nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2021-45046 &lt;[[https://nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2021-45046]]&gt;

	- 
CVE-2021-45105: https://nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2021-45105 &lt;[[https://nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2021-45105]]&gt;



Apache Log4j 2 is an industry-wide very commonly used Java library, which many Java applications and server software use for logging. Select NCR Banking software products make use of the Log4j 2 library.

CVE-2021-44228 &amp; CVE-2021-45046 
Mitigations have been identified and executed to prevent the exploitation of CVE-2021-44228 &amp; CVE-2021-45046 vulnerabilities. Specifically, NCR has assessed its usage of the Log4j 2 library and identified remediation actions for certain NCR Banking products and has enacted those within its Managed Services SaaS and hosted environments. 

CVE-2021-45105
Vulnerability CVE-2021-45105 was originally disclosed on 18th December. NCR is currently assessing this vulnerability. NCR is also working with our vendors and partners to conduct similar activities to reduce the potential issue footprint, while minimizing impact to our customers.

How are my NCR products impacted and what is the recommended mitigation?
This is the current list of identified solutions that are impacted by the Log4j2 vulnerabilities:
Product


Versions Impacted




Passport (Server only)


3.15 and later




Transaction Gateway


All 4.x and 3.4.x WST + TM, LOW 4.3.0




Vision


Vision 4.13 and later




Authentic


4.2.00 and later




Terminal Handler


V 1.1




Cash Management


9.09 - 9.12




Archive


WebView 6.2.0 &amp; 6.2.1




Clear


6.01.00 and later




Inetco Insight


7.3, 7.4




Solidcore (EPO)


ePolicy Orchestrator (ePOS) 5.10 CU 11
What should I do if I run any of these solutions?
The impact of these vulnerabilities is most significant when the solution is deployed as a public internet-facing version of our application. Most of NCR’s affected software is deployed in back-office / internal systems that are not accessible from the public internet reducing the risk. Regardless, NCR recommend that customers should remediate these internal systems as well.

If you are accessing these solutions either through Managed Services or SaaS, there is no action required.

If you are operating any of these solutions on premise, NCR advises that you urgently contact NCR through your normal support channel. NCR will provide guidance on the remediation actions that will address this matter.

Updates on the Apache Log4j vulnerabilities and the impact to NCR banking products can be found at www.ncr.com/banking/Log4j &lt;[[http://www.ncr.com/banking/Log4j]]&gt;. If you have any questions, please contact your NCR representative.

Sincerely,

NCR Banking Team
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
