<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Gated Content: 2021_04_RET_SCOGeneral Webinar 3 Infographic Emails.11-23-21 RET</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Expert tips to get your self-checkouts ready for peak period</subject>
    <textOnly>November 2021
Prepping Your Self-Checkout for Peak Period
Our self-checkout technical experts want to share some tips that will help your self-checkouts be “peak period” ready, delivering great customer experiences while making the checkout 
shift easy on your associates.

Staffing considerations - Turn your self-checkouts into assisted lanes for busy periods

A trained cashier is a lot faster at itemizing and scanning as compared to an average shopper at self-checkout. So, if you want to increase throughput and potential capacity quickly and easily at your front end, one way to do that is by staffing a self-checkout lane. During peak times if you see a line building up at your self-checkout area here is how you can turn that into an assisted lane to increase throughput:
1.Select Assistance Mode -&gt; 2.Select Store Login -&gt; 3.Log in as associate -&gt; 4.Select Systems Functions -&gt; 5.Select Mode of Operations -&gt; 6.Select Store Assistant Mode -&gt; 7.The Orange outline indicates associate mode -&gt; 8.Start scanning

While itemization, scanning and 
bagging is done by cahiers, they can still have the customer do all the tendering themselves. If you have a convertible unit it automatically goes into attendant mode when you swap the unit over.

Lane maintenance – Keep your lanes running

Make sure your lanes have everything from bags to receipt paper for transactions to run smoothly. In addition to that, if some errors pop up during transactions, the NCR Self-checkout has an intuitive error handling process that attendants can use. The self-checkout presents the attendant with exactly what error has occurred, followed by the process steps to resolve along with corresponding photos. So, let&apos;s say there are four process steps to resolve an error. There will be four corresponding pictures, one with each step that shows the attendant, not just a verbal cue of how to resolve but also the visual. For example, if the attendant is not sure where the bill acceptor is, there will be an arrow is pointing to it in picture. 
In addition to the self-help guide on the self-checkout itself, NCR also provides this basic troubleshooting guide &lt;[[https://go.ncr.com/rs/605-BQY-740/images/Generic R6 Trouble Shooting v1_July 2021.pdf]]&gt;. Share this with your store associates so they have it handy.

Reduce friction – Review reports to identify areas for improvement
 
Select “Reporting” from the store authorization screen and you will be able to run a range of reports that will allow you to identify top issues that a lane has had over a period, for example the last two weeks.
Weight Mismatch Report – NCR self-checkout monitors anytime an item is set down in the bagging area or security scale area where the recorded 
weight of the item does not match what&apos;s in your weight learning database. With this visibility you can adjust the weight thresholds and reduce interventions.

Unknown Items Report – Keeps track of every single item that has been scanned over the last seven days and ranks from most scanned to least scanned. It then identifies the UPCs that are generating unknown items, which allows retailers to add the identified items to their price book file, and reduce unknown item intervention.

Device Errors Report - This report identifies all the areas within the self-checkout lane that have experienced some sort of error or issue over the 
previous seven days. It&apos;s going to put a count next to each issue providing a good indicator of issues that need to be resolved. With this information the NCR technician can come prepared and address the issue quickly.

Attendant Entry Report – This report identifies the items that are consistently having troublesome barcodes while scanning, where the attendant is having to enter the UPC. Once the items are identified you can either inform the supplier, fix the issue at the store, or print those barcodes and keep it next to the RAP station or the self-checkout to help speed up the entry of those items. 

Assistance Report – These reports help store managers to review things like average intervention 
resolution times for each lane over a period, average transaction times etc. It helps them to investigate why a certain attendant is taking long to respond to, and clear interventions, looking into things like whether they are approving the interventions at the Self-checkout or through the RAP station. If the report shows that tender time is too long across transactions, the store manager can investigate the main bottlenecks, and address them to speed up the checkout process.

Cash Management Tips.
 
Make sure you are not having to replenish cash multiple times a day. If you are observing that you are having to replenish a certain note or coin denominator more than once a day, consider upping the number of cash / coin denominator you are running out of. If you have a four-note recycler versus six-note recycler and you are not able to add, perhaps you need to consider changing the configuration of the recyclers to accommodate the number of bills you need to house to reduce number of refills.
Hope these tips help you deliver better in-store checkout experiences during the busy holiday season. Please reach out to your Account Executive if you need help or have questions
 
Anitha Gopinathan &lt;mailto:anitha.gopinathan@ncr.com&gt;

NCR Fastlane 
Product Marketing Manager
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
