<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>12-08-21 HOS Prospects Newsletter.Subject Line Test</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>What’s on Your Wish List?</subject>
    <textOnly>It’s a magical time of year: hot chocolate, festive cocktails, and bright lights adorning neighborhoods. Restaurants around the country have brought out their patio heaters and are seeing new, as well as familiar faces as holiday travelers arrive from out of town.     

This time of year also presents a few challenges for you restaurant owners and managers. We’ve got a guess or two on what’s on your wish list for this holiday season. With new strategies in place, a few tips, and a feel-good story, you’ll be ready for one of the most exciting times of the year.
Marketing your restaurant during the holidays
From last minute holiday shopping to reuniting with loved ones, your customers are booked and busy. But that doesn’t mean you can’t entice them to a meal or two at your restaurant.
${CTAText2} &lt;[[${CTAURL}?${url-parameter}]]&gt;
Share on  &lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/283156830259/posts/10160187881040260]]&gt;  &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation/status/1460261335061696515]]&gt;   &lt;[[https://www.linkedin.com/feed/update/urn:li:activity:6866027031478468608/]]&gt;
Three Things to Ask Your Technology Partner
The future of technology-enabled restaurants is brighter than ever as businesses welcome back on-premises diners in a new normal. But before you can start transforming your restaurant, consider these three things to ask from your technology partner.
${CTAText2} &lt;[[${CTAURL}?${url-parameter}]]&gt;
Customer Wins: Waffle House
Waffle House, the “breakfast-all-day” chain, lost internet connection on Christmas Day last year – a potential operational disaster. They faced a loss of online orders, limited offline transactions, and potentially lost revenue-not to mention the risk of disappointing their holiday customers. So, they called us, NCR.
${CTAText2} &lt;[[${CTAURL}?${url-parameter}]]&gt;
Share on   &lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/283156830259/posts/10159950430310260]]&gt;   &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation/status/1414585368675078145]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://www.linkedin.com/feed/update/urn:li:activity:6820351060540973056/]]&gt;
Aloha’s Kitchen
Looking for a treat to add to your holiday menu? We’ve got you covered! Try out these loaded cookie bars to satisfy everyone’s sweet tooth. 

½ (1 stick) cup unsalted butter
1 egg
1 cup light brown sugar 
1 tablespoon vanilla extract
1 cup all-purpose flour
10 Oreo cookies, shopped
½ cup mini M&amp;M’s
${CTAText2} &lt;[[${CTAURL}?${url-parameter}]]&gt;
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
