<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>07-18-22 RET Monthly Emerald Newsletter.07-dd-22 RET Monthly Emerald Newsletter</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>NCR Emerald Community Newsletter – July 2022</subject>
    <textOnly>July 2022
Dear Emerald Community Members,
 
The first half of 2022 has come and gone, in what feels like the blink of an eye! The second half of 2022 looks to be just as busy, if not more. Keeping this productive pace wouldn’t be possible without your continued partnership.
ADVISORY BOARD &amp; EMERALD COMMUNITY UPDATES
Our next Emerald Community Meeting is now scheduled for July 28th at 11 AM EST and we are thrilled to welcome our Advisory Board to attend in-person at our Atlanta headquarters.
 
Agenda topics include:

Retailer Presentations on Deployment Approach
NCR Product Updates (NCR Analytics, Pocket Office &amp; Emerald)
Support Strategy &amp; Structure
We look forward to speaking with you all in just a few weeks!
EMERALD RELEASES AND ROADMAP
The next Emerald Release is 1.7.1. Here is a summary of what it includes – you’ll hear more about this in our Emerald Community Meeting at the end of the month!
REF 488288: L&amp;P: Multi 
Cashing of Coupons and Vouchers
Ref 529287: Tender: Coin Dispenser – 
Add Support for Payout and Tender Exchange
REF 497562: L&amp;P: Display Top Shopper 
Mark and Shopper Points on POS (UE)
REF 524971: L&amp;P: Emerald to Enhance the 
MFR Promotions Behavior on Receipts
REF 524971: L&amp;P: Add the Ability to 
Handle and Print a Coupon Issued by the PE (UE)/deferred promotions
REF 519722: L&amp;P: Emerald to Enhance the 
Simple Promotion by Getting the Indicator from the PE (AMS &amp; LPRO)
REF 485973: POS: Beep Sound when a Weight 
Item is Added to the Transaction after it was Scaled
REF 491691: Sale: Add Beep Sound when Age Verification is Waiting for DL Scan &amp; Lock Scanner
REF 516477: Fuel: Scan Coupon at the Pump 
Terminal and Receive Cents off Gallon Discount Promotion
REF 514100: Online Purchase Profiles: 
Ability to Prohibit an Attempt to Request Activation of a Gift Card More than Once
REF 484063: Security: add the ability to 
Configure Length for Strong Password
REF 496210: Tender Check, EPS (CP) 
Authorization: Handle Shopper ID Details
REF 494953: Tender: Ability to Restrict 
the Tenders that can Pay for a Certain
REF 520645: Operations: Support Partial 
Store Upgrade
RETAILER UPDATES
-Emerald 1.6.304 in production stores
-Upgrade Production stores June 27th Emerald 1.6.307
- AJ’s Pilot scheduled for July 12
- Food City scheduled for July 19
Emerald SCO pilot – TBD: Roll out 
targeting end of Q3 2022 starting with AJ’s


-Emerald Pilot 1.6.4
-One lane installation in production
-Full store conversion (Pilot date) 7/11/22
-three stores are now live on Emerald and are developing a rollout plan
-Next targeted release is Emerald 1.6.308 








-UAT in progress
-Targeting Liquor Pilot July 2022
-Targeting Fuel Pilot Aug 2022
- Emerald 1.6.403 Fuel Pilot upgrade and config 1.2.2 
 







 
-Plan to upgrade to AMS 7.15, Emerald 1.7.1 and corresponding version of SCO.
-Martin’s banner rollout of Emerald complete- POS, SCO, Fuel, RX. (21 stores &amp; 8 gas stations)
-All stores upgraded to AMS 7.14
-Emerald Upgrades in progress from Emerald 1.5.216 to 1.6.304- 15 stores completed. 
Corporate Stores 
Build &amp; Test in Progress stores and 29 gas stations planned 
-2022 Roll Out - 38 stores and 15 gas stations
-Deployed 1,065 lanes out of 1,340; remaining 275 will be rolled out by end of June, completing the total of 171 stores.
-Keep Current Services with NCR is now being discussed
- Integration with Aurus Payments and Quotient electronic coupons
-Pilot planned for Aug 2022 with Emerald 1.6.4x and AMS 7.14
-UAT lab testing of Emerald 1.6.401 and AMS 7.14
NCR TEAM MEMBER HIGHLIGHTS
At the recommendation of our Advisory Board, we will recognize team members from both NCR and client who have done outstanding work on the Emerald solution, pilots and rollouts.
Product
Julio Echeverria is a product manager and has been with NCR since 2018 in various roles, including being a product owner for the Business Services team. He joined Emerald last year to support roadmap definition &amp; delivery. Since the beginning of the year, Julio&apos;s jumped into looking across customers identifying common areas of opportunity to deliver improvements. In particular, he&apos;s been leading efforts to improve testing &amp; solution stabilization for Emerald payments flows. We know there&apos;s nothing more critical than being able to successfully take payment transactions in the retail and we appreciate Julio&apos;s diligence in this space! Look for more improvements coming soon.
Professional Services
Oanh Nguen is an Emerald Technical Consultant that has been with NCR for 11 years. She previously worked on StoreLine and Fuel projects as a Support Analyst, Technical Consultant and Product Specialist. Oanh has amazing technical knowledge and understanding of a variety of NCR Products. She also has detailed and rare knowledge of Operational Flows in different lines of Business. She is a very quick learner that can quickly and easily grasp technical approaches in different areas and successfully implement it in customer project.
With some of you reaching your Emerald rollout completion and most of you entering your active Pilot, it’s more important than ever for us to maintain our synergy. Let’s keep the momentum!
THANK YOU!

Team Emerald
We currently have these Emerald customers in our Community, representing a diverse and growing cross-section of the U.S. and Canadian grocery segment.
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
