<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>11-19-20 HOS eWeekly Channel Newsletter.11-19-20 HOS eWeekly Channel Newsletter</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>eWeekly – Did You Miss It?</subject>
    <textOnly>November 19, 2020
NCR TechFest2020 - Virtual Learning at Its Best
We are very excited about the level of participation in the NCR TechFest 2020 virtual event on November 10 -13, 2020. If you were not among the more than 300 attendees who attended TechFest2020, then you missed an incredible experience. 

Some of the best speakers from NCR, including leaders across the company and highly knowledgeable Product Managers, were on hand to deliver nearly 30 sessions on 15 distinct topics. Sessions covered everything from Aloha upgrade improvements to wireless implementation best practices to new features in contactless dine-in to Aloha payments best practices to Silver implementations, and so much more. 

While it may sound like it was all work and no play, it wasn’t all just bits and bytes. We managed to carve out some time to include a little bit of fun with daily quizzes and hackathon competitions. The winners not only earned bragging rights until next year’s event, but they also won some awesome prizes -- Apple AirPods, portable fire pits, Omaha Steaks, Yeti coolers and tumblers, portable Bose speakers, and portable car battery chargers. 

Please join us in congratulating the TechFest2020 competition winners &lt;[[https://on.lenos.com/ncr/TechFest-2020/Content/Winners]]&gt; who did an amazing job! If you missed TechFest2020, no worries. We’ll share the recordings of the sessions in this newsletter in the coming weeks.
Reshaping the Guest Experience Webinar
NCR hosted another successful customer webinar – Reshaping the Guest Experience – on November 10th. Jessica Bryant, Vice President of NCR Hospitality Marketing, presented an informative session in which she outlined three important strategies - customer re-engagement, safe experiences, and restaurant redesign – that restaurant operators are concentrating their efforts on to address shifting guest expectations and preferences. If you or your customers were unable to attend, listen to the recording of this webinar &lt;[[https://urldefense.com/v3/__https:/u4788348.ct.sendgrid.net/ls/click?upn=RA5k1pJxRyOPl6cXG2PRncCySQwgddNr4Hrs0goms-2BQHy6pXVc-2F7Qx1NTgX-2B2BrISUHU-2FLddVpYFPAdIRFKFPIAQPjVHeNFjFwchQRxMnb4UG-2BmBSDA1-2F8qbUmKxKKDZzv4re-2F8lOH8aQEnyvuHfWvK4FI2FXmr4MF-2BOOu2s6YlV8i5omZlqGiUrLVHvwn-2BXHy-2FUuKr5olJieeHZBGBlP74VmNZvWbkbyHFs-2FnXNRB2ifPW9nPKMmWA-2BY6YIBtAhvQTG_Fsz1v24zetQhy3kbmRoizNYOScpB31HkdDagYzKHxC-2FxcDEMpNOSi6VufzraLSN9VQmTD7T9P9RBdhAubyobeXJUrXsACE1ph-2BARpW102bg8Lgm-2FpS55ZM-2B8wJNY0xlprmMvUYpAVeGYkmWq-2FqWu-2FvMTfg88z73MZvo3a9RHiN8gFst5mQQ5KgcBhgy7Yi7SfuB0nyiNpvVaGYIqjGqSQoQ9s7ldc8K-2FSvAXqcJnDo1BoVc3-2B7uh7Tjp31NPJQLKWM8w72A121O6pI9lQjGCjoK6WMOxsRYvsMiiEWJuw3N-2B7JP-2FqRYVVNCRwGCFMeBr__;!!In4Qlw!4_Fw1xeDfNF4KOAd8qY4TI56HVfV6jBjyHgEKEhKD3WwU5oo4xlYDnM2Pe8EEMTZ$]]&gt; at your convenience. Stay tuned for information about additional webinars we’ll offer in 2021.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
