<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>10-25-22 Channel Partner TCR Note.Email 1</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Transform, connect and run our customers’ technology platforms</subject>
    <textOnly>Transform, connect and run our customers’ technology 
platforms
Dear Valued Channel Partners,
 
At NCR Corporation, we’re committed to working with you to help our shared customers transform, connect and run their technology platforms. These customers — whether in the banking, hospitality or retail industries — are faced with significant changes and challenges driven by trends in consumer preferences, economic uncertainties and more. Watch this brief video &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WEYiHOO_1HE]]&gt; on our strategy for navigating this evolution together through continuous innovation, providing a consistent experience and simplifying operations.
Transform, connect and run: What does it mean?
Now more than ever, our customers need to serve consumers where, when and how they want. They need actionable insights through data and access to the platform economy. And they need to be equipped to handle business disruptors and large-scale global and industry trends. NCR’s combination of enablement and execution capabilities helps achieve that through these strategic objectives:
Transform | Interpreting data and applying 
best practices, deep industry expertise, and continuous innovation to solve problems and keep customers at the forefront of their industries.
Connect | NCR Platforms connect systems 
and endpoints to provide consumers with a consistent experience, using an approach that allows for accelerated innovation and third-party integration.
Run | We provide tech solutions that 
simplify running the entire operation, removing complexity by consolidating functions with one strategic partner — freeing up time to focus on consumers.
What’s next?
In the coming months, you’ll be seeing more detail on how we’re executing our strategy. In January 2023, we look forward to the return of our annual NCR Global Channel Sales Kickoff to prepare us for success in the coming year. We’re excited to reconnect as a global channel partner community, and during the kickoff, you’ll hear more about how we can bring transform, connect and run to life and continue supporting our shared customers. 

We’ve also given the NCR brand a refresh to accompany this strategy and messaging — please download our new NCR Partner Network brand guidelines &lt;[[https://ncr.seismic.com/Link/Content/DCG29DM4BpfTm8W2mQWm46cgV2h3]]&gt; and logos &lt;[[https://ncr.seismic.com/Link/Folder/DC86e796]]&gt; for your team’s use. You’ll see additional branded materials coming out in the coming weeks, featuring our new look and feel. 

In the meantime, if you’d like to amplify this strategy with customers, please feel free to share our LinkedIn post &lt;[[https://www.linkedin.com/posts/ncr-corporation_ncr-brand-statement-activity-6971127388965404672-b8FP?utm_source=share&amp;utm_medium=member_desktophttps://www.linkedin.com/posts/ncr-corporation_ncr-brand-statement-activity-6971127388965404672-b8FP?utm_source=share&amp;utm_medium=member_desktop]]&gt; introducing our message and video.
Questions?
If you have any questions or need additional information, please reach out to your channel account manager or email ChannelSales.NCR@ncr.com. We look forward to sharing more details with you and appreciate your continued commitment and collaboration.

Best regards,
The NCR Partner Network Team
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
