<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>2021 CSAT Survey Results Notes.09-13-21 CSAT HOS Survey Results Note EN.EN Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>We are acting on your feedback</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear {{lead.First Name:default=Valued Customer}},
 
Thank you again to everyone who participated in our 2021 NCR 
Customer Satisfaction Survey. Your insights are a crucial part of how we learn, grow and make simple possible for you. 

I am excited to share that we saw continued improvement in the survey results, particularly in our overall Net Promoter Score (NPS), and in the number of customers who believe NCR provides good value. 

At the same time, we know that we can continue to improve. Based on your responses to the survey, we are focusing on taking action in the following areas:



	- Reducing effort and simplifying: You highlighted opportunities within our organization that could be simplified or made easier to work with. To address these concerns, we:


	- Are leading transformational projects with several of our functional teams with the specific mandate to perform their work from the lens of what our customers need from us first.
	- Launched an employee recognition program that rewards associates who identify ways to improve our customers’ experience or prevent negative experiences.
	- Added a Customer Experience Advocate position, whose primary objective is to be the voice of our customers and to help us drive a customer-centric organization.






	- Quality improvement and error reduction: You told us that we still have work to do when it comes to making Aloha easier to work with and reducing errors in billing. We agree, and have:


	- Launched multiple workstreams focused on addressing critical software issues, such as enhanced support incident trend analysis and root cause identification, Configuration Center simplification, and system integration testing improvement.
	- Launched root cause analysis projects in billing to identify and drive immediate enhancements while also prioritizing transformational improvement projects targeting error reduction through Q4.
	- Launched a customer support pod structure in Q1 that is allowing our team to become more familiar with our customers resulting in higher first call resolution, shorter wait times and overall better support experiences; as this structure continues to build proficiency, we expect additional 
improvements.




Our goal is to make significant improvements in these key areas over the next several quarters, making it easier to do business with NCR. Moreover, by leveraging a customer-centric, “outside-in” mindset throughout our business, we will continue to bring innovations that not only help overcome hardships like the COVID-19 pandemic but, also importantly, create new opportunities for our customers to compete and win in the market. We look forward to hearing from you about how we are doing. 
 
As always, thank you for sharing your insights and for being an NCR customer. 

Warmest regards,

Dirk Izzo
President and General Manager, NCR Hospitality

Sandy Preizler
SVP, Hospitality Global Sales
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
