<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>05-13-21 HOS eWeekly Newsletter.NCR Payments Promotion</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>NCR Payments Promotion</subject>
    <textOnly>May 13, 2021
NCR Payment Solutions Promotional Offer
In response to our channel partner’s request to lower the barrier of entry for customers who need an EMV contactless payment solution, NCR is offering a special promotion for up to two Equinox Luxe 6200 tethered devices per site for customers who 
sign up for NCR Payment Solutions. Learn more details about this promotional offer and access the customer-facing flyer &lt;[[https://ncr.quickbase.com/up/bqe6gx23b/g/rde/ek/va/042121_ProductMktg_HOSP_PaymentSolutionsPromoFlyer_PDF (1).pdf]]&gt; that you can send to your customers.
${CTAText2} &lt;[[${CTAURL}?${url-parameter}]]&gt;
NCR Aloha / Sysco Referral Program
NCR recently signed a new Strategic Referral Program with Sysco Foods. We’re excited about this program and expect it to be one of our most reliable sources for quality Aloha leads. Check out some of the referral program’s highlights in the image below. For more details about the Sysco Referral program, click here &lt;[[https://ncr.quickbase.com/up/bqe6gx23b/g/rdf/ek/va/Sysco Deck for Channel Partners 4.23.21.pdf]]&gt;.
POSaaS Promotion in Action
As a reminder, the March Madness promotion is still available. Continue to work hard with POSaaS customers to modernize their solutions to Aloha Essentials and give them the best tools they need to succeed! If you have questions about the program, review the details of the promotion or reach out to your Channel Account Manager.
${CTAText2} &lt;[[${CTAURL}?${url-parameter}]]&gt;
Aloha Updates ICYMI
In case you missed it, we’ve been asking channel partners to promote the Aloha Status page with your customers -- not just because it’s really cool – it saves time for both you and your customers to receive text message alerts whenever needed. If you haven’t already done so, please encourage all your customers to sign-up today for the Aloha Status Page &lt;[[https://status.aloha.ncr.com/]]&gt; to receive updates about the health and performance of our software. It’s easy and it’s free, so it just doesn’t get any better than that!
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
