<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>12-21-20 HOS Aloha SMB December Newsletter.12-21-20 HOS Aloha SMB December Newsl</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Boost your bottom line with contactless payments</subject>
    <textOnly>Whether it’s dine-in, take out, or curbside delivery, restaurant guests simply don’t want to touch anything that has been handled by anyone else – menus, check presenters, pens, or payment devices. 

To truly help your guests feel more comfortable, the entire experience needs to be contactless. If you are not already offering contactless payments as part of your strategy, it’s easy to deploy and can go a long way in improving efficiency, elevating guests’ experiences, and driving additional revenue for your restaurant.
Innovative ways for delivering contactless payments
Accept payments securely for phone orders
Taking credit card information over the phone for pick-up orders exposes both you and your customers to risk. You can securely process payments without ever verbally exchanging the customer’s credit card information using NCR Mobile Pay. Simply give the customer a 6-digit code during the call and instruct them to pay their check at ncrpay.com using the code provided. When the customer arrives to pick up their order, it’s already been paid for, so they can quickly be on their way. It’s that easy. Learn More &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/restaurants/mobile-pay?utm_source=Email&amp;utm_medium=Other&amp;utm_campaign=&amp;utm_content=Newsletter&amp;utm_industry=hospitality&amp;utm_sub-industry=Restaurants]]&gt;
Text to pay via Mobile Pay
NCR is delivering even more innovation to support contactless payments with text-to-pay, coming in 2021. This new NCR Mobile Pay capability enables you to text the customer a mobile pay code with a link to conveniently pay their check on ncrpay.com. You can look forward to receiving more details about text-to-pay as we get closer to the launch date in late January. In the meantime, please contact your NCR Account Manager if you’re interested in learning more about NCR Mobile Pay text to pay now.
Training opportunities to help you run your business

Get the most out of all the capabilities that are currently available at your disposal with NCR. You can take advantage of the rich offerings of training, webinars, videos, and other resources available online &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/restaurants/aloha-pos-training]]&gt;. Bookmark this page for easy access to updated content in the future.
Check out the training videos for the products below
Aloha POS &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/restaurants/aloha-pos-training]]&gt; Aloha Kitchen &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ao-AESVRAEQ]]&gt;Aloha Online Ordering &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLpEgSRC5pj_UVIPeShpvDLZT5C3EKbWiq]]&gt;
Additional resources about creating contactless experiences
Integrating mobile payments into the restaurant experience &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/blogs/restaurants/things-to-consider-when-integrating-mobile-payments-into-your-restaurant]]&gt;
Promoting pay at table to customers &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/blogs/restaurants/how-to-communicate-pay-at-table-options-to-your-customers]]&gt;
How a mobile app doubles as contactless payment and delivery &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/blogs/restaurants/how-a-chicago-restaurants-mobile-app-doubles-as-contactless-payment-and-delivery]]&gt;
Contactless is the new comfort &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/blogs/restaurants/contactless-is-the-new-comfort-how-touchless-technology-keeps-restaurant-brands-connected-to-customers]]&gt;
Four 
tips for making contactless delivery work for your restaurant &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/blogs/restaurants/contactless-food-delivery]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
