<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>02-28-22 RET Monthly Emerald Newsletter.02-28-22 RET Monthly Emerald Newsletter</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>NCR Emerald Community Newsletter – February 2022</subject>
    <textOnly>February 2022
Dear Emerald Community Members,
 
Here’s to a new year with big plans! Thanks for the continued partnership in 2022 – we look forward to seeing more of you in person throughout the year.
EMERALD COMMUNITY UPDATES
The NCR Emerald Community team hit the ground running this year and you each should have seen an invite come through for our first Emerald Community Meeting of 2022: March 2nd from 12:30 – 3:30 PM EST. Topics currently on our agenda include:



	- 2022 Roadmap &amp; Release Content
	- Retailer Presentations


	- Mani Subramanian, Stater Bros: GS1 Implementation
	- Mark Ennis, FCL: Electronic Shelf Labels  


	- GS1 Organization: Industry Update on Label and Scanning Initiatives
	- Consumer Engagement Update (NCR Consumer Marketing)
EMERALD RELEASES AND ROADMAP
We are excited to announce that now we have a public documentation portal that allows our Emerald customers to see the summary of latest release Emerald 1.6.4. You can access the Emerald POS content from the home page of https://docs.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://docs.ncr.com/]]&gt;. Here is a direct link to the Emerald POS overview &lt;[[https://docs.ncr.com/retail/emerald-pos/overview/]]&gt; page. The Release Notes &lt;[[https://docs.ncr.com/retail/emerald-pos/about/release-notes/version_1_6_1/]]&gt; are under About.
REF 515601: Sale: Display the Price per UOM to the Customer and Cashier when Selling/Returning Weight/Quantity/Volume Item (Phase 2)
REF 515641: POS Report Tenders Expected Amount
Emerald was updated with the ability to print a report at the POS that provides the expected ‘on hand’ amount for all tenders for the lane.
REF 420547: Tare: Provide the Ability to have Proportional Tare Weight for Individual Wrappers
REF 444608: Fuel/Tax: Receive Taxes from Fuel Controller in Pay At Pump (Carwash and Fuel)
REF 520702: Fuel: Trigger Cents Off Discounts Promotion Using Dry Item for Supporting Zipline Tender Discount (Pay At Pump Only)
REF 493370: Fuel: Support Rewards as Tender
REF 354772: Fuel: Sound the Audio Alerts in the POS Lock and Welcome Screen
REF 503874: Tender Check: Handle (capture and endorse) Shopper ID Details when paying with ECC/non ECC tender before Authorizing the Payment.
REF 504401: Tender Check, EPS (CP) Authorization Handle Check Type
REF 499659: Business Rules: Support Delayed Manager Coupon Limit BRMs
REF 488289: WIC EBT: Allow WIC EBT Card to Pay for Non-LEB (Least Expensive Brand) Items
REF 493483: Loyalty &amp; Promotions Pass Transaction Sequence # and Store # to Promotion Engine (AMS/UE)
REF 517768: Catalog: Emerald to Support 100 Characters in Group Names from Catalog instead of 40
REF 523213: Blind Pickup Transaction Type to be Recorded in the Tlog and TDM
REF 523214: Return Reason (Description) to be Captured in Tlog and TDM
REF 523215: Cash Office Account Details in Tlog and TDM
NCR TEAM MEMBER HIGHLIGHTS
At the recommendation of our Advisory Board, we will recognize team members from both NCR and client who have done outstanding work on the Emerald solution, pilots and rollouts.
Engineering
Netta Dagan has been a member of the NCR Emerald team for less than a year. During this short period of time, she has learned significant parts of the product. Recently, Netta was involved in the resolution of two critical and very complex customer issues where she showed an exceptional level of responsibility and dedication. Netta is a valuable team player whose analytical abilities and pleasant personality are highly appreciated.
Pre-Sales
Lynn Kerchner is the hardware and deployment services specialist for the NAMER sales organization. He has been instrumental in presenting, recommending and configuring hardware to support Emerald’s POS and peripherals, SCO, Server, and payment devices. Every Emerald deal to date uses new NCR hardware. He has helped our sales teams navigate through introductions of the new CX7, CX8, 7895 scanners, payment terminals, and other changes in our portfolio. He has Also driven the acquisition of new hardware to setup and support the new Presales Center of Excellence lab in GHQ, which allows us to show Emerald, SCO, Freshop, loyalty, payments, analytics and digital receipts in an integrated end to end solution driven by the Cube cloud demo environment.
RETAILER UPDATES
-Emerald 1.5.211 in 
production stores &amp; 
Emerald 1.6.304 upgrade 
targeting end of Q1
- initiate AMS starting with Food City
-SCO Pilot targeting beginning of Q2 2022


-Upgrade to AMS 7.14 in BGC Test lab
Test Lab Emerald Core Version: 1.6.4
Pilot 1 Revised Date: Q2 2022
-Emerald 1.6.302 in store with
 two out of three lanes deployed
-Third lane conversion targeted for 
next two weeks when rollout will continue 
                

-UAT in progress
-Working to deploy customizations 
and Canada specifics
-Securing hardware for Payments and 
Fuel testing
-Emerald 1.6.302 installed 
in Lab for both Fuel and Grocery
-Will upgrade to 1.6.4 for Fuel pilot
-Fuel Pilot planned Q1
 
 
-Version 1.6.3 currently in lab with 
expectation of early 2022 deployment
-New St Louis Foundry store opened in November
-Fresh Thyme store 606 in Grand Rapids will be 
converted to Meijer Market technology stack 
(i.e. Emerald) mid-2022.
-First customer to sign up for “Keep Current” project 
 -Plan to upgrade to 1.6.4x or 1.7.1x
-Martin’s banner rollout of Emerald 
complete- POS, SCO, Fuel, RX
-Version 1.5.216 in production | 
1.6.303 in lab
-Upgrade all stores March 7th with Emerald 
1.6.304, AMS 7.14 and SCO 1.6.303
-Corporate Store Pilot May 16th with Emerald 
1.6.401, AMS 7.15 and SCO
-Emerald 1.6.201 in three out of four pilots. 
Fourth pilot is running Emerald 1.6.303  
-Awaiting releases of Emerald 1.6.304 and 
1.6.305 which are required for rollout. 
Both releases are due mid-March 2022
-Integration with Aurus Payments and 
Quotient electronic coupons 
-Pilot planned for May/June 2022 with 
Emerald 1.6.4 and AMS 7.14
-Pre-UAT lab testing of Emerald 1.6.3 and 
AMS 7.14
We look forwarding to speaking with you in March at the Emerald Community Meeting! Until then, we’ll see you on the phone, in the lab, or during joint team meetings as we work to meet your business objectives through the NCR Emerald solution.
THANK YOU!

Team Emerald
We currently have these Emerald customers in our Community, representing a diverse and growing cross-section of the U.S. and Canadian grocery segment.
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
