<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>09-13-2022 RET Freshop ABM Campaign Southeastern Grocers Email 1.Email 1</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>What Could eCommerce Look Like at Southeastern Grocers?</subject>
    <textOnly>At Southeastern Grocers, you know your brand better than anyone. Your brand quality is what keeps your customers coming back – and turns your new customers into loyal ones.
 
But don’t you worry about losing your connection with your customers by trying to juggle multiple vendors for your eCommerce?

In comes NCR Freshop. NCR Freshop will enable you to take your unique in-store experience and translate it 
online, taking the in-store experience and delivering it with consistency in a digital world.

Built with retailers like you in mind, NCR Freshop:


	- 
Delivers all essential eCommerce functionality and more — a white-label solution that’s consistent with YOUR brand

	- Provides actionable insights from your eCommerce data — with centralized reporting available across multiple banners
	- Gives you full control over your products and processes — at the corporate level or store level, increasing profits through the sale of merchandise and fresh, higher-margin products


We look forward to demonstrating what NCR Freshop can do for you at Southeastern Grocers.
${CTAText2} &lt;[[${CTAURL}?${url-parameter}]]&gt;
Got questions? Contact us. &lt;mailto:RetailEnterprise.InsideSales@ncr.com&gt;
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
