<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>02-28-23 CP Key Dates and Sales Updates Comm.CP Key Dates and Sales Updates Emai</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Upcoming key dates and channel sales updates</subject>
    <textOnly>Upcoming key dates and channel sales 
updates
Dear Valued Channel Partners,
 
2023 is off to a fast start and we’re excited about the 
opportunities the year brings. As part of our ongoing commitment to keep you apprised of the news, tips and highlights relevant to our global channel community, we’d like to share the latest updates with you:
••••• Mark your calendars for these upcoming dates 
•••••
- 
March 9: Global Channel Sales Kickoff 



If you haven’t already, please be sure to register &lt;[[https://app.wc1.kontiki.com/event/ln8dvepvcp]]&gt; for the NCR Global Channel Sales Kickoff, which will take place on March 9, 2023, from 10:30 a.m.–12:30 p.m. Eastern Time (UTC -5). During our kickoff, we’ll be celebrating channel achievements from the past year, discussing our Transform. Connect. Run. &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WEYiHOO_1HE]]&gt; strategy and sharing enhancements we’re working on to improve your experience in working with NCR.
- April 4: Channel Partner Survey



We want to hear from you! Your feedback is extremely valuable to us as we seek to continuously 
improve our portfolio offering, processes and procedures, and more. This year’s Channel Partner Survey will launch on April 4, 2023, and will remain open through May 2, 2023. We encourage you to take a few minutes to participate and share your insights.
- Q1 2023: Target 
letters



We’ll shortly be distributing target letters to the principals of all our channel partner organizations. Please be on the lookout for these communications and be sure to secure time with your channel account manager(s) to strategically plan and prioritize for the year to achieve your revenue goals.
••••• Tips and 
hints •••••
- 
Channel Pay email — please add to your address books



As 
a reminder, Channel Pay is the entity used to issue payments to our channel partners, which we send under the email address “Helpdesk AMER mailbox.ncrchannelpay.amer@e2open.com.” Please be sure to mark this as a valid email address in your email systems so you’re able to receive notifications from Channel Pay when you have incentives ready to be 
claimed.
- The 2023 market development funds (MDFs) now available


As you may know, NCR co-funds (up to 60%) approved market-development activities with our channel partners to drive co-branded awareness and generate demand. 2023 MDFs are now available so you may send your requests for co-funding through this MDF submission process &lt;[[https://ncr.seismic.com/Link/Content/DCCBGmDDV2cpT8Q2GPjVWJF3MTWd]]&gt;. For full details on NCR’s MDF program, access the guide here &lt;[[https://ncr.seismic.com/Link/Content/DC9RCJcfGqqh6GFDhQGJP2h7WgH8]]&gt;.
- Exchange rates in NCR quoting systems 



We’ve received some questions regarding currency conversions in our quoting systems. Please note that NCR solution pricing is adjusted to reflect currency exchange rate fluctuations monthly and system-quoted pricing is valid for up to 30 days from the date of quote. Please refer to the NCR Partner Network program guide &lt;[[https://ncr.seismic.com/Link/Content/DChHFbdQ8WQBp88hPV3Tm9WPqcTd]]&gt; for the most current information on our channel program guidelines and policies.
••••• Questions? 
•••••
If you have any questions or need additional information, please reach out to your channel account manager or email 
ChannelSales.NCR@ncr.com. We look forward to working together to make this a successful year and appreciate your continued commitment and collaboration.

Best regards,
The NCR Partner Network Team
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
