<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>To all customers in Aloha Insight Microsoft has scheduled the official end of life for SQL 2012 on July 12, 2022, which means Microsoft will no longer supply regular security updates or patches for this version of SQL after that date</description>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>04-19-22 HOS Support Microsoft End Of Life Announcement.Email 2 HOS</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Aloha Insight Database Migration</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear Valued Customer,
 
You are receiving this notification because your company’s Aloha Insight instance is configured for SQL replication. 
 
Microsoft has scheduled the official end of life for SQL 2012 on July 12, 2022, which means Microsoft will no longer supply regular security updates or patches for this version of SQL after that date. With cyberattacks becoming more sophisticated and frequent, running apps and data on unsupported versions can create significant security and compliance risks. To mitigate this risk, NCR will migrate your company’s NCR-hosted Aloha Insight database to a more recent version of SQL Server during an upcoming maintenance window. 
 
Database migrations for all customers will be performed during published maintenance windows on the NCR Aloha Status page &lt;[[https://status.aloha.ncr.com/]]&gt;.  Migrations will start the week of April 18th and will continue until all migration are complete. 
 
ACTION REQUIRED:
If you are a customer who receives replicated data from NCR and your SQL server is running SQL 2008, you will no longer be able to receive replicated data from NCR after your hosted database is upgraded. You need to upgrade your SQL server to a version higher than 2008 (but not higher than 2019) before June 1, 2022. 
 
If your SQL server needs to be upgraded, please reach out to your NCR account representative so we can work with you directly to coordinate your upgrade so your replication feed from NCR continues uninterrupted.
 
Please Note: If you are a customer who receives replicated data from NCR and your SQL server is running SQL 2012, it is highly recommended you upgrade to a more recent version. If you choose to upgrade, the highest supported version of SQL server NCR can currently replicate data to is SQL 2019.
 
If your SQL server is already running a version higher than SQL 2012, no action is needed at this time.
 
If you have any questions about the upgrade, please contact support at support@alohaenterprise.com.
 
Best regards,
NCR Hospitality
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
