<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>08-18-22 HOS 360 Customer Upgrade Comm 2.Email 2</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>NCR Operations 360 v6 delivers enhanced experience</subject>
    <textOnly>Operations 360 delivers new features to enhance your user experience

We’re excited to announce our most recent enhancements to the NCR Operations 360 solution, designed to make your user experience easier and more efficient. 

Here’s a quick rundown of what’s new: 

Mobile Experience 

The new Operations 360 provides a fully accessible mobile experience that enables you to leverage the full power and flexibility of Operations 360 whenever you want, however you want. 

Improved Menu Navigation

There’s a new look and new location for the menu navigation. Now located on the left of the screen, the new menu is structured for usability and can be configured for your business’ specific needs*. 

Next Steps

This update will be rolled out over the next couple of weeks, with no interruption to your service. Once upgraded, you will see a new button added to your MyNCR dashboard labeled “Operations 360 v6”. 

NOTE: following the upgrade, your MyNCR dashboard will have two buttons related to Operations 360. You’ll still have the button you’re using today, which will take you to the current version of the platform, but you will also see a new button labeled “Operations 360 v6” which will take you to the new experience. You can use whichever interface works best for you.

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this upgrade, please reach out to your account team or account executive and they will be happy to assist in getting the answers you need.

Kind regards,

NCR Operations 360 Product Team

*Contact your account team to discuss configuration 
options.
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
