<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Letter to customers 9.16.OPERATIONAL letter to customers 9.16</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>NCR to separate into two independent, industry-leading companies</subject>
    <textOnly>NCR customers and partners, 

Earlier this year, the NCR Board of Directors launched a comprehensive strategic review process to unlock the value of our business. Yesterday, we announced &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/news/newsroom/news-releases/company/ncr-to-separate-into-two-independent-industry-leading-companies]]&gt; that our board approved a plan to separate NCR into two independent, separately traded companies – one focused on digital commerce, the other on ATMs. 

The digital commerce company will leverage NCR’s software-led model to continue transforming, connecting and running global retail, hospitality and digital banking customers’ technology platforms. It will maximize common solutions to drive innovation and boost operational efficiency. 

The ATM company will focus on delivering ATM as a Service to a large, installed customer base across banks and retailers. It will build on NCR’s leadership in self-service banking and ATM networks to meet global demand for ATM access and leverage new ATM transaction types, including digital currency solutions, to drive market growth. 

None of this changes our focus on you, our customer. We will continue serving as your trusted partner, delivering high-quality products and the best customer experience. Our commitment to you remains the same. 

Thank you for trusting NCR. The future is bright and we are eager to share it with you.
Best,


Michael D. Hayford
Chief Executive Officer, NCR
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
