<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>06-07-21 HOS Support McD Tecnology Refresh Comm.Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Your 2021 Technology Refresh Order</subject>
    <textOnly>It’s time to review your 2021 Technology Refresh Order

As the preferred 
in-restaurant provider for McDonald’s US restaurants, NCR is pleased to support the 2021 Technology Refresh initiative to further support the digital capabilities for McDonald’s restaurants. We are reaching out today to inform you about hardware in scope and what to expect from NCR during this initiative.
 
Information about your Technology Refresh Order

NCR has uploaded hardware replacement orders to MyNCR.com for restaurants that have end-of-life equipment in scope for the 2021 Technology Refresh initiative. The below list contains end-of-life hardware in scope and the steps to take to place an order.
 
End-of-life hardware in scope for the 2021 Technology Refresh
Type of Hardware


Hardware Model


Replacement Hardware




Register


JS960
Par 7700



NCR CX7




KVS, ORB and EPROD Controller


Dell Wyse Z Class


Lenovo M625q




eSmart Clock


JS960 eSmart Clock
Par 7700 eSmart Clock
Dell Wyse eSmart Clock with a Z90 Zclass Controller



CX7 eSmart Clock




Kiosk Controllers


Lenovo M93P
Lenovo M400



To be determined by McDonald’s at a later date
No more excel quotes for Technology Refresh Programs 
 
Operators will receive an 
email notification from MyNCR once their 2021 Technology Hardware order is uploaded. Operators who have not previously activated their MyNCR account can do so by going to the MyNCR &lt;[[http://myncr.ncr.com/]]&gt; home page and selecting the forgot password link and input their partners.mcd.com email address to go through the process to set up their account credentials.

Once operator receive their 
“Pending Order” notification and have active credentials, they should click on the link to log in to MyNCR to review and accept their order. If the order requires changes, operators can decline the order with a comment for NCR to take action. For information about the order process, click here &lt;[[https://go.ncr.com/rs/605-BQY-740/images/2021 McD Tech Refresh - MyNCR Order Guide.pdf]]&gt; to view the 2021 Technology Refresh Order Guide.

Please Note: All self-install orders have a $95 dollar Installation Support line item that cannot be 
removed from the order. This covers installation support issues that your OTP may encounter. 

Extend end-of-life hardware lifecycle 

In an effort to provide technology that better serves you and your restaurants, the Windows 10 operating system upgrade is now available for select restaurant devices. Completing this upgrade provides ongoing security protection of the McDonald’s brand.

Hardware that can be reimaged with Win 10 images are:
Type of Hardware


Model




Registers


XR7, JS970 (JS970WSUM75), ES8315




KVS, ORB and EPROD Controllers


KC4, HP T630




eSmart Clock


P1235, es550




Kiosk Controllers


Diebold K1.0, Diebold K2.0, Dell Wyse 7040
Hardware that will need a Win 10 Operating System License purchased prior to Win 10 image upgrade (this Win 10 Operating System License can be purchased through Insight):
Type of Hardware


Model




Registers


JS970 - (JS970WP01B8, JS970WSUM71, JS970WPUM71, JS970XSUM71)




KVS, ORB and EPROD Controllers


Dell Wyse 93L, Dell Wyse 98L




eSmart Clock


JS970 lite Smart Clock (ESC-JS970WP01B8-M)
Restaurants with an OTP 1 or OTP 2 must engage a professional install technician to reimage hardware at the site. Sites utilizing a professional install technician are required to show proof of purchase of the Windows 10 Operating System license to the technician if required. Prior to the installation visit, NCR will also validate that the licenses were purchased for the devices. Pricing for this service can be obtained by calling the Customer Care Center via email at mcdonalds.orders@ncr.com &lt;[[mailto:mcdonalds.orders@ncr.com]]&gt; or by phone at 800.421.8230 on Monday through Friday from 8:00 a.m. ET to 8:00 p.m. ET.
 
The time frame that a technician is required to be on-site to reimage hardware will vary according to the number of devices at the restaurant.



	- 1-6 devices: The installation can be completed during the day while avoiding rush hour time frames 

	- 7-14 devices: Installation will require the restaurant to close at 9 p.m. and the site will be returned to on-site crew members by 4 a.m. 
	- 15+devices: Installation will require the restaurant to close at 9PM and the site will be returned to on-site crew 
members by 4 a.m. for two consecutive days 


Once NCR has completed your Win 10 upgrade activity, your break fix contracts will be updated to the Win 10 version of 
the hardware. If a restaurant has an OTP 3 that will reimage the hardware themselves, the OTP 3 should call the Customer Care Center to update their break fix contracts. Failure to notify NCR will cause issues with Break-Fix swap returns if NCR’s records do not reflect Windows 10 image update on hardware.

Break-Fix Implications to consider

End-of-life hardware in scope for the 2021 Technology Refresh that you wish to continue to use after October 1, 2021 will need to have an extended security license purchased for 
those units. Details on these licenses are forthcoming. These units will be considered replace upon failure as of October 1, 2021.

For questions or concerns about your 2021 Technology Refresh order, please contact the Account Executive for your field office or the NCR Customer Care team via email at Mcdonalds.Orders@ncr.com &lt;[[mailto:Mcdonalds.Orders@ncr.com]]&gt; or by phone at 800.421.8230 on Monday through Friday from 8:00 a.m ET to 8:00 p.m. ET.
ACCOUNT MANAGEMENT AND SALES
 




NCR DIVISION


MCDONALD’S FIELD OFFICE


CONTACT




East


Atlanta, 
Bethesda, 
Stamford



Rob Ireland
rob.ireland@ncr.com
W: (770) 299-6202, C: (828) 719-8236





Central


Chicago, 
Columbus, Denver,
Nashville



Amy Spytko
amy.spytko@ncr.com
C: (315) 327-8603





West


Dallas, Long Beach,
Walnut Creek



Valencia Hunter
valenica.hunter@ncr.com
W: (678) 442-1539, C: (404) 840-6975





New Initiatives/
Program Support



 


Tracey Morgan
tracey.morgan@ncr.com
W: (770) 299-5514, C: (863) 326-0542
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
