<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>05-16-22 HOS Aloha 1.Email 1</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Aloha v19 Now in General Release</subject>
    <textOnly>Over the past year, we’ve been hard at work and wanted to share some exciting news with you on both our Aloha and Silver Pro products.
Our Software Architecture
We have and will continue to invest in our software architecture and ecosystem that supports the digitization of the restaurant. Components of Aloha have been redefined as common APIs and services to integrate partners and transact in the cloud, aggregate all data points, and manage and monitor edge devices, applications and infrastructure more easily. These common APIs and services become the foundation that make up a selling engine flexible enough to enable all the different types of experiences you want to create. They will also enable us to bring our Aloha and Silver Pro products together into one cohesive ecosystem and deliver even more value to our customers.
Aloha v19.6 Now Available
As part of our continued evolution, we’re excited to announce that Aloha v19.6 is now available in general release and already in use in over 1,700 locations around the world. As the latest major release, Aloha v19.6 is not just about the POS. It’s about the entire solution and all NCR products integrated with Aloha. With this release, we have completed solution integration testing with ~40 different products to certify that all components of our full solution are working together, improving the user experience. 

Additionally, we know how important software stability and quality are and have also implemented changes in our software engineering org, dedicating ourselves to a culture of quality. We increased our rigor around testing and increased the testing completed with Aloha v19.6 by 3X over previous versions. We have a new Aloha suite installer available on Aloha Update that includes all the individual product versions that have been tested together as one full stack so that you no longer need to decode which versions of our software work best together. And we will be releasing a new deployment platform in Q3 that makes upgrading the store-site software easier and more reliable and enables you to orchestrate the upgrades on all the devices at the site. 

Please contact your NCR Account Executive to start adding Aloha v19.6 to your lab environment.
Silver Pro is Becoming Aloha Cloud
10 years ago, we launched a cloud-based POS solution called Silver Pro. This product has helped us expand our capabilities in parallel with the Aloha POS. It’s now time for us to bring these products together under one consolidated brand.

Silver Pro is being rebranded as Aloha Cloud and will become a cloud-based deployment option as a POS endpoint, depending upon your concept and operational needs. Over the next 12 months, we will be adding new features to Aloha Cloud and integrating it with the same common set of APIs and services as Aloha uses today. As part of our roadmap, this means that you will be able to use the same set of third-party integrations and NCR add-on capabilities (reporting, labor, scheduling, inventory, eCommerce, etc.) across both an on-premise and/or cloud deployment of your POS.
Next Steps
We will be hosting a virtual event on June 2nd that will go in more-depth on the evolution of our software architecture, the latest release of Aloha, and Aloha Cloud. Click here &lt;[[https://ncr.webex.com/ncr/onstage/g.php?MTID=ee0b1d3742065389f9868c4da9c7a18e9]]&gt; to register to attend.
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
