<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Channel Newsletter 5.28.05-28-20 HOS eWeekly Channel Newsletter Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Streamline Aloha Online Ordering Requests</subject>
    <textOnly>May 28, 2020
More Free Hospitality Training In June 2020
Feedback on the Hospitality training courses has been phenomenal, so we&apos;re offering another round of informative sessions in June. Take advantage of these opportunities to invest in yourself and your business by learning more about NCR solutions from our team of experts. Advanced registration in NCRU is required to reserve your spot.
${CTAText2} &lt;[[${CTAURL}?${url-parameter}]]&gt;
YOUR OPINION MATTERS
We’ve updated this newsletter with a fresh new design, and we’re also revamping the content to include various topics to help you deliver the best service to our customers. We want you to hear from you about the information you’re most interested in seeing in future issues – training, tips and tricks, system updates, support, and more! Please take a few moments to respond to an anonymous survey and share your opinion about the NCR eWeekly newsletter. Thank you for your response by June 5th, 2020.
${CTAText2} › &lt;[[${CTAURL}?${url-parameter}]]&gt;
Aloha Online Ordering Made Easy
To streamline the Aloha Online Ordering requests, we created website links to use going forward when submitting requests for Aloha Online Ordering. These external links may be sent to customers.



	- Prescreen Request &lt;[[https://ncr.quickbase.com/db/bqh2kczjb?a=nwr]]&gt;
	- Aloha Online Ordering Customer Questionnaire &lt;[[https://ncr.quickbase.com/db/bqh88nhyh?a=nwr]]&gt;
	- External Enrollment Request &lt;[[https://ncr.quickbase.com/db/bqh86sqp2?a=nwr]]&gt;: For external builds, our team receives this request from Channel Partner’s/Local Offices to 
begin the project.
	- Remove from Demo Mode &lt;[[https://ncr.quickbase.com/db/bqh87fzv3?a=nwr]]&gt;: For external builds, our team receives this request from Channel Partner’s/Local Offices as the 
testing phase step or the final step to go live.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
