<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>01-03-22 RET NRF 2022 Email 3.Email 3</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>NRF 2022: Start the New Year with NCR at NRF</subject>
    <textOnly>Simple, made possible.
Happy New Year! See you at NRF.
 NRF 2022 | New York | 16-18 January 2022 | NCR Booth 4819
NCR wishes you a Happy New Year and we have a surprise for you that we would like to show you at NRF. Imagine that everything in your store generates data – an associate completing a sale, a shopper using mobile e-commerce or making a purchase at a self-checkout station, even customers entering and leaving the store - NCR lets you see that data in intuitive and relevant views and empowers you to make improvements based on what that data is telling you. Isn’t that fantastic?
 
 The data that NCR gathers from touchpoints and applications coupled with our consulting services can optimize labor, reduce shrink, and increase customer satisfaction.

 NCR brings all the data from a store’s operations into one place, we can apply meaningful analytics and machine learning models to find patterns and make them quickly 
obvious.
 
 Visit NCR at Booth 4819 at NRF to discover how NCR can make your life easier by hi-technology that turns all transactions into data.

 &lt;[[https://nrfbigshow.nrf.com/]]&gt;

Learn more about NCR at NRF &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/retail/nrf-2022]]&gt;

Schedule 
a meeting with us at NRF &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/retail/nrf-2022]]&gt;
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
