<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>2022 CSAT C2 Action Notes.01-09-23 HOS CSAT C2 Action Note EN.EN Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>We are acting on your feedback</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear {{lead.First Name:default=Valued Customer}},
 
At NCR, we remain focused on our customers’ success. Your input helps us learn how we can further improve your experience and the services and products we offer you.

We are excited to see significant improvement in our most recent NCR Customer Satisfaction Survey 2022. However, there is always opportunity to do better and we continue to listen to your feedback to identify areas for development. Based on the responses we received, we are focusing on the following categories and actions within the NCR Hospitality business:


	- 
Service delivery — Building on the momentum following our customer support evolution to a pod approach, we applied those same principles within our implementation and delivery teams to get even closer to our customers, drive process efficiencies and make it easier to work with NCR.

	- 
Software investment — It is our goal to provide world-class solutions for our customers. We have been focusing our investments in the areas that better help you run your restaurant. The launch of Aloha Cloud, Consumer Marketing, Digital Signage and Aloha v19 in 2022 will be followed by the new back office, e-commerce and mobile handheld solutions in 2023. Continued enhancements to our NCR Commerce Platform, including application programming interface (API) capabilities and our partner marketplace to drive integrations and innovation, have also been a top priority. 

	- 
Invoicing — Throughout 2022, we built the foundation that will deliver multiple enhancements to our invoicing experience. Specifically, we improved automation to drive invoice accuracy and a new invoicing structure that will allow for customer-directed formatting of invoices. 



Our customers’ success will remain our priority and we aim to drive substantial progress in each of these areas in 2023. We will continue to invite you to share your feedback, letting us know how we are doing in these areas and others. 

Thank you for being an NCR customer and sharing your opinion with us.

Warmest regards, 

Dirk Izzo
President and General Manager
NCR Hospitality
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
