<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>06-30-22 Hos BiWeekly Newsletter.Email 1</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>KC5, 4th of July Holiday, Fiserve EDC Notice</subject>
    <textOnly>June 30, 2022
KC5 Available for 
Controlled Deployment

 The new KC5 Kitchen Controller is available for Controlled Deployment, and NCR is looking for sites to install the KC5 as we prepare for GA; please contact Austin Anderson (austin.anderson@ncr.com) or Bill Ward (bill.ward@ncr.com &lt;[[mailto:bill.ward@ncr.com]]&gt;).


	- 
Designed to meet the increased demand for kitchen systems driven by omni channel ordering innovations





	- Quad Core Intel Elkhart Lake Celeron processor, 120GB storage and 8GB RAM for high performance




	- Solid state reliability -no fans, no vents




	- Small form factor




	- Multiple points of connectivity - 2 Serial RJ12, 4 USB 3.0, Display port++, Ethernet, Audio out.




	- Locking power connector




	- Windows 10 2019 Embedded LTSC OS




	- Designed for harsh kitchen environments in Quick service, Table service, and fast casual restaurants




	- New KT2200 Stainless Steel Kitchen touch display with display port connection available


Fiserv EDC Notice

We have received information that Fiserv (formerly First Data) appears to have made a business decision to no longer issue 
new MIDs for customers on Aloha EDC. Fiserv has taken the stance that all new Fiserv MIDs should be EMV-gateway only. This impacts not only Fiserv direct merchants, but also those using individual Fiserv agents, referral partners, and ISOs.
 
When questioned about this, it’s important to explain to customers, that this is a business decision on the part of Fiserv. NCR still supports EDC… to the extent that we now offer NCR Payments on the EDC platform. Let’s keep in mind that this represents an opportunity. Channel Partners have had success closing a couple NPP deals for this very reason. Existing customers using Fiserv, or Fiserv ISO’s that are opening new locations, and have been denied EDC MIDs. I think the response should be something along the lines of…
 
“we understand that Fiserv has made a business decision to no longer provide customers the ability to process on Aloha EDC and that this decision has trickled down to agents and ISO’s that use that same Fiserv processing platform. NCR supports Aloha EDC, and now offers customers the ability to process through EDC on our processing platform. If you are encountering this, our suggestion would be to provide us with a current processing statement… we will work to match your current rates, offer you no-cost contactless payment options, and provide you with an Aloha EDC VAR sheet so you can continue to process the same way you are processing today with no cost to convert” 

Josh and I would be eager to assist with 
any such opportunities. Please let us know how we can help. 

Seth Wilson
Payments Specialist 
Seth.wilson@ncr.com &lt;[[mailto:Seth.wilson@ncr.com]]&gt;
(330) 312-5065 

Josh Woodson
Josh.woodson@ncr.com  &lt;[[mailto:Josh.woodson@ncr.com]]&gt;
(480) 466-4072 

Fulfillment Reminder: Monday, July 4

This is a reminder that Monday, July 4, 2022 is a US National holiday and observed by NCR and our logistics provider. It is not considered a “business day.” Orders with a Service Level of the Next Business Day (NBD) will be fulfilled as shown below.

Orders with a Service Level of Next Calendar Day (NCD) will not be affected by the holiday. They will be shipped the same day as ordered and delivered the following day. Next Flight Out (NFO) service will also be available every day, including Monday, July 4. 
Please remember 6:00PM Eastern Time is the cut off time.
      
 Please remember 6:00PM Eastern Time is the cut off time.




 AED Next Business Day Fulfillment Schedule




Date Ordered


Date Shipped


Date Delivered




Friday 7/1/22 


Friday 7/1/22


Tuesday 7/5/22




Monday 7/4/22 


Tuesday 7/5/22


Wednesday 7/6/22




Tuesday 7/5/22


Tuesday 7/5/22


Wednesday 7/6/22
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
