<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>03-01-21 HOS Support McD Break-Fix HW Return Change.Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Important: Your HW Return Process Has Changed</subject>
    <textOnly>To make your returns easier, we’ll now be shipping all break-fix packages with a return label under the shipping label. Now, when you receive the package, you only need to:


	- 
Remove the new hardware from the box

	- Place your old, broken hardware into that same box
	- Peel off the shipping label to display the return label
	- And either:


	- Call 1-800-GO-FEDEX to schedule a pickup; or
	- Drop the package off at any FedEx location 




You must send your broken HW back in the same box because:


	- 
The box’s tracing number is how we match the HW sent to the HW received in our depot

	- For example, if we get a controller back but are expecting a register, you’ll be invoiced for the missing register
	- Matching the break-fix ticket to the HW received prevents you from being mistakenly invoiced for not returning the HW


NOTE: Take a picture of the return label or write down the tracking number and store it. If the shipment doesn’t arrive, we can’t trace it without the tracking number. Equipment not returned within 30 days or damaged from improper packaging will be invoiced. 

Also, if you ship a part to NCR by mistake and want it returned, there’s a $100 charge to ship it back. But you don’t have to remember all of this—all HW shipped will have the instructions in each box. 

Please update your McDonald’s staff on these changes. We believe this will give you more control of your hardware returns. If you have any questions, please email unreturnedequipment.hsr@ncr.com &lt;mailto:UnreturnedEquipment.HSR@ncr.com&gt;.

We appreciate the opportunity to support your restaurants. Thank you for your business!
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
