<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>04-21-21 HOS Newsletter QSR Top 10 McDonalds.MCD Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Are you managing your NCR account through MyNCR?</subject>
    <textOnly>Managing your NCR account just got a lot simpler
To help you manage your business more efficiently, NCR partnered with McDonald’s stakeholders to develop a customized ecommerce portal to help all authorized McDonald&apos;s stakeholders manage their NCR accounts. 

With MyNCR, you can login to your NCR account anytime, anywhere, to access a customized portal that gives you real-time information for better NCR account management. 

NCR will send the link to activate your MyNCR account to 
operator&apos;s partners.mcd.com email address on Friday, April 23, 2021.
NEW! - MyNCR Functionality
COMING SOON: Program orders

Gone are the days of excel quotes that you have to review and send back to NCR. Instead, NCR will send orders that support McDonald’s in-restaurant technology initiatives through MyNCR. If you’re an Operator or OTP with access to online orders, you can simply log into your account to review and provide feedback.
What you’ll be able to do with MyNCR:
One-stop-shop: Access a centralized portal to manage your business with real-time account information, reporting capabilities and self-service features.
 
Dashboard navigation: Streamline your business by customizing your MyNCR 
dashboard to easily navigate all the various account functions.
eCommerce: Place orders for hardware and other products any time you can connect to the internet. 

Invoice management: An interactive pie chart shows you all paid, past due or upcoming invoices. You can also access the MyNCR invoice page to search, view, download, print or dispute invoices online.

Invoice payment: Pay your invoices with the new automated clearing house (ACH) option.
 
Order reporting management: Search, view, download and print order reports in the “Order” portlet 
and access specific orders to view product details, status and shipping information.

Invoice dispute management: Submit and see the status of open disputes and any still waiting for your feedback. Access the MyNCR Invoice Dispute page for summary details on all invoice disputes.

Self-management of users: Gain two different user roles to allow legal account owners to manage their own users, including adding new users, resetting passwords, deleting users and managing user permission and access to information.

Training and Help: Use 
the help icon for access to training modules, short demos, invitations to webinars, a getting-started guide and a user manual.
MyNCR user roles
Administrator

MyNCR requires at least one designated administrator from your company to have access to all MyNCR features and to be responsible for:


	- 
Creating and managing other users and resetting passwords 

	- 
Disabling/deleting users 

	- 
Requesting application access



User 

MyNCR general authorized users can see, manage and interact with MyNCR depending on your user permissions granted by your administrator. Access to functions are managed by your administrator when they create a new user or in users’ profile page.

If you have any questions or need assistance with your MyNCR account, please contact the dedicated NCR-McDonald’s Customer Care team Monday through Friday between 8:00 a.m. and 8:00 p.m. EST or by emailing McDonalds.orders@ncr.com &lt;[[mailto:McDonalds.orders@ncr.com]]&gt;.
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
