<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>Objective: Inform Hospitality customers on the upcoming launch of a new customer portal Audience/Distribution List: MVP Hospitality customers</description>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>09-26-22 HOS MVP New Customer Portal.09-26-22 HOS - MVP Hospitality customers Up</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>NCR Support Hub Transition Changes for Tuesday</subject>
    <textOnly>NCR customers and partners,

This is a reminder that on Tuesday, September 27th, you will automatically have the new ‘NCR Support Hub’ applet on your MyNCR Homepage.
MyNCR
On the homepage, you will have access to both My Support Link – O360 and NCR Support Hub temporarily. Starting Tuesday, NCR Support will enter new support cases into the NCR Support Hub and be closing currently opened cases in My Support Link – O360. Starting Tuesday, please log new cases and work orders into the NCR Support Hub (if that’s a role you perform). On September 30th, your access to ‘My Support Link – O360’ will be removed, and over the weekend of October 1st, all remaining open cases and 90 days of closed cases will be migrated to the NCR Support Hub.
Pulse
With the move to the NCR Support Hub, Pulse will ONLY be used for reporting and not for creating cases. You will have the option either to call Support (especially for urgent issues) or create tickets within NCR Support Hub.
Getting Ready for Migration
Moving to the NCR Support Hub will be easy for both you and your employees. A training manual and videos are now available on MyNCR under the MyNCR Training Center.
If you have additional questions, please reach out to your NCR Customer Success Manager or Account Executive.
Additionally, if you need assistance with this transition or further clarification, feel free to reach out to the NCR Support Hub team at Hospitality.SupportEnablement@ncr.com &lt;[[mailto:Hospitality.SupportEnablement@ncr.com]]&gt;.
We hope you are excited as we are for this new platform, and appreciate your continued partnership.

Sincerely,
 NCR</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
