<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>03-13-23 CP HOSP SWaaS and HWaaS Price Increase Update.03-13-23 CP HOSP SWaaS an</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Important Update: Pricing Changes for NCR SWaaS &amp; HWaaS Products</subject>
    <textOnly>Important Update: Pricing Changes for NCR SWaaS &amp; HWaaS 
Products
To our valued Channel Partners,

NCR is committed to being a reliable provider of high-quality products 
and services to help our customers RUN their businesses. We are still seeing material costs and cost of capital increases driven by the current inflation environment and we are not immune. NCR has absorbed many of these cost increases and we have taken measures to minimize them, however we expect these cost pressures to continue for the foreseeable future. 

In order to ensure we can deliver with the quality and lead times our customers and partners expect, NCR will be implementing a 5% - 8.5% price increase on SWaaS and HWaaS with select HWaaS products receiving some additional increases. This pricing change will go into effect on April 13th, 2023 and will be reflected in NCR quoting systems. 

We plan to regularly review our costs throughout 2023 and will re-evaluate pricing as the economic environment continues to change. Thank you for your continued partnership and collaboration through this process, and please reach out to your CAM with any questions. 

Best regards,
NCR Global Channel Program Team
&lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
