<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>09-15-21 HOS Integration Partner Newsletter.Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>NCR 3rd Party Partnerships Newsletter</subject>
    <textOnly>September 15, 2021
Greetings Third Party Partner,

We’re excited to send you NCR’s first Third Party Partner Newsletter. We want you to know that we value our partnership and hope to stay better connected in sharing the latest updates, new partner additions, support information, FAQ’s and more. Below you’ll find a wealth of content that will hopefully be of interest to you as we continue to build out our partner ecosystem with our joint customers in mind. Giving our customers access to the “best of the best” in each vertical is important to NCR. As you review the information enclosed, please do not hesitate to reach out with any questions or comments (See FAQ’s). We welcome your feedback and look forward to continuing our value-added partnership in the future
Welcome New Partners




	- APEX – Ordering
	- BevSpot – Inventory 
	- CheddrSuite (RD Solutions) – Inventory, Labor Management, Training
	- Deliverect – Ordering 
	- Gratuity Solutions &lt;[[https://gratuitysolutions.com/]]&gt; – Tip Management
	- MarginEdge – Accounting &amp; Payroll, Business Analytics, Inventory, Labor Management &amp; Scheduling
	- Restaurant Accounting Systems Inc (RASI) &lt;[[https://rasiusa.com/]]&gt; – Accounting &amp; Payroll, Business Analytics, Inventory, Labor Management &amp; Scheduling
	- SipScience (CC App Holdings) &lt;[[https://www.sipscience.com/]]&gt; – Loyalty, Marketing &amp; Surveys, Payments
	- Solink - Training
	- Vemos – Business Analytics, Loyalty, Restaurants &amp; Guest Management
Frequently Asked Questions



	- How to Obtain NCR Support
	- Billing Questions and Deadlines
	- Partner Relations Team Members
	- Do you have another question that is not answered above, please contact Partner Relations at ISV.Partnerships@ncr.com &lt;[[mailto:ISV.Partnerships@ncr.com]]&gt;
Our Partner Portal is ready for YOU
- Our new Partner Portal allows our valued partners to take the reins in managing and tracking their interactions with NCR and our joint customers. You can review your invoices, pay online, see your statement and even request additional detail. We’re continually striving to improve your experience with us because we value your partnership. You can apply for Portal access via https://www.ncr.com/how-to-buy/account-request  settle  &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/how-to-buy/account-request]]&gt;
Help Center Resource
Have you visited the help 
center page &lt;[[https://developer.ncr.com/portals/dev-portal/help-center/search]]&gt; on the developer portal lately? We continually update the developer portal with new and pertinent information for partners. Be sure to bookmark this page and check it continuously for the latest updates &lt;[[https://developer.ncr.com/portals/dev-portal/help-center/search]]&gt;.
Current standard requirements for our Online Ordering Third Party Partners
For our Ordering partners, the latest software stack requirements at the site level have been updated. Aloha Takeout v19.1 is now required. NCR works hard to add support in these times to help restaurants. This version now supports car information via BSP. v19.1 also supports revenue center information through BSP. Revenue information can be used to drive multiple pricing by item at the pos level, Think of pricing items by pickup verses delivery.
Order Monitor Overview (For Ordering Partners)
Order Monitor &lt;[[https://email.ncr.com/NjA1LUJRWS03NDAAAAF_QKHz8kGK5mVhMjaKsw5tRpdSmX2wAfskiH9Sl7H1oHJwOCDgkXDQtiQiL4-JxCcVI0aI7v0=]]&gt; offers our mutual customers the ability to know the status of their sites 
and if the sites are unable to process orders. This application is comprised of two components: Passive Monitor and Active Monitor. Passive Monitor checks regular traffic to detect potential downtime based on configurable latency metrics. When the Passive Monitor detects potential downtime, the Active Monitor is triggered and sends a synthetic order down to the site. It then awaits a response from the site to verify whether or not it is down. Click here to access the Order Monitor &lt;[[https://email.ncr.com/NjA1LUJRWS03NDAAAAF_QKHz8kGK5mVhMjaKsw5tRpdSmX2wAfskiH9Sl7H1oHJwOCDgkXDQtiQiL4-JxCcVI0aI7v0=]]&gt;.
Meet The Team at NCR
Kathy Pittman 
Kathy.Pittman@NCR.com
Kathy has many years in Hospitality and IT Technology Industries in various leadership functions from perspectives of the customer, provider, vendor/partner, and now with NCR, 6 years. 
Kathy is responsible for the Global NCR Hospitality Partnership Ecosystem.
Kelly Martinez
Kelly.martinez@ncr.com
Kelly has 10 years of experience with NCR. Her first 7 years were spent working in Product Management and the past 3 years she has been working with NCR’s Partnership Team. Kelly’s current focus is working with internal groups to onboard new Strategic Partnerships along with managing existing Partner Relationships.
Dan Whitcomb 
Dan.Whitcomb@ncr.com
Dan has worked on Aloha for 32 years and for NCR for 23 years. He currently works with the technical onboarding of new partners. He is married with five children and enjoys all things outdoors. His long-term goal is to buy a campground and retire. His favorite motto is if it is not broke do not fix it.
Timothy Sean Newby 
Timothy.newby@ncr.com
Timothy, goes by Sean, has over 30 years of experience in the Hospitality Industry. 
He has worked in a project management and technical support capacity both for Aloha Resellers and Aloha customers. 
He currently works with the technical onboarding of new partners.
Corbin Lappin 
Corbin.Lappin@ncr.com
Corbin graduated in May of 2020 from the University of Arizona. 
He was hired as a Product Analyst and has taken on the role of managing various projects within the Partnerships Team. He works closely with Kelly and Kathy on Partnership interaction along with the partner on-boarding process.
Chris Barron 
Chris.barron@ncr.com
Chris has over 30 years in the hospitality industry with a focus on high volume restaurants. He brings this experience to the NCR partnership team to help identify the best partner solutions to run restaurants as smoothly and as efficiently as possible. cell: (305) 968-8884
Andy Swimmer 
Andrew.Swimmer@NCR.com
Andy has 15 years of experience with NCR via our Radiant Systems Inc acquisition in 2011. His tenure has included roles in both IT &amp; Finance. Currently Andy is focused on identifying new strategic and tactical partner opportunities and streamlining the Partner Onboarding process.
Invoicing Updates
Did you know that you have several choices for how you can receive your invoices?



	- Mail – this is the default communication method
	- Email – Please email HospitalityPartnership.HSR@ncr.com &lt;[[C:\Users\CQ185008\AppData\Local\Microsoft\Windows\INetCache\Content.Outlook\NVQVU1M2\HospitalityPartnership.HSR@ncr.com]]&gt; to request email receipt of your invoice and include:


	- Your MCN
	- The email address you would like your invoices sent to


	- Portal – you can apply for Portal access via https://www.ncr.com/how-to-buy/account-request &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/how-to-buy/account-request]]&gt;



	- Here you can view your invoice, view a statement of your account, history and make payments.
	- You can also log an invoice dispute through the portal.
How to obtain NCR support
Remember as an official partner you do not need to have our 
mutual customer open a support incident/ticket. You are empowered to open a support ticket  by following these steps:



	- Call the support line at 800-792-5642, option 2.
	- Email support@alohaenterprise.com &lt;[[mailto:C:\Users\CQ185008\AppData\Local\Microsoft\Windows\INetCache\Content.Outlook\NVQVU1M2\support@alohaenterprise.com]]&gt; (for non-critical issues ONLY)



Needed Case 
Information: The following information is required to be provided. This information helps NCR Support quickly create and resolve any technical/support issue:



	- Third Party Partner’s name
	- Name of the customer you are working with
	- Integration Type: Cloud Connect/API, Business Service Platform (BSP), or SDK/COM?
	- Customer&apos;s Site HASP Key #
	- Date / Time issue occurred
	- Detailed Description of issue (Including any API call, any POS error message, Nep org, Enterprise unit, BSP order id)
	- Point of Contact Name &amp; Email/Phone for Third Party Partner and customer
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
