<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>2021 CSAT Action Notes Cycle 2.01-11-22 RET CSAT Action Note EN.EN Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>We are acting on your feedback</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear {{lead.First Name:default=Valued Customer}},
 
At NCR, we remain focused on our customers’ success. Your input helps us learn how we can further improve the services and products we offer you.

We are excited to see significant improvement in our most recent NCR Customer Satisfaction Survey. However, there is always room to do better and we continue to listen to your feedback to identify areas for enhancement. Based on the responses we received, we are focusing on the following areas and actions within the NCR Retail business unit.


	- Customer Service and Support—Earlier this year, we rolled out a new structure that established clear 
accountability and a single point of contact for our customers. This enables us to respond to incidents faster and significantly reduce the backlog of tickets. With the opening of our new campus in Belgrade, Serbia, we will further improve customer experience as we build continuity, communication, knowledge growth and transfer from more than 4,000 employees located on site.




	- Software Support and Quality—We continue to remain focused on advancing our agile processes to help improve how we develop and deliver 
our software. Our goal is to reach full end-to-end automation for our products and the entire solution, consistent practices for code reviews and greater sprint governance. Another key focus remains on incident reduction and problem management in our software support to enable higher levels of availability.




	- Product Lifecycle Management—As part of the overall communication improvements, we will be sharing more details on our product lifecycle 
and areas of innovation as we work more closely with our customers to better understand your needs and build the products that help you differentiate and grow.


We aim to drive substantial progress in these areas in 2022. We will continue our customer satisfaction process and invite you to continue sharing your feedback, letting us know how we are doing in these fields and others.
 
Thank you for being an NCR customer and sharing your opinion with us.

Warmest regards,
 
David Wilkinson 
President and General Manager, NCR Retail

Eric 
Schoch
Senior Vice President, NCR Global Retail Sales &amp; Field Operations
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
