<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>2021 CSAT Notes Industry.03-24-21 RET CSAT Note EN.EN Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>We Are Acting On Your Feedback</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear {{lead.First Name:default=Valued Customer}},
 
At NCR, we remain focused on the success of our customers. Your input helps us learn how we can make simple possible for you and further improve the service and solutions we offer you. 

As Mike Hayford shared in his note to you, we are excited to see significant improvement in our most recent Customer Satisfaction survey results. As just one example, we were pleased to see that the improvements in our invoicing process are taking effect. This is all the more rewarding given the challenging year we have all experienced, during which we hope NCR was a great support to you. However, there is always room to do better, and we continue to listen to your feedback to identify areas for improvement. Based on your responses to the survey, we’re focusing on the following areas and actions within the Retail business unit:



	- 

We have brought together the different teams that touch a customer today under one roof in the retail organization to create an end-to-end customer experience from the first commercial engagement throughout the entire delivery process. This significantly reduces the number of internal hand-offs and creates clear accountability and a single point of contact for our customers. 

	- 

We continue to improve our software quality and software support and are advancing our agile processes to help improve how we develop and deliver our software. Our goal is to reach full end-to-end automation for our products and the entire solution, consistent practices for code reviews and greater sprint governance. Another key focus remains on incident reduction and problem management in our software support to enable higher levels of availability.

	- From the most recent responses we see that the structured program for resolving tickets by soliciting real-time customer feedback is yielding results, and we are glad to hear you are seeing improvements. Still, we want to get even better and continue to improve our service quality.


We aim to drive substantial improvement in these areas over the course of 2021. We will continue our Customer Satisfaction survey process, and invite you to continue to share your feedback and let us know how we’re doing on these areas and others. 
 
Thank you again for being an NCR customer and for sharing your feedback with us.

Warmest regards,

David Wilkinson 
President and General Manager, NCR Retail

Eric Schoch
SVP, Global Retail Sales &amp; Field Operations
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
