<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>12-06-22 HOS Vitalcast EOL External Communication.12-06-22 HOS  Vitalcast Extern</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>End of Life Announcement &amp; Timeline for Vitalcast Digital Signage</subject>
    <textOnly>NCR is committed to providing the highest quality products and services to our customers. We continually assess our existing solution portfolio to give our customers a clear competitive advantage, new technology and product innovation, and operational efficiencies. This can also include making the difficult decision to discontinue the availability and maintenance of products that have reached the end of their useful life.
This letter is to formally communicate the End of Life (EOL) for NCR Vitalcast Digital Signage effective June 30, 2024, or the end of your contract term. The last day to order these products is June 30, 2023.  Customers will continue to receive support for this product until June 30, 2024, or the 
end of your contract term. Hardware Maintenance Warranty replacements will continue until the end of your current warranty term.


This product is being discontinued due to market demand, shifts in technology and a change in focus and investment. In March of 2022, we announced a strategic partnership with Stratacache &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/news/newsroom/news-releases/hospitality/ncr-and-stratacache-partner-to-engage-customers]]&gt;, a global industry leader in digital signage. This partnership accelerates our digital signage innovation and enables us to deliver solutions that create a competitive edge. Stratacache provides mature and proven digital personalization, customization, sales optimization and suggestive sell capabilities for greater guest engagement and 
stronger brand loyalty.

If you are using NCR Vitalcast today, your Account Manager will be reaching out to you over the coming months to discuss migrating to Stratacache digital signage..

 
Below are the key dates and milestones that will be part of the Vitalcast EOL process:




Milestone


Definition


Date




End of Life (EOL)
Notification


End of Life notification is distributed via email to product users.

December 6, 2022



Last Order Date


The last day to order any Vitalcast solution component, HW, SW etc.


June 30, 2023




Last Fulfillment Date (for pre-orders)


The last day NCR will ship any Vitalcast solution component, HW, SW etc.


September 30, 2023




End of Life 


The last day the hosted solution will be available. All SW service and support end.


June 30, 2024





How to learn more about Digital Signage (powered by Stratacache):



	- Contact your NCR Account Manager 
	- Register here &lt;[[https://ncr.webex.com/ncr/onstage/g.php?MTID=e0c5dedf09ba012f0d29c0a7277b631f9]]&gt; for a quick session on our NCR Digital Signage solution where we have partnered with Stratacache to provide a 
comprehensive solution set for a fully immersive digital customer experience. 
	- Visit ncr.com here &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/restaurants/digital-signage]]&gt;



Thank you for your attention to this notification. Please contact us if you have any questions or need additional information.
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
