<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>02-dd-23 HOS Customer &quot;In the Know&quot; Webinar.HOS Customer &quot;In the Know&quot; Webinar E</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Important announcement about NCR Digital Signage</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear {{lead.First Name:default=edit me}}:

NCR is committed to providing the highest quality products and services to our customers. We continually assess our existing solution portfolio to give our customers a clear competitive advantage, new technology and product innovation, and operational efficiencies. This can also include making the difficult decision to discontinue the availability and maintenance of products that have reached the end of their useful life.

As previously communicated the NCR Vitalcast Digital Signage solution will become End of Life (EOL) effective June 30, 2024, or the end of your contract term. The last day to order these products is June 30, 2023. This product is being discontinued due to market demand, shifts in technology and a change in focus and investment. In March of 2022, we announced a strategic partnership with Stratacache &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/news/newsroom/news-releases/hospitality/ncr-and-stratacache-partner-to-engage-customers]]&gt;, a global industry leader in digital signage. This partnership accelerates our digital signage innovation and enables us to deliver solutions that create a competitive edge. Stratacache provides mature and proven digital personalization, customization, sales optimization and suggestive sell capabilities for greater guest engagement and stronger brand loyalty.

If you are using NCR Vitalcast today, please speak to your Account Manager to discuss migrating to the Stratacache digital signage. 


How you can learn more about NCR Digital Signage (powered by Stratacache):


	- 
Register here &lt;[[https://ncr.webex.com/weblink/register/r0560f2f150d255fc90bf0eec2ad5b43d]]&gt; for a quick session on February 27th at 3:30pm EST to hear about our NCR Digital Signage solution where we have partnered with Stratacache to provide a comprehensive solution set for a fully immersive digital customer experience. In this session you will learn about:



	- 
NCR’s Expertise in the field

	- 
Why the strategic partnership with Stratacache?

	- 
High-level overview of the NCR Digital Signage (powered by Stratacache) solution

	- 
Transition steps to move from Vitalcast to Stratacache
Register here
Thank you for your attention to this notification. Please contact us if you have any questions or need additional information. Visit ncr.com to learn more about our digital signage solution &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/restaurants/digital-signage]]&gt;.

{{company.Account Owner Name:default=edit me}}
&lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
