<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>https://www.ncr.com/retail/nga-2023</description>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>02-07-23 RET NGA Pre Show Email 1.RET NGA Pre-Show Email 1</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>NGA 2023: Join NCR to see where grocery retail is headed</subject>
    <textOnly>With staffing shortages, supply chain challenges, and the pressure of always-rising customer expectations, the need to get rid of 
inefficiencies in your store has never been higher.

From POS to analytics to back office and beyond, NCR has made it easier than ever to integrate and simplify your technology and operations so you can focus on what matters most to you – your customers. We can help you meet your customers’ expectations and run your stores in a whole new way – totally seamlessly.

Visit us at Booth #1319 at NGA 2023 to discover new ways to:


	- 
Introduce your own eCommerce and delivery services within weeks – and without expensive third-party providers

	- 
Delight shoppers when they’re inside your store with smarter self-service technologies

	- 
Automate standard processes to free resources that help you grow



It’s your chance to put our innovative retail technology to the test – and see how we can help run your store, today and tomorrow.

The NGA Show is approaching fast, and we’re looking forward to seeing you 
and your customers there!
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
