<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>2020 T&amp;T CX Survey.Email Note from Sophia</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Your voice counts in helping NCR meet your needs</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear {{lead.First Name:default=Valued Customer}}, 

By all measures, 2020 has a been a challenging year for everyone. During such tough times, we realize how important it is to have a customer and a partner who work closely together. We’re very proud and thankful that you trust NCR to deliver the highest quality service possible and to serve your needs at this critical moment.
This year, we’re still working hard to enhance the customer experience based on your feedback. We’d love to share some of these details with you and your account manager may have already reached 
out to you. 

Here are some highlights of those improvements:


	- 
Delivered superior performance against our business continuity plan 

	- 
Initiated a plan to facilitate more innovative and robust solution designs for our customers 

	- 
Invested significant hours training customer engineers to represent your brand 

	- 
Continued investment in our Remote Services portfolio roadmap

	- 
Achieved solid progress producing higher quality invoicing

Beginning on Tuesday, October 6, you’ll start receiving our first 2020 relationship survey. It takes only about three minutes to complete and focuses on several ways to strengthen our strategic relationship, such as sales, services and invoicing. The survey is flexible, so you can skip areas that don’t apply. And we love written feedback. This is a big help in understanding the results. 

Your voice truly matters and we’re eager to hear from you. Thank you for your feedback and support. It’s a privilege to be your strategic partner.

Sincerely, 

Sophia Williams
SVP and General Manager
NCR Telecom and Technology</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
