<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>CP Partner Emails.Product Management Organizational Changes - Jan 2020</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Counterpoint Product Management - Organizational Changes</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;
NCR Counterpoint
Product Management Announcement
3 Key Counterpoint Organizational Changes
I am excited to announce that effective immediately Al Russo has officially accepted the Counterpoint Product Manager role. This role has an expanded view of Counterpoint as a business instead of a standalone product. Al will be responsible for working across software, hardware and payment functional areas ensuring the Counterpoint business thrives.

Al has been deeply involved with Counterpoint for 10 years including various roles in the engineering team from Lead Developer to Product Architect and has been 
instrumental in the growth and market coverage of Counterpoint.
His deep product knowledge, partner relationships and continual focus on customer success will help drive Counterpoint as we fittingly move into the next decade and next generation of Counterpoint. 

Al is based in NCR’s Global Headquarters and lives in Atlanta with his wife and his 11 and 12 year old daughters who are avid soccer and basketball players.

I also am excited to announce that Rahul Dixit 
has accepted a new challenge and role as Sr Field Product Manager. Rahul’s deep experience as a Senior Architect in Advanced Store’s PS team, fanatical focus on customer success, personal drive and business acumen positions him to uniquely excel in this role. Rahul has been with NCR for 17 years in the area of Specialty Retail and contributing in various fields including requirement management, delivery, deployment, project management and customer engagement. His professional experience and result oriented approach gives him deep knowledge of professional services, business operations and customer experience.

Rahul will be leading the effort with channel partners on best practices for deploying Advanced Store in a mid-market space which has unique challenges. Rahul will also be working closely with the product, engineering and channel teams on building efficiencies (such as best practice pre-configurations) and roadmap requirements within the DSR products. 

Rahul will also be key in driving the effort with the Pricing and Channel team to enable Advanced Store to be sold standalone in the mid-market.

Rahul currently lives in Atlanta with his wife and 2 beautiful 
daughters (Shreeya and Sara).

Philip Looney has decided to leave NCR. I want to thank Philip for his efforts across multiple products within NCR and wish him the best going forward.

Wishing everyone a prosperous 2020,
Michael
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
