<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Channel Newsletter 10.15.20.10-15-20 HOS eWeekly Channel Newsletter Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>eWeekly – TechFest 2020 Registration Now Open!</subject>
    <textOnly>October 15, 2020
TechFest 2020 Registration Now Open
Get ready for TechFest 2020 on November 10 -13, 2020. This annual event is the NCR annual Hospitality technical conference that provides a unique opportunity for our Hospitality community to come together to collaborate, learn, and have fun networking with peers in the industry. 

TechFest 2020 is virtual this year and attendance is totally free. It just doesn’t get any better than that! 

It’s important to register now &lt;[[https://on.lenos.com/ncr/TechFest-2020/Content/RegisterNow]]&gt;, to reserve your spot. Registration closes Friday, October 30th. 

At TechFest 2020, we’ll have experts and product owners presenting over 25 topics with new and exciting product updates. Technicians will learn the latest implementation techniques for core NCR Hospitality solutions. NCR will also offer multiple hands-on certification tracks and workshops.

Here’s a sneak peek at some of the information you’ll learn:



	- 
Wireless implementation best practices


	- 
Aloha Kitchen and Aloha Takeout integration


	- 
Menu and Order Services – integrating with 3rd party applications


	- 
Implementing Contactless Dine-In


	- 
Upgrade simplification and process improvements


	- 
Keyless licensing – deployment and strategy


	- 
Implementing NCR Order Pay


	- 
NCR Payments training that includes payments troubleshooting, payment devices updates, implementation best practices and converting customers to NCR Payments Processing Topics and more...



We promise, you don’t want to miss TechFest 2020!

Unleash the power of simplicity for the restaurant now by visiting the TechFest 2020 site &lt;[[https://on.lenos.com/ncr/TechFest-2020/Content/Overview]]&gt; to register today.

We 
can’t wait to see you!
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;  
   
© 2020 NCR Corporation. All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
