<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Channel Newsletter 6.18.20.06-18-20 HOS eWeekly Channel Newsletter Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>eWeekly – NCR Payment Processor is Ready – Complete Required Training</subject>
    <textOnly>June 18, 2020
NCR Payment Processor is Ready – Complete Required Training &lt;#NCR Payment Processor is Ready&gt;
NCR Payment 
Solutions Lab Setup &lt;#NCR Payment Solutions Lab Setup&gt;
Updates to Subscription Program &lt;#Updates to Subscription Program&gt;
Fulfillment Orders Reminder for Independence 
Day – July 3, 2020 &lt;#Fulfillment Orders Reminder&gt;
End of Support for Aloha Guest Manager Jan. 31, 2021 &lt;#End of Support&gt;
More Aloha and Payments Training &lt;#More Aloha and Payments Training&gt;
NCR Payment Processor is Ready – Complete Required Training
NCR Payment Processor is now ready! All sales representatives and technical contacts are asked to complete the Payments courses listed below by July 15, 2020. 
Additional technical training courses for 
NCR Payment Solutions 
are available on NCRU via this link &lt;[[https://ncr.quickbase.com/up/bqe6gx23b/g/rm/ek/va/NCR Payment Solutions Training and Resources v2.pdf]]&gt;.


NCR Payment Solutions Lab Setup

To order Equinox Luxe lab equipment, allow a 3 - 4 week lead time to receive the equipment. Please use the Aloha with NCR Payment Solutions Playbook &lt;[[https://ncr.seismic.com/Link/Content/DCQi4CPmEPsU-MkbNu3009Qg]]&gt;  
for information on processes to set up your equipment. 
  
 
 
Your Channel Account Managers are available to assist if you have any questions. Cloud Sales Representatives are also available to help you input NCR Payment Solutions orders into Salesforce. Leveraging them as a resource will prevent issues in implementation due to hardware delays.
Updates to Subscription Program
Equinox Tethered Device Clarification 
  
  
  
 
All tethered devices sold through the Aloha Essentials program will come with the stand cable, but does not include the stand. Any stands should be sold upfront through your office, similar to mounting brackets or printer cabling. 
  
 
 
New Quoting Functionality – Clone and Move 
  
  
  
 
You will now see a “Clone and Move” button on the Quote page in the Aloha Essentials Salesforce portal. This should help multi-site customers with similar configurations across sites, or even single-site customers asking for several different configurations quoted out. Visit this link &lt;[[https://ncr.quickbase.com/up/bqe6gx23b/g/rn/ek/va/New Quoting Functionality Article.pdf]]&gt; for  
detailed instructions.

Updated NCR Tablet  Essentials has updated the Tablet to PID 7779-3023-8801 – the main change is a new processor. These units will no longer ship with a USB charging cable, only the tablet charging stand (PID 7779-K101).    Available Documents on Aloha Essentials Salesforce Portal    You can always access commonly requested documents – including the latest addendum tools - through the Salesforce portal. Go to the Documents tab, choose the “POS Partner Docs” from the drop-down and press Go. That will display the documents you can view/save/print as needed.    Please contact alohaessentials@ncr.com &lt;[[mailto:alohaessentials@ncr.com]]&gt; with any questions.
Fulfillment Orders Reminder for Independence Day – July 3, 2020

Friday, July 3, 2020 is Independence Day, a U.S. national holiday observed by NCR and our logistics provider. It is not considered a business day, so all orders will be fulfilled as listed below. The cut off time for all orders is 6:00 p.m. ET.
 
 

 	- Next Calendar Day (NCD) service level orders are not affected by the holiday. These orders will be shipped the same day as ordered and delivered the following day. 	- Next Business Day (NBD) service level orders will be fulfilled on the next business day following the holiday. 	- Next Flight Out (NFO) service level orders will be available every day, including Friday, July 3rd and Saturday, July 4th.
End of Support for Aloha Guest Manager January 31, 2021
NCR is extending the end of support date for Aloha Guest Manager (text messaging, reservations and waitlist API) from August 31, 2020 to January 31, 2021 to provide additional time for customers to leverage these products until they can successfully migrate to a new solution.

We recommend customers migrate to solutions powered by NCR partners that are integrated with Aloha POS. Customers should contact our partners directly for pricing, features and functionality. You may share this one-page guide &lt;[[https://ncr.seismic.com/X5/DocCenter.aspx?ContentId=75b7ce87-7142-4a89-a852-11c2748a3f0f#/doccenter/8ef384b5-b3bb-424b-823f-729a41e48366/doc/%252Fdd1717070f-03d0-418d-d4c2-282b87790374%252Fdd4388b120-052f-dbea-43a2-e0276b01635e%252Flddefc094c-010d-471a-b921-5979404d505c%252Flf50d30878-ad1f-43ca-b4d9-d8caa360af48/grid/]]&gt; and functionality matrix with customers to help them select a new NCR partner. Please ensure your customers are aware of the January 31, 2021 deadline and are preparing to transition to other solutions. 

Read More &lt;[[https://ncr.quickbase.com/up/bqe6gx23b/g/rh/ek/va/End of Support for Aloha Guest Manager.pdf]]&gt;
More Aloha and Payments Training

Don’t miss this opportunity to take one of the three remaining training sessions available this month. Advanced registration in NCRU is required to reserve your spot. Stay tuned for a new round of courses coming in July.

${CTAText2} &lt;[[${CTAURL}?${url-parameter}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
