<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>04-08-21 HOS biWeekly Newsletter.Restaurants can learn from the 2008 financial c</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Restaurants can learn from the 2008 financial crisis</subject>
    <textOnly>April 8, 2021
What Can Restaurants Learn From the 2008 Financial Crisis?
After the 2008 financial crisis, financial institutions were facing a recovery, which became the catalyst for progress toward a more modern, more digital, more customer-centric banking industry. Similarly, in 2020 the pandemic was the catalyst that turned the hospitality industry on its head. And once again, the themes of recovery are very similar – Digital! Digital! Digital! Mobile ordering, online ordering, contactless menus, contactless order/pay, curbside and delivery, and the growth of ghost kitchens are key to growing your business in the new restaurant world. You need a strategy to enable these digital channels to serve your guests seamlessly and consistently across multiple channels. Read More &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/blogs/restaurants/restaurants-learn-from-financial-crisis]]&gt;
Kitchens are Playing Greater Role in Digital World
Technology has long been a difference maker for the restaurant industry, ushering in an array of practices that have made them more efficient and effective. The kitchen of today is a digital operation driven by vision and by adversity of the coronavirus pandemic. Innovations that were in the not-too-distant future were accelerated by months and even years due to the pandemic. Check out our white paper, Kitchens Playing Greater Role in Digital World &lt;[[https://ncr.quickbase.com/up/bqe6gx23b/g/rc7/ek/va/NCRHospitality_KitchensDigitalWorld_March2021.pdf]]&gt;, that explores four areas where technology in the kitchen will continue making an impact for restaurants.
Lokahi Podcast – Aloha Customer Chat With Thomas Ward of Pig Floyd&apos;s
Check out our latest Lokahi podcast episode &lt;[[https://ncr.seismic.com/Link/Content/DCakd7e_xK1EmUjIYZUKSTSw]]&gt; in which we had the pleasure of a one-on-one conversation with one of our Aloha customers - Thomas Ward of Pig 
Floyds in Orlando, Florida. Thomas shares candid insights about why he switched to Aloha, how the pandemic derailed expansion plans for his restaurant, and his thoughts on where the industry is going. There’s something for everyone to learn in this discussion.
More New Payments Training for Customers
NCR is offering five new payments training courses in April to help your customers better understand NCR Payment Solutions with Aloha. Please share this registration link &lt;[[https://email.ncr.com/NjA1LUJRWS03NDAAAAF8QBllnDi4T6vvutwOmonp-RNM4jWyxXsAklOtR2cYYilHWEC0ygb_wa5JTQJwW5lGIkidiag=]]&gt; with your customers. The sessions are also recorded so customers can listen when it’s most convenient for them. 

NCR Payment Solutions with Aloha – Overview
     •   Tuesday, April 13th, 2021 @ 10 AM CT
NCR Payment Solutions with Aloha - Payments Reconciliation
     •   Tuesday, April 13th, 2021 @ 3 
PM CT
NCR Payment Solutions with Aloha - Chargebacks 101
     •   Wednesday, April 14th, 2021 @ 10 AM CT
NCR Payment Solutions with Aloha - Resolve Settlement and Reconciliation Issues
     •   Wednesday, April 14th, 2021 @ 3 PM CT
NCR Payment Solutions with Aloha - Statements and Fees
     •   Thursday, April 15th, 2021 @ 10 AM CT
Last Call on Deeply Discounted S500 Servers!
This is your last chance to take advantage of the remaining S500 servers that NCR is offering at a deeply discounted price of over 50% off the MRP (list price). These S500 servers are brand new and come with a standard 1-year hardware warranty. You can place your order by following the normal ordering process. 

For any questions, contact Austin.Anderson@NCR.com &lt;[[mailto:Austin.Anderson@NCR.com]]&gt;.
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/ncrcorp/?${url-parameter}]]&gt;    &lt;[[https://twitter.com/NCRCorporation?${url-parameter}]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/ncrcorporation/?${url-parameter}&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=]]&gt;


 


© 2019 NCR Corporation All rights reserved.
864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
https://www.ncr.com/ &lt;[[https://www.ncr.com/?${url-parameter}]]&gt; | 
Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
