<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <name>Partner Quote Builder Communication HTML</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>ATTENTION - Partner Account new info</subject>
    <textOnly>CHANNEL ORDER PROCESS


Channel Ordering Process Enhancement

Dear {!Contact.Name},

As announced last Friday, Sept 21st, in NCR’s continuous effort to make every day easier, we are going to enhance our current ordering process. This change will happen on October 1st, 2018.

Key benefits:

Ability for all Partners to create and submit their own quotes in QuoteBuilder
Simplification of the ordering process
Reduction of the overall cycle time


As learnt during this week’s training session, QuoteBuilder is the tool used to configure quotes. The objective of this email is to provide you with all the key information you will need to start creating your own quotes.

Please find below your partner account detail information:

New Master Customer Number (MCN) ={!Account.Master_Customer_Number__c}
Channel Account Manager (CAM) = {!Account.OwnerFullName}
Sales Support contact = {!Account.Sales_Support_contact__c}
QB login steps (Guide) Link = 
https://ncr.my.salesforce.com/sfc/p/700000008mDk/a/0g000000PyNC/IUWB1u4FETRj2.sMwzRAt2R7u3g.hYmTS5cD3P48seg


Your Sales Support person will be the one that will provide further guidance on any questions you may have regarding the quoting process. Please contact them for further assistance, or with any questions.

If you were unable to attend the scheduled Quote creation training sessions, your Sales Support person will be able to send you a recording.

Resources:

Your Sales Support person will be your ‘go-to’ contact throughout the quoting process.
If you experience any application-related issues, please contact the support desk at Quotebuilder.SalesOpsSupport@ncr.com.


Irantzu Chinchetru
Channel Operations Sr. Manager
NCR Corporation
ic162500@ncr.com |  www.ncr.com

NCR and Partner Confidential.
NCR Corporation 864 Spring St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308
©2018 NCR Corporation. All rights reserved. ncr.com
To unsubscribe or manage subscriptions, please click here. NCR respects your privacy.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
