<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <letterhead>NCRLogoLetterhead</letterhead>
    <name>APTRA Exchange</name>
    <style>freeForm</style>
    <subject>Actions that need to be taken!</subject>
    <textOnly>{!Contact.FirstName},

I am following up on my voicemail as well as my previous email (see below) in regards to the Windows 10 migration for your ATM Fleet. It is imperative that we have a conversation about the actions that need to be taken to ensure that migration is fully completed by January 14th, 2020.


Does your schedule allow for a quick 15-minute call to discuss?


Also, if there is a better contact to speak with, please provide their contact information and I will be happy to reach out to them.



Thank you,



Martin Lopez

Sales Development Executive – Financial Services
NCR Corporation, World Headquarters Duluth GA USA
office: 678.808.7917 | mobile: 425-200-5654
martin.lopez@ncr.com | www.ncr.com

__________________________________________________

Windows 10 Pricing is Available






This is {!Contact.OwnerFirstName} with NCR. I am happy to report to you that pricing is now available for the Windows 10 Upgrade on your ATM Fleet.


Microsoft is discontinuing all services related to Windows 7 January 14th,2020. The reason we are reaching out now in regards to this is because it takes approximately 12-18 months to complete the migration process.


If you are not fully migrated by January 14th, 2020 you will lose the following services from Microsoft:


· Security Patches and Updates

· Auto-fixes

· Technical Support


We want to start this conversation with you as soon as possible to ensure uninterrupted ATM compliance with up to date security standards.


Please let me know the best time to speak with you.


Thank you,


Martin Lopez

Sales Development Executive – Financial Services
NCR Corporation, World Headquarters Duluth GA USA
office: 678.808.7917 | mobile: 425-200-5654
martin.lopez@ncr.com | www.ncr.com</textOnly>
    <type>html</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
