<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>June 6 Webinar</description>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <letterhead>General_Template</letterhead>
    <name>Webinar Omni-channel consumer experiences</name>
    <style>freeForm</style>
    <subject>NCR Software Webinar registration now open</subject>
    <textOnly>Register Now!



Webinar Title: Omni-channel consumer experiences, connecting physical and digital channels.
Date: 6th June
Time: 12 noon (ET), 9am (PT)
Duration: 45 Minutes
Speaker: Alex Borthwick, Global Solution Director



Are you able to deliver a consistent messaging approach to your customers across both digital and physical channels?

NCR enables banks to seamlessly create, manage, distribute and measure their marketing communication strategy across ATMs, mobiles, web, email, electronic receipts, SMS, digital signage and Kiosks.

Are your ATMs part of your digital experience today?
Are you looking for an opportunity to target customers of the competition in a relevant way?
How important is overall user experience to your customer retention?
Are you considering the following issues:

Attract customers to adopt further channels
Are customer contact details an issue for the bank?


What if you
-   Were able to market directly to people who aren’t your customers?
-   Had the ability to reuse marketing assets from digital channels at the ATM
-   Could deliver a connected experience across channels
-   Can build your databank of customers and key contact details
-   Had seamless management of leads from one channel to another

What if you could
-   Deliver a more personalized and interactive service that has direct benefit to you and your customer?

Retain customers through personalization and more joined up experiences?

Please register HERE for the CxMarketing Webinar.



Regards,


Martin Lopez

Sales Development Executive – Financial Services
NCR Corporation, World Headquarters Duluth GA USA
office: 678.808.7917 | mobile: 425-200-5654
martin.lopez@ncr.com | www.ncr.com</textOnly>
    <type>html</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
